<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Derek Llambias on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/derek-llambias/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Derek Llambias on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 12:01:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/derek-llambias/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Graham Carr labels Mike Ashley &amp; Derek Llambias as “fantastic people to work for”</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/13/graham-carr-labels-mike-ashley-derek-llambias-as-fantastic-people-to-work-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 12:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/13/graham-carr-labels-mike-ashley-derek-llambias-as-fantastic-people-to-work-for/</guid>
      <description>Signings - Tioté and Yohan Cabaye signings advised by chief scout Graham Carr Despite the extraordinary outburst by Derek Llambias last night Graham Carr has only positive things to say about the two men that run this football club; Mike Ashley &amp;amp; Derek Llambias. Both are still seen as businessmen and their disregard for the supporters of this great football club is held against them, time and time again. They&amp;rsquo;ve made some ridiculous decisions in their time on Tyneside it has to be said but financially they&amp;rsquo;ve brought Newcastle Unite back on a sound footing and are hoping to break-even in the books this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Same old excuses and same old lies from the hierarchy at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/03/same-old-excuses-and-same-old-lies-from-the-hierarchy-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 15:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/03/same-old-excuses-and-same-old-lies-from-the-hierarchy-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Llambias - Released statement explaining failed striker hunt after window shut When the window slammed shut at 11PM on Thursday night most Newcastle United fans were disappointed, tired, and angered that we hadn&amp;rsquo;t managed to recruit a new striker with £40m plus in our back-pockets and with over 8 months to do it. Of course we got Demba Ba in early on in the season - because he was a free transfer, looked for modest wages and wasn&amp;rsquo;t incredibly old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Chris Hughton isn’t offered a nice new contract by Newcastle, there’ll be war</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/09/if-chris-hughton-isnt-offered-a-nice-new-contract-by-newcastle-therell-be-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/09/if-chris-hughton-isnt-offered-a-nice-new-contract-by-newcastle-therell-be-war/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Has done a fantastic job since taking over a sinking ship What can we say about this man? Bringing a relegated club back up to the Premier League straight away, with a record number of points, buying for pennies, some seriously talented footballers, going to Stamford Bridge in the Cup and scoring 4 goals, including an injury time winner in one of the most memorable cup games of the decade, giving us a 5-1 thrashing of our bitter rivals Sunderland to celebrate about, and on Sunday last, bringing us to the Emirates Stadium where we beat Arsenal 0-1 thanks to an Andy Carroll header, courtesy of a much practiced tactic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llambias – Newcastle United not for sale anytime soon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/03/llambias-newcastle-united-not-for-sale-anytime-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 20:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/03/llambias-newcastle-united-not-for-sale-anytime-soon/</guid>
      <description>Ashley - No plans to sell Newcastle United FC in the very near future He&amp;rsquo;s a man we&amp;rsquo;ve wanted out for a couple of years now. I do mention &amp;lsquo;we&amp;rsquo; because I&amp;rsquo;m sure every Newcastle United fan out there, young and old, saw what has happened since Mike Ashley took over. Relegation and so on, but let&amp;rsquo;s not get into that as it&amp;rsquo;s been discussed many a time before. There&amp;rsquo;s an interesting article in the Telegraph today with Derek Llambias and indeed his &amp;amp; Mike&amp;rsquo;s stance on Newcastle United FC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>