<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mike Ashley on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/mike-ashley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mike Ashley on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 16:00:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/mike-ashley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Relieved’ Mike Ashley will be in for a shock in the near future</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/10/20/relieved-mike-ashley-will-shock-near-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/10/20/relieved-mike-ashley-will-shock-near-future/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but have a good laugh to myself when I heard that Mike Ashley had visited the home dressing-room after Saturday&amp;rsquo;s 1-0 victory over Leicester City to congratulate the players on securing their first Premier League win of the season. It just proved to countless NUFC and myself - something we already knew: Mike Ashley has no understanding of the game. When Leicester City failed to take their chances in front of goal and Gabriel Obertan eventually went on to score a fine solo effort to secure all three points, it was an almost embarrassing victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley already planning summer transfers on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/22/mike-ashley-already-planning-transfers-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 16:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/22/mike-ashley-already-planning-transfers-summer/</guid>
      <description>While every Newcastle United fan, women, child and dog hope to see the news that Mike Ashley has agreed a deal to sell the club to an ambitious owner, such a dream looks like it is a far away prospect according to recent developments at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park. Manager Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s future has been called into question over recent form, and based on results from the turn of the year Pardew should be jobless, there is no debating that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United made record offer for Luuk de Jong</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/05/newcastle-united-made-record-offer-for-luuk-de-jong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 13:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/05/newcastle-united-made-record-offer-for-luuk-de-jong/</guid>
      <description>#### Ashley - Willing to part with his highest ever sum since taking charge of NUFC
Not many people might have realised, but our £11m bid deemed unacceptable by FC Twente, for their star man Luuk de Jong, happened to be the highest ever bid Mike Ashley has financed in his NUFC tenure thus far. When Ashley arrived on Tyneside, he immediately threw forward £10.3m to sign Fabricio Coloccini - a well spent ten million if you ask me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Same old excuses and same old lies from the hierarchy at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/03/same-old-excuses-and-same-old-lies-from-the-hierarchy-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 15:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/03/same-old-excuses-and-same-old-lies-from-the-hierarchy-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Llambias - Released statement explaining failed striker hunt after window shut When the window slammed shut at 11PM on Thursday night most Newcastle United fans were disappointed, tired, and angered that we hadn&amp;rsquo;t managed to recruit a new striker with £40m plus in our back-pockets and with over 8 months to do it. Of course we got Demba Ba in early on in the season - because he was a free transfer, looked for modest wages and wasn&amp;rsquo;t incredibly old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian plans £260m offer for Newcastle United when 2011/12 Premier League status is confirmed</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/13/wealthy-indian-plans-260m-offer-for-newcastle-united-when-201112-premier-league-status-is-confirmed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 00:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/13/wealthy-indian-plans-260m-offer-for-newcastle-united-when-201112-premier-league-status-is-confirmed/</guid>
      <description>Pull the other one one might say. However, news is news. According for the Sunday Mirror; Newcastle United could be owned by a wealthy Indian in the summer, should they confirm Premier League safety. A £260m figure is being touted as the price tag Anil Ambani is willing to offer Mike, but the real question is: would the smart-minded Englishman accept that bundle of notes? Again, take this with a rather large pinch of salt because I expect it to be utter tosh, per usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United close to signing Ben Arfa – An early Christmas present?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/23/newcastle-united-close-to-signing-ben-arfa-an-early-christmas-present/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 16:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/23/newcastle-united-close-to-signing-ben-arfa-an-early-christmas-present/</guid>
      <description>#### Ben Arfa - Wants to play for Newcastle United and is looking for permanent deal
We may well be in for an early Christmas present with the new that Hatem Ben Arfa, could be quite close to a permanent deal at Newcastle United. The French winger who joined this summer thanks to Chris Hughton, played less than five games, in which he scored a stunner against Everton at Goodison Park, in an excellent away win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Newcastle United need to sign anyone this January transfer window?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/do-newcastle-united-need-to-sign-anyone-this-january-transfer-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 01:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/do-newcastle-united-need-to-sign-anyone-this-january-transfer-window/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people aren&amp;rsquo;t really sure of Alan Pardew yet, and one of the areas he can send out a message to Newcastle United fans is in the transfer market. In 10 or so days times, the January transfer window will open for business. Teams will enquire for players, other will try their utmost to hang on to their key men. Indeed that&amp;rsquo;s what I expect us to do this January, try keep Andy Carroll, Joey Barton and some of our youngsters at NUFC for the remainder of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United 3-1 Liverpool – A Tribute to Chris Hughton</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/11/newcastle-united-3-1-liverpool-a-tribute-to-chris-hughton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 23:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/11/newcastle-united-3-1-liverpool-a-tribute-to-chris-hughton/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Scored a peach of a goal today in a very good win dedicated to Chris First things first - what a brave man Mike Ashley is showing up to Newcastle United v Liverpool today. I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to see his unsightly figure in the luxurious stands of St.James&amp;rsquo; Park during Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s first game in charge. However, I expect it was exactly that that lured the owner to the game, to oversee his new signing, and to decide whether he needed the sack just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley proves yet again what an incompetent, clueless owner he really is</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/07/mike-ashley-proves-yet-again-what-an-incompetent-clueless-owner-he-really-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 20:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/07/mike-ashley-proves-yet-again-what-an-incompetent-clueless-owner-he-really-is/</guid>
      <description>I heard at about 1.10pm roughly from a source at the club that Chris Hughton was on his way out of St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. It was shocking news to receive, especially for me when I was stuck on a three hour long bus journey. However, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure whether it was confirmed or not. At 2pm that day (yesterday) Newcastle United confirmed that Chris Hughton had been sacked as manager of Newcastle United and the search for a replacement had already begun, with Peter Beardsley taking charge of the Liverpool game forthcoming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacking Chris Hughton would be the worst decision made by NUFC since Sir Bobby’s dismissal</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/06/sacking-chris-hughton-worst-decision-nufc-since-sir-bobbys-dismissal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/06/sacking-chris-hughton-worst-decision-nufc-since-sir-bobbys-dismissal/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - William Hill have suspended betting on his dismissal this afternoon First things first - surely this cannot be right? Chris Hughton, the man who brought Newcastle United from the Championship back up to the Premier League with a record number of points, was responsible for the 5-1 thrashing of our rivals this season, our fantastic display against Chelsea in the Cup with a 4-3 win at Stamford Bridge, and the man who guided NUFC to a precious 1-0 away win at the Emirates to Arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Chris Hughton isn’t offered a nice new contract by Newcastle, there’ll be war</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/09/if-chris-hughton-isnt-offered-a-nice-new-contract-by-newcastle-therell-be-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/09/if-chris-hughton-isnt-offered-a-nice-new-contract-by-newcastle-therell-be-war/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Has done a fantastic job since taking over a sinking ship What can we say about this man? Bringing a relegated club back up to the Premier League straight away, with a record number of points, buying for pennies, some seriously talented footballers, going to Stamford Bridge in the Cup and scoring 4 goals, including an injury time winner in one of the most memorable cup games of the decade, giving us a 5-1 thrashing of our bitter rivals Sunderland to celebrate about, and on Sunday last, bringing us to the Emirates Stadium where we beat Arsenal 0-1 thanks to an Andy Carroll header, courtesy of a much practiced tactic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle’s Five Year Plans could find Chris Hughton’s men in trouble</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/05/10/newcastles-five-year-plans-could-find-chris-hughtons-men-in-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 21:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/05/10/newcastles-five-year-plans-could-find-chris-hughtons-men-in-trouble/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Really does need a couple of signings this summer to get things right I suppose when you see the demise of Portsmouth Football Club and indeed the serous financial state of many well known clubs across the land, you know it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be long before Newcastle United would be hit with some sort of financial implication. Indeed here it is. A statement released by the club yesterday outlined the boards&amp;rsquo; plans for the coming few years, which 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United considering keeping Fitz Hall permanently</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</guid>
      <description>There are reports flying about the place in the last couple of days that Fitz Hall could be arriving on Tyneside on a permanent basis once the transfer window reopens. The defender, on-loan from Queens Park Rangers has seen a turbulent time at Loftus Road and indeed has seen the club dig their way through more than 3 managers this season. Their current manager in Neil Warnock could well have very different plans for the back four he wants next season and indeed Hall may not be included in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United need to buy this Summer if we want to stay up</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</guid>
      <description>Owen - We don&amp;rsquo;t want too many signings similar to this guy anytime soon The day we splashed a record-breaking £15m to bring Alan Shearer to Newcastle from Premier League winning Blackburn Rovers, the footballing world came to a standstill and admired the Tyneside team for their courage in doing so, or at least we like to think they did! What a signing Alan Shearer turned about to be though, a true predator in front of goal and one of the best English strikers ever, if not the.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llambias – Newcastle United not for sale anytime soon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/03/llambias-newcastle-united-not-for-sale-anytime-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 20:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/03/llambias-newcastle-united-not-for-sale-anytime-soon/</guid>
      <description>Ashley - No plans to sell Newcastle United FC in the very near future He&amp;rsquo;s a man we&amp;rsquo;ve wanted out for a couple of years now. I do mention &amp;lsquo;we&amp;rsquo; because I&amp;rsquo;m sure every Newcastle United fan out there, young and old, saw what has happened since Mike Ashley took over. Relegation and so on, but let&amp;rsquo;s not get into that as it&amp;rsquo;s been discussed many a time before. There&amp;rsquo;s an interesting article in the Telegraph today with Derek Llambias and indeed his &amp;amp; Mike&amp;rsquo;s stance on Newcastle United FC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United lucky not to have encountered administration</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/23/newcastle-united-lucky-not-to-be-in-administration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 22:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/23/newcastle-united-lucky-not-to-be-in-administration/</guid>
      <description>Mike - Love him or loath him he&amp;rsquo;s kept NUFC in a financially stable condition You only have to look at Portsmouth FC to see what the economic recession is doing to football. Stoke City&amp;rsquo;s 1-2 win against Avram Grant&amp;rsquo;s side was rumoured to have been the last ever game played in Fratton Park, however whether this is true or not, I really don&amp;rsquo;t know. Either way, Pompey are in a serious financial mess at the minute and the signs for the future are not good at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley more involved in Newcastle United’s Coca Cola Championship season</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/19/mike-ashley-more-involved-in-newcastle-uniteds-coca-cola-championship-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/19/mike-ashley-more-involved-in-newcastle-uniteds-coca-cola-championship-season/</guid>
      <description>In a season that has saw our owner Mike Ashley try to sell but failing miserably yet again, however finally deciding to establish a tad of stability at the club. By that, it meant selling players, keeping some and after a long debacle as to who would be the full-time manager of Newcastle United, appointing Chris Hughton the former assistant of Kevin Keegan and Alan Shearer (alongside Iain Dowie). Hughton has since guided us to a pretty decent season so far which sees us top of the Coca Cola Championship, as we enter the final stages of what&amp;rsquo;s been a long season, and it&amp;rsquo;s still not over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portsmouth or Newcastle need to fork out an extra £1.2m or Williamson won’t arrive on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/22/portsmouth-or-newcastle-need-to-fork-out-an-extra-1-2m-or-williamson-wont-arrive-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 22:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/22/portsmouth-or-newcastle-need-to-fork-out-an-extra-1-2m-or-williamson-wont-arrive-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Pompey - A real mess at that club right now both financially and on the fields After successfully completing a medical on Tyneside, Mike Williamson was expected to secure a £1m transfer to Newcastle today. However, some late checks on the contract by Pompey have resulted in them finding a snag or a little clause that they had forgot about. Sky Sports (who else?) reported that the deal had indeed been stalled after the club found the clause and they want Newcastle United to pay it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Players will be signed in January if needed – Llambias</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/23/players-will-be-signed-in-january-if-needed-llambias/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/23/players-will-be-signed-in-january-if-needed-llambias/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - Might actually invest in January in promotion bid
There&amp;rsquo;s some unbelievable news regarding Newcastle United today, Managing Director Derek Llambias has confirmed that Chris Hughton will be given cash to spend on new players if he needs. Ok, it mightn&amp;rsquo;t be that unbelievable but it might come as a surprise to some fans. Speaking today, Llambias said that Chris will be supported in the January transfer window by Mike Ashley and that it will be Chris&amp;rsquo;s own players that arrive at the club, if any players happen to arrive at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Mike Ashley really thinking of selling?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/06/is-mike-ashley-really-thinking-of-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 15:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/06/is-mike-ashley-really-thinking-of-selling/</guid>
      <description>News is emerging from the ever unreliable News Of The World, that Mike Ashley is contemplating selling the club, in January. However, I find that a little hard to believe considering we lie top of the Championship, have a huge amount of players and their hefty wages shipped off the wage bill and seem to be actually enjoying our football at the minute. Of course meaning that should we continue our good form until May, then Newcastle United will be a Premier League team, the clubs value will have doubled and so will it&amp;rsquo;s revenues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the impossible becoming possible?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/27/is-the-impossible-becoming-possible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2009 21:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/27/is-the-impossible-becoming-possible/</guid>
      <description>Ashley - Beginning to take some responsibility? I know it might be a tough question to ask and one that will have a common answer but it&amp;rsquo;s worth taking a look at this issue all the same. Although we haven&amp;rsquo;t heard much about, from or to him of late, it seems as if Mike Ashley has settled down just a little bit. Ashley who took us off the market for a second time earlier this season because he failed to sell, is slowly but surely eeking a possible title of a football club owner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Possibly the most pointless move to date?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/05/possibly-the-most-pointless-move-to-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 16:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/05/possibly-the-most-pointless-move-to-date/</guid>
      <description>### St. James&amp;rsquo; Park - &amp;lsquo;New&amp;rsquo; name utter nonsense
They insist that the new name is to bolster revenue for the club, and for Chris Hughton&amp;rsquo;s transfer pot. However, naming it Ashley&amp;rsquo;s own company brings us absolutely no funding and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a mathematician to figure out that it means no cash for Chris in January either. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m wrong and that there will be some cash injected from Sports Direct but in all fairness , there would need to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley is caught between two stools</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/04/ashley-is-caught-between-two-stools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 17:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/04/ashley-is-caught-between-two-stools/</guid>
      <description>Ashley - All his eggs in one basket at Newcastle If Newcastle United are not promoted come May, which is a very strong possibility, then Mike Ashley is in serious serious bother. After taking the club off the market for a second time, he now is hoping that we are brought straight back to the Premier League at first attempt, guided by Chris Hughton. To back up his hopes he&amp;rsquo;s promised Chris that&amp;rsquo;ll he&amp;rsquo;ll back him both as manager and in the transfer window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley promises Hughton a nice pot of gold – Sure</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/28/mike-ashley-promises-hughton-a-nice-pot-of-gold-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 16:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/28/mike-ashley-promises-hughton-a-nice-pot-of-gold-sure/</guid>
      <description>### Hughton - No grudge against him getting the job
The worst insult that a Newcastle United fan could get is not only destroying their beloved club, but trying to destroy their stadium name. Yesterday, on top of the devastating news that Mike Ashley had taken Newcastle United off the market, he also said that they were open to any offers for the naming rights of the stadium. This, is probably the cheekiest, and most arrogant move he has taken to date, and you really have to question yourself if he&amp;rsquo;s that stupid or being an outright (Insert your own word here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley takes Newcastle off the market</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/27/mike-ashley-takes-newcastle-off-the-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 22:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/27/mike-ashley-takes-newcastle-off-the-market/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - Going to put another £20m into the club quickly
The worst news possible has come today with owner Mike Ashley confirming he has taken the club off the market and has appointed Chris Hughton as permanent manager on an 18-month contract. This isn&amp;rsquo;t surprising news but devastating all the same. To cap it all, Ashley claims to invest £20m immediately and bring the club forward. Not the first time we&amp;rsquo;ve heard this and it&amp;rsquo;s sure to cause uproar amongst the Toon faithful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another one bites Ashleys’ dust</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/26/another-one-bites-ashleys-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 15:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/26/another-one-bites-ashleys-dust/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - Deliberating whether to stay or to sell
It&amp;rsquo;s amazing the number of articles I&amp;rsquo;ve written and Mike Ashley has been the subject of, and quite frankly, annoying. The infamous &amp;lsquo;owner&amp;rsquo; has today, if you are to believe the Chronicle, broken off talks with Geoff Sheard&amp;rsquo;s American based investment group. The news comes after Newcastle victory against Doncaster and we can&amp;rsquo;t say it&amp;rsquo;s a surprise really. Mike Ashley&amp;rsquo;s patience is meant to have reached it&amp;rsquo;s limit, (the irony) and he&amp;rsquo;s pulled out of negotiations with the much talked about consortium led by the questionable Geoff Sheard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another waste of time for NUFC</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/19/another-waste-of-time-for-nufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 15:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/19/another-waste-of-time-for-nufc/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - About to take NUFC off the market - again
I&amp;rsquo;m sorry if this article sounds a bit pessimistic but it&amp;rsquo;s hard not to be on a downer. News has broken today that Chris Hughton will be offered the full-time job and that later this week he&amp;rsquo;ll accept the final terms of what I&amp;rsquo;m sure will be quite a lucrative contract. However, that&amp;rsquo;s not the bad part, actually that probably the best news we could have expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Mike Ashley have a case?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/18/does-mike-ashley-have-a-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 18:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/18/does-mike-ashley-have-a-case/</guid>
      <description>Before I start,I&amp;rsquo;d like to say I don&amp;rsquo;t think Mr.Ashley has a case and today&amp;rsquo;s tattle in the media is being perhaps just a little rich from his side. Speaking today Mike said that&amp;rsquo;s he has lowered the asking price, to an initial fee of £80m and that Barry Moat&amp;rsquo;s persistence in buying the club has been ongoing, for nearly two years. It&amp;rsquo;s obvious that Mike himself is frustrated at the stage of the sale and that it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been completed yet but he just doesn&amp;rsquo;t realise how we feel as our beloved club is being dangled over a burning pit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley finally speaks as he lowers asking price to £80m</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/18/mike-ashley-finany-speaks-as-he-lowers-asking-price-to-80m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 12:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/18/mike-ashley-finany-speaks-as-he-lowers-asking-price-to-80m/</guid>
      <description>Ashley - Lowers asking price to £80m There is some quite astonishing news today that Newcastle United owner Mike Ashley has first of all, spoken to the media for the first time in months and indeed that he has lowered his asking price of the club to £80m. Speaking today to the Sunday Times he claims that he&amp;rsquo;s done his very best to sell the club and that Barry Moat has been on his case for the last two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Moat about to keep Newcastle afloat</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/06/barry-moat-about-to-keep-newcastle-afloat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 15:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/06/barry-moat-about-to-keep-newcastle-afloat/</guid>
      <description>As it finally seems Mike Ashley will pack his bags and leave Newcastle United, a little premature excitement is creeping in. Not just the fact he&amp;rsquo;s leaving (or so we are led to believe) but also the reality that we are set to get a local owner, and not many clubs can say that. Today reports say that Mr.Barry Moat has written a letter to Mike with a formal offer, expected to be in the region of £90-95m and we expect our current owner to accept it or God knows what will happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley days are finally numbered</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/04/mike-ashley-days-are-finally-numbered/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2009 12:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/04/mike-ashley-days-are-finally-numbered/</guid>
      <description>### Moat - At long last will complete takeover
Finally the day has come when I can say that Mike Ashley will not be Newcastle United owner for another few months. The Keegan scenario has been dealt with and £2m is a shock relief for Mike Ashley and his compatriots. This is good news, as it means that the wreckage has been cleared from the track to complete the sale of Newcastle United, and the long awaited one at that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Price of Keegan departure – £2m and relegation</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/02/price-of-keegan-departure-2m-and-relegation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 15:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/02/price-of-keegan-departure-2m-and-relegation/</guid>
      <description>### Kevin - Insistent on suing Mike Ashley
It&amp;rsquo;s a sad day to see a former Newcastle footballer and manager, win a court case against his &amp;lsquo;beloved&amp;rsquo; club. However, you have to look at Mike Ashley&amp;rsquo;s side of the story. Perhaps he deserved it, maybe there&amp;rsquo;s no question about it, but surely you think that Keegan wouldn&amp;rsquo;t go to such lengths just to be able to say he was right. Today Mike Ashley was ordered to pay £2m in compensation to Kevin and perhaps even more, dependent on future developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silence is deafening on takeover front</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/28/silence-is-deafening-on-takeover-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 15:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/28/silence-is-deafening-on-takeover-front/</guid>
      <description>The news hasn&amp;rsquo;t bee based on the takeover news this Sunday or indeed the last week, which is quite surprising. Barry Moat is still on course to complete the takeover of our beloved club but he;s waiting on the Kevin Keegan court case to be settled before he&amp;rsquo;s handed the keys of St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. You can imagine the scenes around Newcastle when Mike Ashley finally leaves the club, and a local owner with every ambition to appoint Alan Shearer as manager, control the club properly, or so we hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marlon’s a Magpie as King Kev awaits decision</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/25/marlons-a-magpie-as-king-kev-awaits-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/25/marlons-a-magpie-as-king-kev-awaits-decision/</guid>
      <description>### Harewood - Enjoying his first training session
It could only happen at Newcastle, where their local cult hero, leaves the club, not for the first time, and then, turn around and tries to sue the clubs owner. As yo probably guessed it&amp;rsquo;s Kevin Keegan I&amp;rsquo;m talking about and his little affair with Mike Ashley. Today, the case closed are the tribunal resigned in order to make their decision. Whether Keegan will win his case is still unknown but he must be pretty confident when he&amp;rsquo;s brought the millionaire to the courts over &amp;lsquo;an unfair dismissal&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle sale in final stages – again</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/19/newcastle-sale-in-final-stages-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/19/newcastle-sale-in-final-stages-again/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - Agreed fee with unnamed group
We haven&amp;rsquo;t heard much on the Newcastle United sale lately but today brings news that a fee has been agreed with a buyer. The club issued an official statement to the &amp;lsquo;Journal&amp;rsquo; saying that the £100m had been met but the overdraft was still a stumbling block as well as the Kevin Keegan scenario. Although Barry Moat is being strongly linked with the role, and it&amp;rsquo;s more than likely he is the man involved, there are reported to be two other bidders interested in the club, but yet to make an official bid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Moat is Newcastle’s last chance saloon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/24/barry-moat-is-newcastles-last-chance-saloon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 14:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/24/barry-moat-is-newcastles-last-chance-saloon/</guid>
      <description>Ashley - Still in control Mike Ashley is still in control of Newcastle United, 13 weeks after we suffered the dreaded drop to the Coca Cola Championship. The news today, is that the deadline has been extended for Barry Moat to complete the takeover of the club but that news, carries both good and bad consequences. First of all it means we probably will not sign anyone this transfer window at all but the upside is, that Mike Ashley is very much willing to sell to Barry Moat and is trying his utmost to hand over the club to the local businessman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor could well have played his last game for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad when it has come to this, a Newcastle United player, brought through the ranks, and having becoming a Newcastle United first team member, looking for the exit door at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. Sky Sports News (who else?) are reporting that the local lad, could be set for a move to David Moyes&amp;rsquo;s Everton side who are fighting a losing battle with their own English centre back, Joleon Lescott. If this news is true, which we hope it&amp;rsquo;s not, then it&amp;rsquo;ll really put gas to the fire and the frustration will be taken out on Mike Ashley more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llambias – Barry Moat close to completing takeover</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/llambias-barry-moat-close-to-completing-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/llambias-barry-moat-close-to-completing-takeover/</guid>
      <description>We can&amp;rsquo;t fault the lads performances over the season so far, two wins and a draw, that draw being a dreaded away trip to the Hawthorns for any other Championship side. However Newcastle United are not any Championship side, only at Newcastle could we attract nearly 44,000 to a home game, mind you, it only being the third game of the season and the traveling Geordies weren&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. Another Ameobi goal and another three points, leaving Newcastle 3rd in the Coca Cola Championship league standings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The man leading ‘Fans 410’ bid for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/the-man-leading-fans-410-bid-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 14:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/the-man-leading-fans-410-bid-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>There has been a new spanner thrown into the works at Newcastle United now as yesterday, Sky Sports were told that Graham Roberts, a former footballer was heading a bid from a consortium called &amp;lsquo;Fans 410&amp;rsquo;, to buy Newcastle United. This news comes just as Barry Moat was close to sealing the club but now the former defender said that he has friends who want to own a football club and that the Magpies are the perfect opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moat may not complete Newcastle sale</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/moat-may-not-complete-newcastle-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 11:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/moat-may-not-complete-newcastle-sale/</guid>
      <description>The future of Newcastle United lies with a bank called Barclays, the sponsors of the Premier League. Today (Wednesday), Barry Moat was expected to hear back on whether he&amp;rsquo;s request was successful. If he is not which there is a good chance in happening, then Newcastle will remain in the hands of Mike Ashley until January at the very least, however, we&amp;rsquo;re hopeful that Moat does indeed get his loan from Barry Moat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Moat has competition for Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/18/barry-moat-has-competition-for-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/18/barry-moat-has-competition-for-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>Derek Llambias today confirmed to Sky Sports News that Barry Moat has indeed begun talks with the clubs hierarchy over the sale of the beleaguered club. Moat was present at our 3-0 win over Reading in which was one of the finest games the lads have played in St.James&amp;rsquo; Park in a long time. At the final whistle, Moat was seen shaking hands with Mike Ashley, perhaps just a business style fashion but it could be interpreted as agreeing on the sale of the club in principle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shola strolls in St.James’ success</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/15/shola-strolls-in-st-james-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/15/shola-strolls-in-st-james-success/</guid>
      <description>### Ameobi - Sublime three goals today
In a game which saw potential Newcastle United owner Barry Moat sit inbetween the current hierarchy at Newcastle of Mike Ashley and Derek Llambias, Newcastle produced a performance to remember and one needed to boost all sides morale. Newcastle started the game brightly creating chances and were comfortably controlling the game. Jonas was presented with a great opportunity after a Kevin Nolan through ball but the Argentine per usual, stumbled and didn&amp;rsquo;t show an end product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley ready to accept defeat on Newcastle sale and stay on</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/mike-ashley-ready-to-accept-defeat-on-newcastle-sale-and-stay-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 14:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/mike-ashley-ready-to-accept-defeat-on-newcastle-sale-and-stay-on/</guid>
      <description>As I said in my previous article, the loan signing of Danny Simpson could have well indicated that Mike Ashley is staying as owner and breaking news from Sky Sports and their North Eastern reporter, David Craig indicate Ashley will take the club off the market in about a week if no one comes forward to offer an acceptable amount. What ever happened to Barry Moat and his deposit today or about them being in talks with more consortia that just Moat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simpson loan signing may indicate Ashley is staying on</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/simpson-loan-signing-may-indicate-ashley-is-staying-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/simpson-loan-signing-may-indicate-ashley-is-staying-on/</guid>
      <description>When you see loan signings coming to Newcastle you might, first of all, surprised that we have even attempted to sign a player or secondly there has been some development in the sale of the club. However, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get too excited as I think it could mean something far worse, Ashley staying on at Newcastle and regaining control of our club for another season. Sky Sports have just announced that David O&amp;rsquo;Leary is out of the running (Good) and that the post is still under consideration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley and Moat both stubborn businessmen</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/12/ashley-and-moat-both-stubborn-businessmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 13:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/12/ashley-and-moat-both-stubborn-businessmen/</guid>
      <description>### Moat - Stubborn as Ashley
OK, you might be saying to yourself, Ashley is far from a businessman and has no brain at all. Each day it keeps tilting towards that instinct but considering he was a billionaire, he must have done some things right. He&amp;rsquo;s the owner of most Sports Direct retail stores, and even though their sales went sky high this year, their operating profit has decreased steadily from the last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ball is in Barry Moat’s court now</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/11/the-ball-is-in-barry-moats-court-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 13:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/11/the-ball-is-in-barry-moats-court-now/</guid>
      <description>Moat - Needs to deposit funds by Friday It seems that the decision is with Barry Moat whether to buy the club at this stage. It&amp;rsquo;s understood that Mike Ashley is willing to accept the offer from Moat but he wants a deposit by Friday in an unspecified bank account. If Moat can do this then he will complete the takeover and we will be finally be Ashley free. Whether Moat can agree to this is another thing, Ashley will then take Newcastle United off the market and appoint either David O&amp;rsquo;Leary or Joe Kinnear to the managerial role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley likely to stay on as owner</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/10/mike-ashley-likely-to-stay-on-as-owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 14:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/10/mike-ashley-likely-to-stay-on-as-owner/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - His reign to continue
All the hopes we had after relegation, of Shearer bringing us back up to the Premier League under new ownership and the most appetizing thought of them all Mike Ashley ending his tenure in charge of the club. Well it seems we&amp;rsquo;re all going to be disappointed again, with Mike Ashley about to take the club off the market. We&amp;rsquo;ve had Malaysians, Iranians, Americans, Englishmen, Irish, Singaporean and many more supposed interest in NUFC but none of the them had come to bear fruit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley has one last chance</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/09/mike-ashley-has-one-last-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 11:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/09/mike-ashley-has-one-last-chance/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - Coming back from holiday
Mike Ashley, the torrid owner of Newcastle United, has one last chance to get out of the club before it&amp;rsquo;s too late, yet again. It&amp;rsquo;s being reported today that Ashley is flying back from Hawaii , cutting short an undeserved holiday to return and discuss Barry Moat&amp;rsquo;s bid. It&amp;rsquo;s believed Moat has bid around £70m and Ashley isn&amp;rsquo;t too keen on accepting it, only thing is, it&amp;rsquo;s the only bidder let on the table with the Profitable Group having pulled out a while back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Barry Moat float our boat?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/06/will-barry-moat-float-our-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 14:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/06/will-barry-moat-float-our-boat/</guid>
      <description>Moat - Has reportedly bid £100m The latest news coming for St.James&amp;rsquo; Park is that a local business tycoon has bid £100m for Newcastle United. This news comes as yesterdays article from The Times and The Chronicle claimed that local business tycoon was ready to invest into the club. Moat is a luxury box-office holder at Newcastle and has been for some time now. The payment from which he renewed his season ticket, the money was used in the youth setup and invested in that area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye to a flipping legend</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/goodbye-to-a-flipping-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 21:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/goodbye-to-a-flipping-legend/</guid>
      <description>Martins - The goal that nearly kept us up It&amp;rsquo;s well and truly the end of an era when you see Obafemi Martins departing from St.James&amp;rsquo;. Although he had mixed receptions from supporters it was pretty clear he was loved upon Tyneside and will be sorely missed in our front line. Martins scored an abundance of goals in his first season after arriving for £10m and earned Alan Shearer&amp;rsquo;s much coveted #9 shirt for Newcastle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Newcastle United ready for a season in the Coca Cola Championship?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/28/are-newcastle-united-ready-for-a-season-in-the-coca-cola-championship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 16:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/28/are-newcastle-united-ready-for-a-season-in-the-coca-cola-championship/</guid>
      <description>Players - Can they gain automatic promotion? With the new Coca Cola Championship season only days away we look at players who we think can lead us back to where we belong, the Premier League. When we look for a leader in a team that had the 5th highest wage bill in the Premier, and were relegated, what leaders just shoot out of a bunch of over-paid Prima donnas? There&amp;rsquo;s not many, which is rather alerting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profitable Group can’t provide any proof of funds</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/28/profitable-group-cant-provide-any-proof-of-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 10:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/28/profitable-group-cant-provide-any-proof-of-funds/</guid>
      <description>This doesn&amp;rsquo;t really come as much of a shock to us Newcastle fans, because we questioned their interest when it all started long ago. The Profitable Group who declared an interest in Newcastle, saying they wanted to expand the stadium to 60,000 , appoint Shearer and give him a nice transfer kitty, have &amp;lsquo;pulled&amp;rsquo; out of the race for the club. According to SSN the group couldn&amp;rsquo;t provide any proof of funds to Mike Ashley and co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Derek Llambias know what’s going on?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/27/does-derek-llambias-know-whats-going-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 13:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/27/does-derek-llambias-know-whats-going-on/</guid>
      <description>Llambias - What can believe from this guy? Another day passes and another day missed for Newcastle United. Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s game at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park for Sir Bobby Robson was a great scene and a very much deserved ovation for the legend that is Sir Bobby. England went on to win the game 3-2 courtesy of a Shearer penalty in which he earned the penalty too. Indeed any time Shearer did get the ball, it was met with a huge roar of excitement and Alan, was looking as sharp as ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley happy to let mighty Newcastle fans suffer</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/26/mike-ashley-happy-to-let-mighty-newcastle-fans-suffer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 13:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/26/mike-ashley-happy-to-let-mighty-newcastle-fans-suffer/</guid>
      <description>Fans - Tired of Ashley and his ownership After an embarrassing defeat to Leyton Orient yesterday it really put a cap on Mike Ashley&amp;rsquo;s tenure. Probably the biggest friendly loss in a long time, the Newcastle players didn&amp;rsquo;t seem bothered, besides the odd exception. It can&amp;rsquo;t be called anything short of a disgrace and Leyton players were magnificent to say the least. Mind you, Orient are a League 1 side and we have to play many a Championship game this year, who inevitably will be better than Leyton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Mike Ashley the worst football club owner ever?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/is-mike-ashley-the-worst-football-club-owner-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 17:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/is-mike-ashley-the-worst-football-club-owner-ever/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not funny really, how messed up we are. I&amp;rsquo;m not one for shifting the blame and allow things to justify themselves but Mike Ashley&amp;rsquo;s tenure at Newcastle United is far from laughable. The hopes and expectations when he took over were pretty high, the couple of men who voiced their concerns over his takeover were looked on is if they had two heads. Eventually them two guys turned into a group but still, the moderate Toon supporter backed the billionaire owner who invested nearly £300m into their beloved NUFC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton more than likely staying as manager for West Brom game</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 13:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</guid>
      <description>It seems that the hierarchy have learned nowt over the last season and continue to play their own game, which is affecting all of us. Mike Ashley doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he&amp;rsquo;s doing sadly enough and his puppets aren&amp;rsquo;t much better. Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;m being a little too harsh on them, after all Ashley did invest a whole lot of money into Newcastle United with very little, no, return. You would have to feel a little sympathy for him in that sense but he made no steps whatsoever to make amends and sort the club and effectively brought the club to it&amp;rsquo;s knees, meaning here we are in the Coca Cola Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United fans still loyal as ever</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/newcastle-united-fans-still-loyal-as-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/newcastle-united-fans-still-loyal-as-ever/</guid>
      <description>Fans - Where else would you find such fans? We may have suffered the worst in relegation but it could be a mixed blessing for the Toon faithful. We no longer will be paying high earners for sitting on the benches and won&amp;rsquo;t going through managers as if they were skittles - right? We certainly hope things will change but so far the only thing good at the club, are the fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley reconsidering Newcastle United sale</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/14/mike-ashley-reconsidering-newcastle-united-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 15:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/14/mike-ashley-reconsidering-newcastle-united-sale/</guid>
      <description>The worst has really come , Mike Ashley is reportedly reconsidering his selling position (for the second time) and may well take Newcastle United off the for sale list. This comes as all parties interested in buying have expressed a concern at the finance books at Newcastle and indeed you&amp;rsquo;d expect that. There are so many financial problems at the club, now that we&amp;rsquo;re a Championship Club. Reports indicate that Ashley will remain as owner and Llambias as MD still, however a new Public Relations figure who we don&amp;rsquo;t know just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United horror story is nearing an end – finally</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/07/newcastle-united-horror-story-is-nearing-an-end-finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 12:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/07/newcastle-united-horror-story-is-nearing-an-end-finally/</guid>
      <description>Finally we&amp;rsquo;re nearly there , Mike Ashley is ready to sell Newcastle United and there are three very willing buyers from what we hear. Apparently there are two from Asia and one from America but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure, it&amp;rsquo;s one from Malaysia, one from Singapore and the other from America. The American interest could well be the man I reported on a couple of articles down, or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not. The identities are yet to be unveiled but we&amp;rsquo;re more worried about how long it&amp;rsquo;ll take.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>