<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graham Carr on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/graham-carr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graham Carr on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 15:54:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/graham-carr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Graham Carr in France scouting players as we speak</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/22/graham-carr-in-france-scouting-players-as-we-speak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 15:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/22/graham-carr-in-france-scouting-players-as-we-speak/</guid>
      <description>Debuchy - On a long list of players in France that NUFC are interested After already luring the likes of Ben Arfa, Cabaye, Marveaux and Mehdi Abeid from France, Graham Carr in already working on new transfer targets as the season draws to a close. In a recent interview, Alan Pardew confirmed that work was already under way for next season, as Newcastle United hope to build on what has been quite honestly, a phenomenal second season in the Premier League since our return from the Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graham Carr labels Mike Ashley &amp; Derek Llambias as “fantastic people to work for”</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/13/graham-carr-labels-mike-ashley-derek-llambias-as-fantastic-people-to-work-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 12:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/13/graham-carr-labels-mike-ashley-derek-llambias-as-fantastic-people-to-work-for/</guid>
      <description>Signings - Tioté and Yohan Cabaye signings advised by chief scout Graham Carr Despite the extraordinary outburst by Derek Llambias last night Graham Carr has only positive things to say about the two men that run this football club; Mike Ashley &amp;amp; Derek Llambias. Both are still seen as businessmen and their disregard for the supporters of this great football club is held against them, time and time again. They&amp;rsquo;ve made some ridiculous decisions in their time on Tyneside it has to be said but financially they&amp;rsquo;ve brought Newcastle Unite back on a sound footing and are hoping to break-even in the books this year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>