<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newcastle United Takeover on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/newcastle-united-takeover/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newcastle United Takeover on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 00:39:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/newcastle-united-takeover/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian plans £260m offer for Newcastle United when 2011/12 Premier League status is confirmed</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/13/wealthy-indian-plans-260m-offer-for-newcastle-united-when-201112-premier-league-status-is-confirmed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 00:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/13/wealthy-indian-plans-260m-offer-for-newcastle-united-when-201112-premier-league-status-is-confirmed/</guid>
      <description>Pull the other one one might say. However, news is news. According for the Sunday Mirror; Newcastle United could be owned by a wealthy Indian in the summer, should they confirm Premier League safety. A £260m figure is being touted as the price tag Anil Ambani is willing to offer Mike, but the real question is: would the smart-minded Englishman accept that bundle of notes? Again, take this with a rather large pinch of salt because I expect it to be utter tosh, per usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Americans have lead in takeover race</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/29/americans-have-lead-in-takeover-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 11:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/29/americans-have-lead-in-takeover-race/</guid>
      <description>Sitting here in an internet cafe in the Algarve, the weather is almost too hot for comfort, so, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to muster up an article or two. While I&amp;rsquo;ve been away it seems there&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of talk and not much action per usual, but the good news that greeted me today, was reports that the firesale had ended at Newcastle United, and that&amp;rsquo;s very good news, to say the least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another sportswear tycoon ready to take NUFC off Ashley’s hands</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/25/another-sportswea-tycoon-ready-to-take-nufc-off-ashleys-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 14:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/25/another-sportswea-tycoon-ready-to-take-nufc-off-ashleys-hands/</guid>
      <description>### Sheard - Supposedly watched the Palace game
Things are never dull at Newcastle, not for one minute. All of a sudden we&amp;rsquo;re being taken over, then we have a deadline set, and then the deadline delayed. The latest gust of news/rumours/(made up nonsense), is that Newcastle United have a new bidder. In the Chronicle in the last few minutes, Lee Ryder has posted up a ground breaking (well not really) story, that Geoff Sheard is making a bid for the Magpies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llambias – Barry Moat close to completing takeover</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/llambias-barry-moat-close-to-completing-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/llambias-barry-moat-close-to-completing-takeover/</guid>
      <description>We can&amp;rsquo;t fault the lads performances over the season so far, two wins and a draw, that draw being a dreaded away trip to the Hawthorns for any other Championship side. However Newcastle United are not any Championship side, only at Newcastle could we attract nearly 44,000 to a home game, mind you, it only being the third game of the season and the traveling Geordies weren&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. Another Ameobi goal and another three points, leaving Newcastle 3rd in the Coca Cola Championship league standings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The man leading ‘Fans 410’ bid for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/the-man-leading-fans-410-bid-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 14:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/the-man-leading-fans-410-bid-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>There has been a new spanner thrown into the works at Newcastle United now as yesterday, Sky Sports were told that Graham Roberts, a former footballer was heading a bid from a consortium called &amp;lsquo;Fans 410&amp;rsquo;, to buy Newcastle United. This news comes just as Barry Moat was close to sealing the club but now the former defender said that he has friends who want to own a football club and that the Magpies are the perfect opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley ready to accept defeat on Newcastle sale and stay on</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/mike-ashley-ready-to-accept-defeat-on-newcastle-sale-and-stay-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 14:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/mike-ashley-ready-to-accept-defeat-on-newcastle-sale-and-stay-on/</guid>
      <description>As I said in my previous article, the loan signing of Danny Simpson could have well indicated that Mike Ashley is staying as owner and breaking news from Sky Sports and their North Eastern reporter, David Craig indicate Ashley will take the club off the market in about a week if no one comes forward to offer an acceptable amount. What ever happened to Barry Moat and his deposit today or about them being in talks with more consortia that just Moat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye to a flipping legend</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/goodbye-to-a-flipping-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 21:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/goodbye-to-a-flipping-legend/</guid>
      <description>Martins - The goal that nearly kept us up It&amp;rsquo;s well and truly the end of an era when you see Obafemi Martins departing from St.James&amp;rsquo;. Although he had mixed receptions from supporters it was pretty clear he was loved upon Tyneside and will be sorely missed in our front line. Martins scored an abundance of goals in his first season after arriving for £10m and earned Alan Shearer&amp;rsquo;s much coveted #9 shirt for Newcastle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle miss out on another talented youngster</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/newcastle-miss-out-on-another-talented-youngster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 15:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/newcastle-miss-out-on-another-talented-youngster/</guid>
      <description>Although we know that there probably won&amp;rsquo;t be any new faces arriving this summer to Newcastle United it&amp;rsquo;s irritating to see where the players, that could be Newcastle players, go to different clubs. For example , Kyle Naughton went to Spurs, fair enough, we mighn&amp;rsquo;t have stood much of a chance there, but Daniel Fox went to Celtic, I think we could&amp;rsquo;ve snapped him. Jermaine Beckford has been taken off the transfer list although his agent stated he wanted to join Newcastle pretty much and Simon Cox going to Brom, although I&amp;rsquo;m sure he&amp;rsquo;d be tempted to join Newcastle if he was given the chance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profitable Group can’t provide any proof of funds</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/28/profitable-group-cant-provide-any-proof-of-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 10:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/28/profitable-group-cant-provide-any-proof-of-funds/</guid>
      <description>This doesn&amp;rsquo;t really come as much of a shock to us Newcastle fans, because we questioned their interest when it all started long ago. The Profitable Group who declared an interest in Newcastle, saying they wanted to expand the stadium to 60,000 , appoint Shearer and give him a nice transfer kitty, have &amp;lsquo;pulled&amp;rsquo; out of the race for the club. According to SSN the group couldn&amp;rsquo;t provide any proof of funds to Mike Ashley and co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Derek Llambias know what’s going on?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/27/does-derek-llambias-know-whats-going-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 13:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/27/does-derek-llambias-know-whats-going-on/</guid>
      <description>Llambias - What can believe from this guy? Another day passes and another day missed for Newcastle United. Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s game at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park for Sir Bobby Robson was a great scene and a very much deserved ovation for the legend that is Sir Bobby. England went on to win the game 3-2 courtesy of a Shearer penalty in which he earned the penalty too. Indeed any time Shearer did get the ball, it was met with a huge roar of excitement and Alan, was looking as sharp as ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton more than likely staying as manager for West Brom game</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 13:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</guid>
      <description>It seems that the hierarchy have learned nowt over the last season and continue to play their own game, which is affecting all of us. Mike Ashley doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he&amp;rsquo;s doing sadly enough and his puppets aren&amp;rsquo;t much better. Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;m being a little too harsh on them, after all Ashley did invest a whole lot of money into Newcastle United with very little, no, return. You would have to feel a little sympathy for him in that sense but he made no steps whatsoever to make amends and sort the club and effectively brought the club to it&amp;rsquo;s knees, meaning here we are in the Coca Cola Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United fans still loyal as ever</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/newcastle-united-fans-still-loyal-as-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/newcastle-united-fans-still-loyal-as-ever/</guid>
      <description>Fans - Where else would you find such fans? We may have suffered the worst in relegation but it could be a mixed blessing for the Toon faithful. We no longer will be paying high earners for sitting on the benches and won&amp;rsquo;t going through managers as if they were skittles - right? We certainly hope things will change but so far the only thing good at the club, are the fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United could start the season with the same 11 that finished it</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/21/newcastle-united-could-start-the-season-with-the-same-11-that-finished-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 11:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/21/newcastle-united-could-start-the-season-with-the-same-11-that-finished-it/</guid>
      <description>Still haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to move out any high earners With the start of the Championship not too far away it&amp;rsquo;s a frightening fact that Newcastle United could be fielding pretty much the same starting eleven that played on the final day in Villa Park, where we suffered relegation. Apart form Owen, Viduka, Edgar and Lovenkrands leaving there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been much other developments especially with the new transfer embargo put on Newcastle by &amp;lsquo;owner&amp;rsquo; Mike Ashley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McMahon not offering the full £100m for Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/20/mcmahon-not-offering-the-full-100m-for-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 14:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/20/mcmahon-not-offering-the-full-100m-for-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>Steve McMahon today has confirmed that the group he is leading, or supposedly, have not hit the asking price that Mike has wanted. Mr.Ashley put Newcastle up for sale at the price of £100m and he was quoted as saying, the first person to hit that figure would be the new owners of the club. However Derek Llambias has confirmed that &amp;lsquo;two or more&amp;rsquo; groups have et that asking price, so why hasn&amp;rsquo;t Mike accepted the first £100m bid like he said he would?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>