<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leon Best on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/leon-best/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leon Best on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 14:22:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/leon-best/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leon Best has adapted to the physicality of the Premier League brilliantly</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/01/leon-best-has-adapted-to-the-physicality-of-the-premier-league-brilliantly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 14:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/01/leon-best-has-adapted-to-the-physicality-of-the-premier-league-brilliantly/</guid>
      <description>Best - Has thrived since Andy Carroll&amp;rsquo;s departure to Liverpool in January When Andy Carroll made his shock deadline day move to Liverpool FC for a staggering initial fee of £35m - Newcastle United fans started to worry as to where our goals for the remainder of the Premier League campaign would come from. It might be easy to say now, but I never doubted our ability to score goals with or without the Newcastle born front-man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle cruise by Carlisle as Best &amp; Vuckic grab first goals for club</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/17/newcastle-cruise-by-carlisle-as-best-vuckic-grab-first-goals-for-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 21:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/17/newcastle-cruise-by-carlisle-as-best-vuckic-grab-first-goals-for-club/</guid>
      <description>Vuckic - Delighted after scoring his first goal for Newcastle United Newcastle kicked off their first preparation for the upcoming Premier League campaign by defeating Carlisle by three goals, with Leon Best, Haris Vuckic and Nile Ranger all hitting the back of the net. I&amp;rsquo;ve yet to see the goals but they were meant to be nice finishes from all three. Whilst seeing off The Cumbrians, the Toon lads sported the new Newcastle United away strip, and it&amp;rsquo;s a very nice jersey to say the least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leon Best is going nowhere – Give the lad a chance</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/05/05/leon-best-is-going-nowhere-give-the-lad-a-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 22:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/05/05/leon-best-is-going-nowhere-give-the-lad-a-chance/</guid>
      <description>Best - Hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a giving the sight of day at Newcastle United this season All I&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing of late is of who will be leaving Newcastle United this summer and throughout lists of many fans preferred &amp;lsquo;Ins and Outs&amp;rsquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed that Leon Best is close to the top of them. To be quite honest, I can&amp;rsquo;t understand why. This is the lad we bought on the final day in January from Coventry, who was their leading scorer at that stage and well up the scoring charts .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s only a matter of time before Leon Best starts scoring</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/15/its-only-a-matter-of-time-before-leon-best-starts-scoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 21:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/15/its-only-a-matter-of-time-before-leon-best-starts-scoring/</guid>
      <description>Best - Only needs his first goal for the club and more will follow A lot of people have doubted the talent of Leon Best in the last few weeks and are concerned that he might have been a poor signing from Chris Hughton. Leon arrived on Tyneside in a dream move (for him) on the last day of the transfer window in January of this year. The former Coventry striker had scored reached double figures in the league with Coventry up until his move but he is yet to bag his first goal for Newcastle United in what&amp;rsquo;s been a very successful Coca Cola Championship campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t judge Leon Best before he plays in a Newcastle United shirt</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/02/dont-judge-leon-best-before-he-plays-in-a-newcastle-united-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 20:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/02/dont-judge-leon-best-before-he-plays-in-a-newcastle-united-shirt/</guid>
      <description>Best - Some Toon fans concerned at the signing of Leon by Chris Hughton It seems if a lot of Newcastle United fans have already formed opinions on our new signing, Irish international Leon Best. Having watched Best on many occasions, although he&amp;rsquo;s no Alan Shearer he certainly has the potential as Hughton rightly said, to make a good striker. Signing from Coventry for a rumoured fee of 650k, Best was Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s deadline day signing , getting in a striker after missing our on Victor Moses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>