<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Krul on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/tim-krul/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tim Krul on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 17:51:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/tim-krul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle preparing for the departure of Tim Krul</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/24/newcastle-preparing-departure-tim-krul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 17:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/24/newcastle-preparing-departure-tim-krul/</guid>
      <description>Few Newcastle United fans will forget Tim Krul&amp;rsquo;s European debut against Palermo in the old UEFA Cup. A team which featured the likes of Alberto Luque and Antoine Sibierski travelled to Italy with the hope of pulling off a memorable result and they did exactly that, with Tim Krul the sole reason behind the famous victory. At just 17 years of age, Krul replaced an injured Steve Harper between the sticks and made a name for himself by contributing a handful of physic-defying saves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spurs bid £10m for Krul as Newcastle have £4m offer for Anita knocked back</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/06/12/spurs-bid-10m-for-krul-as-newcastle-have-4m-offer-for-anita-knocked-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 13:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/06/12/spurs-bid-10m-for-krul-as-newcastle-have-4m-offer-for-anita-knocked-back/</guid>
      <description>#### Anita - Highly rated by the Newcastle scouting team and likely to arrive
First off, there&amp;rsquo;s a couple of rumours going around that Tim Krul has been subject to a £10m bid from Harry Redknapp&amp;rsquo;s Tottenham Hotspurs. If this is the case, then I&amp;rsquo;m sure the NUFC hierarchy will only laugh off the bid and tell Harry that Timmy&amp;rsquo;s left hand isn&amp;rsquo;t for sale. £10m?! For one of the keepers of the season - in a side that finished just off the Champions League spots - ten million wouldn&amp;rsquo;t cover half the keepers fee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is the last time Newcastle United have had so many..</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/when-is-the-last-time-newcastle-united-have-had-so-many/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 21:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/when-is-the-last-time-newcastle-united-have-had-so-many/</guid>
      <description>Benny - Making the French squad a testament to his work since the horrid broken leg NUFC players heading to a major tournament? World Cup 2010, Jonas Gutierrez featured for Argentina, was there anyone else in South Africa on Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s books? Euro 2008? Can&amp;rsquo;t say I remember anyone representing NUFC at the tournament. This year however, Hatem Ben Arfa, Yohan Cabaye and Tim Krul look likely to go. For a European championship, that is a pretty impressive showing, and a testament to Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s fantastic season; especially when two of the three are part of a potential Euro 2012 winning team, in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would Tim Krul even consider joining Chelsea?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/17/would-tim-krul-even-consider-joining-chelsea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 13:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/17/would-tim-krul-even-consider-joining-chelsea/</guid>
      <description>Krul - One of the top performing keepers in the Premier League this season I&amp;rsquo;ll never forget the first time I saw Tim Krul in &amp;lsquo;real&amp;rsquo; action for the senior team - away to Palermo in what was then the UEFA Cup. We were leading 0-1 courtesy of Albert Luque in one of his few games for Newcastle United. The pressure began to increase and the shots started pouring in on the young Dutchman between the sticks, however, after a string of quality saves, NUFC held out for a valuable three points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Newcastle United really need anymore goalkeepers?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/10/do-newcastle-united-really-need-anymore-goalkeepers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 23:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/10/do-newcastle-united-really-need-anymore-goalkeepers/</guid>
      <description>There are reports emerging that Chris Hughton was in Scotland yesterday to watch John Ruddy play and keep tabs on the youngsters progress. The 23 year-old which is quite young for a keeper is on loan at Motherwell from Everton, with the hope he can finally over-take Time Howard between the sticks. If that&amp;rsquo;s hard enough, it&amp;rsquo;s a very long shot that he&amp;rsquo;ll outdo either the long-serving Steve Harper or indeed Time Krul and that&amp;rsquo;s before I even mention Fraser Forster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A good point and a good performance</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/08/a-good-point-and-a-good-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 21:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/08/a-good-point-and-a-good-performance/</guid>
      <description>### Krul - Some great saves today
A pretty good performance all round had Newcastle fans cheering throughout the 90 minutes at the Hawthorns today. In a game which is the start of a relentless Championship campaign, Newcastle United showed , in patches that they could well come to terms with the Championship, sooner rather than later. Holding a minutes applause for the late, Great Sir Bobby Robson, teams got under way and Newcastle to say the least, were looking the most dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>