<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ryan Taylor on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/ryan-taylor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ryan Taylor on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:30:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/ryan-taylor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Chris Hughton not rate Ryan Taylor at all?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/20/does-chris-hughton-not-rate-ryan-taylor-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/20/does-chris-hughton-not-rate-ryan-taylor-at-all/</guid>
      <description>### Taylor - Hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen a whole lot of playing time on Tyneside this season
A great win yesterday and a very successful season to say the least. Thank you Chris Hughton, thank you supporters and indeed our thanks to the players. That aside, there&amp;rsquo;s been something in the back of my mind all the time and I have to bring it up. Ryan Taylor arrived from Wigan Athletic over a season ago, in the January transfer window alongside Kevin Nolan and came here with high hopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argentine returns as Taylor is out</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/29/argentine-returns-as-taylor-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 15:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/29/argentine-returns-as-taylor-is-out/</guid>
      <description>### Ryan - Has settled well on Tyneside
You could nearly say that he&amp;rsquo;s been one our players of the season so far. Chipping in with a couple of goals too, and no ordinary goals mind you. Ryan Taylor&amp;rsquo;s latest was against Ipswich when he caught the keeper in an awkward position and caressed it into the top corner, and not a fluke as some may have suggested. He also hit the target with a stunning strike, with his left this time, into the other top corner, in a two nil win against Crystal Palace earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Taylor willing to fill Habib Beye’s role</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/25/ryan-taylor-willing-to-fill-habib-beyes-role/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/25/ryan-taylor-willing-to-fill-habib-beyes-role/</guid>
      <description>Taylor - Hoping to improve on last season Ryan Taylor today reiterated his desire to remain at Newcastle by saying he wants to fill the departing Habib Beye&amp;rsquo;s role at right back. Taylor, who arrive din January in a deal which saw Charles N&amp;rsquo;Zogbia go the other way, never got going in his first season and didn&amp;rsquo;t settle too well. Today he revealed that that the behind the scene&amp;rsquo;s going on&amp;rsquo;s effected everyone&amp;rsquo;s performances and training was far from a normal teams run out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>