<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastien Bassong on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/sebastien-bassong/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sebastien Bassong on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 15:00:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/sebastien-bassong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bassong finally on his way out of troubled Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/06/bassong-finally-on-his-way-out-of-troubled-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/06/bassong-finally-on-his-way-out-of-troubled-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>After a long time of asking and constant speculation, last seasons best player is extremely close to signing for Harry Redknapp&amp;rsquo;s Spurs side. Following Darren Bent&amp;rsquo;s departure to Sunderland for £10m it&amp;rsquo;s believed that Redknapp will be using that money on Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s prized asset, Sebastien Bassong. Bassong who signed for a mere £500,000k has proved himself in English football in his first season, shining out in a lacklustre Newcastle United side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebastien Bassong trying his utmost to leave stranded NUFC</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/04/sebastien-bassong-trying-his-utmost-to-leave-stranded-nufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 13:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/04/sebastien-bassong-trying-his-utmost-to-leave-stranded-nufc/</guid>
      <description>As the rumours get the hopes up on Tyneside we are let down again , this time the Chronicle are claiming that the club will more than likely be under the control of Mike Ashley. We&amp;rsquo;ve had Malaysians, Singaporeans , Americans, Irish, Chinese, Dubai, Iranians, Nigerians, Englishmen and Sunderland fans hoaxes throughout our takeover journey. We hoped that after relegation things would&amp;rsquo;ve picked up and maybe with Shearer appointed as manager and new owners we could just make the play-offs but now, there&amp;rsquo;s not much chance of this happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle reject £10m bid for Bassong</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/02/newcastle-reject-10m-bid-for-bassong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2009 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/02/newcastle-reject-10m-bid-for-bassong/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s understood, amidst all the takeover speculation and Shearer saga that Newcastle United, have rejected a £10m from Tottenham for Sebastien Bassong. Sky Sports are now reporting this story and if true which we believe it is, £10m is a lot to reject for someone we only paid £500k for last summer. Harry Redknapp is no doubt interested as are Arsenal, and Arsene Wenger has a good lot of cash now that Kolo Touré and Emanuel Adebayor have departed to cash filthy Manchester City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tottenham Hotspurs lead Sebastien Bassong chase</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/06/25/tottenham-hotspurs-lead-sebastien-bassong-chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/06/25/tottenham-hotspurs-lead-sebastien-bassong-chase/</guid>
      <description>News has broke today that Sebastien Bassong, Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s best player last season by far is on the verge of joining Tottenham. Well no really but apparently Spurs are leading the chase to sign the Cameroonian international. We expected high demand for this player and we would be surprised if Arsenal didn&amp;rsquo;t come in and make a suitable offer. Indeed we know Seb wants to leave but how much will he go for is another thing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>