<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sir Bobby Robson on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/sir-bobby-robson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sir Bobby Robson on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 22:57:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/sir-bobby-robson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tyneside blast from the past</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/24/a-tyneside-blast-from-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 22:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/24/a-tyneside-blast-from-the-past/</guid>
      <description>Sir Bobby Robson - Who&amp;rsquo;ll ever forget his years in charge of Newcastle United? The years during Sir Bobby Robson&amp;rsquo;s tenure at Newcastle were perhaps the best days of the football club so far. A real gentleman in charge, that sent out a team capable of beating anyone. We were able to defeat anyone in those glorious years, years that saw us in the Champions League, in with big names such as Inter Milan, Juventus, Barcelona , so on and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“The first ninety minutes of a football match are the most important.”</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/26/the-first-ninety-minutes-of-a-football-match-are-the-most-important-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 13:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/26/the-first-ninety-minutes-of-a-football-match-are-the-most-important-/</guid>
      <description>Indeed it&amp;rsquo;s very true that the first 90 minutes of any football game are the most important, and that will be the case at Portman Road come half five too. This will be the first time in some time that we&amp;rsquo;ve visited Ipswich Town, one of Bobby Robson&amp;rsquo;s many homes. Hopefully we can do Sir Bobby proud and grab all three points but Roy Keane&amp;rsquo;s team will also be hoping to clinch a long awaited win for the Tractor Boys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passionate Peterborough performance for Sir Bobby</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/22/passionate-peterborough-performance-for-sir-bobby/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/22/passionate-peterborough-performance-for-sir-bobby/</guid>
      <description>Sir Bobby - An emotional ceremony in Durham Cathedral An emotional ceremony in Durham Cathedral some of the greats of English and European football pay their never ending respects to the late Sir Bobby Robson. In a gathering, in the fine Durham cathedral saw the Newcastle first team, alongside Chris Hughon, Alan Shearer, Paul Gascoigne, Peter Beardsley, Gary Lineker, and Fabio Capello all attend. It was an emotional event for Gazza who was reduced to tears but most people within the sacred grounds couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but feel they had a lost a great great man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A win for Sir Bobby</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/08/a-win-for-sir-bobby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 13:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/08/a-win-for-sir-bobby/</guid>
      <description>Players - Will dedicate 3 points to Bobby if they win When Newcastle players grace the pitch today at half five, there will be a moment of silence for the great Sir Bobby Robson. Passing away at 76, the whole world mourned his death. As George Caulkin rightly said, it brought the North East of England together. Seeing Newcastle United jerseys everywhere with a few patches of red and white, signaling the Sunderland respect it showed, as much as there was rivalry between the two sides, there is a very thin line between it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle wave goodbye to a true legend</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/31/newcastle-wave-goodbye-to-a-true-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 12:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/31/newcastle-wave-goodbye-to-a-true-legend/</guid>
      <description>Your usual takeover talks goes out the window when you hear something like this. You are stopped in your tracks. When I heard Bobby Robson had died today, it shocked me although I can&amp;rsquo;t say I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect it. Sir Bobby, has been battling cancer for the fifth time and eventually, the horrible cause got the better of a true legend. No fan in England won&amp;rsquo;t know that famous name that is Sir Bobby Robson and no one will have a bad word to say about him, simply because he was a gentle, caring man who had football running through his veins</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>