<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hatem Ben Arfa on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/hatem-ben-arfa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hatem Ben Arfa on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:07:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/hatem-ben-arfa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens to Hatem Ben Arfa after transfer window?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/08/21/happens-hatem-ben-arfa-transfer-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/08/21/happens-hatem-ben-arfa-transfer-window/</guid>
      <description>Hatem Ben Arfa - where to start? The Frenchman is without doubt one of the most exciting players I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen in Black and White. The sense of excitement when he received the ball on either flank and looked to drive at defenders. His ability to spot a pass, or indeed use his yard of pace to burst clear of a couple of challenges and leave his markers for dead. Those were the good days under Hatem Ben Arfa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is the last time Newcastle United have had so many..</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/when-is-the-last-time-newcastle-united-have-had-so-many/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 21:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/when-is-the-last-time-newcastle-united-have-had-so-many/</guid>
      <description>Benny - Making the French squad a testament to his work since the horrid broken leg NUFC players heading to a major tournament? World Cup 2010, Jonas Gutierrez featured for Argentina, was there anyone else in South Africa on Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s books? Euro 2008? Can&amp;rsquo;t say I remember anyone representing NUFC at the tournament. This year however, Hatem Ben Arfa, Yohan Cabaye and Tim Krul look likely to go. For a European championship, that is a pretty impressive showing, and a testament to Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s fantastic season; especially when two of the three are part of a potential Euro 2012 winning team, in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best £5m Newcastle United have spent in the last decade</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/30/the-best-5m-newcastle-united-have-spent-in-the-last-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 21:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/30/the-best-5m-newcastle-united-have-spent-in-the-last-decade/</guid>
      <description>Ben Arfa - Starting to show his raw potential in a Newcastle United shirt I think it is fair to say that Hatem Ben Arfa played his best ever 75 minutes in a Newcastle United shirt last Sunday against West Brom. His touch, pace, movement and vision crafted two goals for Papiss Cissé, before taking time out to score a beautiful effort himself. He didn&amp;rsquo;t put a foot wrong all game long and ran riot any time he got the ball to his feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatem Ben Arfa has the potential to rip apart the Premier League</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/06/hatem-ben-arfa-has-the-potential-to-rip-apart-the-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 13:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/06/hatem-ben-arfa-has-the-potential-to-rip-apart-the-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>Ben Arfa - Has raw potential that needs harnessing by Alan Pardew &amp;amp; NUFC I think it is fair to say that when Hatem Ben Arfa came on for Newcastle United against Sunderland on Sunday; the Geordie faithful felt he had the potential to rescue what was an impending disaster. We weren&amp;rsquo;t wrong. The Frenchman gave Kieran Richardson one of the hardest times he&amp;rsquo;ll get all season from anyone on the wing - tearing him to pieces over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United must attack Norwich City from the start tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/09/newcastle-united-must-attack-norwich-city-from-the-start-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 17:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/09/newcastle-united-must-attack-norwich-city-from-the-start-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Ben Arfa - His creativity and pace crucial for NUFC tomorrow at Carrow Road Norwich City will most definitely fancy their chances of gaining all three points in tomorrows battle at Carrow Road and rightly so. We&amp;rsquo;re without Cheik Tioté, Danny Guthrie, Steven Taylor, Mike Williamson and more than likely Fabricio Coloccini as well. Four big losses in that injury list, indeed four members that probably would have started tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United close to signing Ben Arfa – An early Christmas present?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/23/newcastle-united-close-to-signing-ben-arfa-an-early-christmas-present/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 16:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/23/newcastle-united-close-to-signing-ben-arfa-an-early-christmas-present/</guid>
      <description>#### Ben Arfa - Wants to play for Newcastle United and is looking for permanent deal
We may well be in for an early Christmas present with the new that Hatem Ben Arfa, could be quite close to a permanent deal at Newcastle United. The French winger who joined this summer thanks to Chris Hughton, played less than five games, in which he scored a stunner against Everton at Goodison Park, in an excellent away win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatem Ben Arfa can give us a glimse of his potential tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/10/hatem-ben-arfa-can-give-us-a-glimse-of-his-potential-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 20:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/10/hatem-ben-arfa-can-give-us-a-glimse-of-his-potential-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>After weeks of haggling, and negotiations, Newcastle United finally managed to bring Hatem Ben Arfa to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park and indeed tomorrow the Frenchman will make his début for the Toon. At home to Blackpool, the scene is set for Ben Arfa to do the business alongside his teammate Cheick Tioté who also joined from Dutch side FC Twente. We can&amp;rsquo;t really expect goals upon goals from either, but hopefully tomorrow, we&amp;rsquo;ll get a glimpse of what they can both do, and Ben Arfa in particular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Window Closed – Hughton gets the job done for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>St.James&amp;rsquo; - Will be graced by Hatem Ben Arfa &amp;amp; Cheick Tioté against Blackpool Five players signed, and a job well done by Chris Hughton and co. James Perch, Dan Gosling, Sol Campbell, Cheick Tioté &amp;amp; Hatem Ben Arfa all signed for Newcastle United,a nd four of those on a permanent basis. The pick of the bunch really is a coin toss between Dan Gosling and Hatem Ben Arfa, but the fact Ben Arfa is fit and ready to go unlike his counterpart, perhaps shades it for the Frenchman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Arfa will join Newcastle United – Says Jean Claude Dassier</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/26/ben-arfa-will-join-newcastle-united-says-jean-claude-dassier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/26/ben-arfa-will-join-newcastle-united-says-jean-claude-dassier/</guid>
      <description>Ben Arfa - Will fly to Newcastle United to complete the loan move One thing&amp;rsquo;s for sure - Jean Claude Dassier likes talking and talk he will. According to GOAL.com, who can often be well off the mark on transfer stories, Ben Arfa will finally complete his long forlorn move to Newcastle United in the next couple of days. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re only telling you what&amp;rsquo;s in the news, but I&amp;rsquo;d be fairly sure that the Frenchman will indeed make the trip to St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatem Ben Arfa arrives in Newcastle Airport – Set to sign?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/13/hatem-ben-arfa-arrives-in-newcastle-airport-set-to-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 19:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/13/hatem-ben-arfa-arrives-in-newcastle-airport-set-to-sign/</guid>
      <description>Hatem Ben Arfa - Spotted in Newcastle Airport - signing soon? Well the situation goes on! Even after Marseille president claiming Ben Arfa would be staying in France with L&amp;rsquo;OM, and even after Hughton admitted he didn&amp;rsquo;t know where the rumours of this supposed capture were coming from - Hatem Ben Arfa has been spotted in Newcastle Airport. Whether this is true, or just unbelievable Photoshoppin&amp;rsquo;, either way there&amp;rsquo;s questions still to be answered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Arfa waves goodbye to Marseille and sets sights on Premier League</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/09/ben-arfa-waves-goodbye-to-marseille-and-sets-sights-on-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/09/ben-arfa-waves-goodbye-to-marseille-and-sets-sights-on-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>Reports in the Shields Gazette are suggesting that French winger Hatem Ben Arfa who has been strongly linked with a move to Newcastle United - has waved goodbye to his fans at Marseille and his sights are now set on trying the Premier League. Ben Arfa who a couple of days ago came off the bench for Marseille assisted their only goal of the game with a delightful chip beyond Caen&amp;rsquo;s centre-backs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>