<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Hughton on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/chris-hughton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chris Hughton on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 22:39:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/chris-hughton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>To all Newcastle United fans – Happy Christmas from Tyne Time</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/24/to-all-newcastle-united-fans-happy-christmas-from-tyne-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 22:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/24/to-all-newcastle-united-fans-happy-christmas-from-tyne-time/</guid>
      <description>NUFC - Has been a hectic year for Newcastle United as club but enjoy Xmas! It really has been a frantic year as a Newcastle United supporter. From January till May, we were crowned Coca Cola Championship champions with a record number of points, and back in the Premier League after a little while away. We had made great improvements since the bad years upon Tyneside, with stability under Chris Hughton, and a great team spirit amongst the lads in the dressing -room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United 3-1 Liverpool – A Tribute to Chris Hughton</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/11/newcastle-united-3-1-liverpool-a-tribute-to-chris-hughton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 23:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/11/newcastle-united-3-1-liverpool-a-tribute-to-chris-hughton/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Scored a peach of a goal today in a very good win dedicated to Chris First things first - what a brave man Mike Ashley is showing up to Newcastle United v Liverpool today. I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to see his unsightly figure in the luxurious stands of St.James&amp;rsquo; Park during Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s first game in charge. However, I expect it was exactly that that lured the owner to the game, to oversee his new signing, and to decide whether he needed the sack just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley proves yet again what an incompetent, clueless owner he really is</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/07/mike-ashley-proves-yet-again-what-an-incompetent-clueless-owner-he-really-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 20:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/07/mike-ashley-proves-yet-again-what-an-incompetent-clueless-owner-he-really-is/</guid>
      <description>I heard at about 1.10pm roughly from a source at the club that Chris Hughton was on his way out of St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. It was shocking news to receive, especially for me when I was stuck on a three hour long bus journey. However, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure whether it was confirmed or not. At 2pm that day (yesterday) Newcastle United confirmed that Chris Hughton had been sacked as manager of Newcastle United and the search for a replacement had already begun, with Peter Beardsley taking charge of the Liverpool game forthcoming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacking Chris Hughton would be the worst decision made by NUFC since Sir Bobby’s dismissal</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/06/sacking-chris-hughton-worst-decision-nufc-since-sir-bobbys-dismissal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 12:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/06/sacking-chris-hughton-worst-decision-nufc-since-sir-bobbys-dismissal/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - William Hill have suspended betting on his dismissal this afternoon First things first - surely this cannot be right? Chris Hughton, the man who brought Newcastle United from the Championship back up to the Premier League with a record number of points, was responsible for the 5-1 thrashing of our rivals this season, our fantastic display against Chelsea in the Cup with a 4-3 win at Stamford Bridge, and the man who guided NUFC to a precious 1-0 away win at the Emirates to Arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor close to signing long-term Newcastle United deal</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/02/steven-taylor-close-to-signing-long-term-newcastle-united-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/02/steven-taylor-close-to-signing-long-term-newcastle-united-deal/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people seem to have lost faith and perhaps respect for Steven Taylor over the last few months, with the debacle over where his future lay very much up in the air. We read reports of Steven wanting close to £60,000 a week if he was to sign a new deal, and this outraged some Newcastle supporters, rightly so. However, his agent, and the controversial one at that, came out and dismissed any idea of Taylor wanting those outstanding wages, and said he just wanted to play for the club he loves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton responsible for Andy Carroll’s inclusion in England squad</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/15/chris-hughton-responsible-for-andy-carrolls-inclusion-in-england-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 21:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/15/chris-hughton-responsible-for-andy-carrolls-inclusion-in-england-squad/</guid>
      <description>7 goals so far this season, including the memorable one against Arsenal at the Emirates to secure a truly inspirational win. Called up by Fabio Capello at the age of 21 to represent his country, it really doesn&amp;rsquo;t get much better for the Geordie lad. It&amp;rsquo;s not the fact he&amp;rsquo;s one of our own that makes us so happy with him, it&amp;rsquo;s the type of striker he is. A nuisance for defenders, a great header of the ball, an old fashioned CF to put it to you straight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too much being made of Barton punch on Gamst Pedersen</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/11/too-much-being-made-of-barton-punch-on-gamst-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 19:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/11/too-much-being-made-of-barton-punch-on-gamst-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>Barton - Made his feelings known to Morten Gamst Pedersen foolishly last night Well some say it was a matter of time. Joey Barton has hit the headlines again, not for his great performances of late which includes 3 assists in the last 4 games, but for another reason. As the many various papers and online journals have pointed out, Joey Barton struck Morten Gamst Pedersen in the stomach with a right handed clout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Chris Hughton isn’t offered a nice new contract by Newcastle, there’ll be war</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/09/if-chris-hughton-isnt-offered-a-nice-new-contract-by-newcastle-therell-be-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/09/if-chris-hughton-isnt-offered-a-nice-new-contract-by-newcastle-therell-be-war/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Has done a fantastic job since taking over a sinking ship What can we say about this man? Bringing a relegated club back up to the Premier League straight away, with a record number of points, buying for pennies, some seriously talented footballers, going to Stamford Bridge in the Cup and scoring 4 goals, including an injury time winner in one of the most memorable cup games of the decade, giving us a 5-1 thrashing of our bitter rivals Sunderland to celebrate about, and on Sunday last, bringing us to the Emirates Stadium where we beat Arsenal 0-1 thanks to an Andy Carroll header, courtesy of a much practiced tactic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carroll &amp; Nolan binge after the Sunderland victory, where do the media get off?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/07/carroll-nolan-binge-after-the-sunderland-victory-where-do-the-media-get-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 13:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/07/carroll-nolan-binge-after-the-sunderland-victory-where-do-the-media-get-off/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Staying in Nolan&amp;rsquo;s house since his courting hearing a few weeks ago Well my latest article has been a long time coming and I apologise for that, however, I was intending on writing an article before the Tyne Wear derby about why on earth there was rumours of Chris Hughton being sacked, but when they won 5-1 it would&amp;rsquo;ve look a little suspect. Observing all the latest news about Newcastle in the latest few weeks has led me to inevitably write this article, quite frankly because I can&amp;rsquo; believe what I&amp;rsquo;m seeing day in day out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigel de Jong’s inability to tackle has left Newcastle United without much needed flair</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/10/06/nigel-de-jongs-inability-to-tackle-has-left-newcastle-united-without-much-needed-flair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 11:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/10/06/nigel-de-jongs-inability-to-tackle-has-left-newcastle-united-without-much-needed-flair/</guid>
      <description>Ben Arfa - Brave fella who wants to play in a Black and White jersey again Three minutes in, Newcastle United with possession and looking threatening. The ball is on our right wing, and Ben Arfa picks it up. He dribbles inward showing a tad of pace before Nigel de Jong slides in to dispossess him. All seems fine, but the Frenchman is on the floor, and not looking very well at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s just have a look at Newcastle United right now</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/28/lets-just-have-a-look-at-newcastle-united-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 15:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/28/lets-just-have-a-look-at-newcastle-united-right-now/</guid>
      <description>### Hughton - Delighted to be manager of Newcastle United FC
This day one year ago, we were preparing for the home visit of QPR at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park, and indeed looking to grab top spot of what when then called the Coca Cola Championship. We went on to draw that game 1-1, Marlon Harewood scoring his début goal for the club, after Ben Watson had put Queens Park Rangers in line for a win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United are heading to a good place at the right time</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/18/newcastle-united-are-heading-to-a-good-place-at-the-right-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 12:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/18/newcastle-united-are-heading-to-a-good-place-at-the-right-time/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Could manage all three points today if he plays his cards right It&amp;rsquo;s funny to see the media already dishing Newcastle after a &amp;lsquo;shocking&amp;rsquo; loss to Blackpool last weekend. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t anything shocking about it really, apart from the fact Blackpool had a great keeper on the day, and two guys who could finish their chances. So far we&amp;rsquo;ve two losses, a draw and a win. For a newly promoted side, having to play Manchester United, Aston Villa , Wolves and Blackpool, that&amp;rsquo;s not a bad showing at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United eye Nacim Boukhelifa &amp; Oriol Romeu signings</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/06/newcastle-united-eye-nacim-boukhelifa-oriol-romeu-signings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2010 18:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/06/newcastle-united-eye-nacim-boukhelifa-oriol-romeu-signings/</guid>
      <description>Romeu - Being looked at by Chris alongside Nacim Boukhelifa I know the transfer window is well and truly closed until January but Chris Hughton and his background staff are already looking at targets for when the action starts again in the New Year. In the last couple of days, Oriol Romeu and Nacim Boukhelifa have been linked with the club and according to reports, these two players have very bright futures indeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Window Closed – Hughton gets the job done for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>St.James&amp;rsquo; - Will be graced by Hatem Ben Arfa &amp;amp; Cheick Tioté against Blackpool Five players signed, and a job well done by Chris Hughton and co. James Perch, Dan Gosling, Sol Campbell, Cheick Tioté &amp;amp; Hatem Ben Arfa all signed for Newcastle United,a nd four of those on a permanent basis. The pick of the bunch really is a coin toss between Dan Gosling and Hatem Ben Arfa, but the fact Ben Arfa is fit and ready to go unlike his counterpart, perhaps shades it for the Frenchman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ricky van Wolfswinkel linked with Newcastle United last minute switch</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/29/ricky-van-wolfswinkel-linked-with-newcastle-united-last-minute-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/29/ricky-van-wolfswinkel-linked-with-newcastle-united-last-minute-switch/</guid>
      <description>What a name, what a name. Ricky van Wolfswinkel has today been linked with a move to Newcastle United just before the window slams shut for this summer. The Daily Mail have an article about it, but there&amp;rsquo;s discussion in volumes throughout Dutch forums about his proposed move to Newcastle and it seems as if the Utrecht fans expect him to leave for St.James&amp;rsquo; in the next day or so. The only time I&amp;rsquo;ve seen this guy play is when he destroyed Celtic with a hat-trick and I was very impressed by his finishing and overall play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Newcastle United really be looking to sign Robbie Keane?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/27/should-newcastle-united-really-be-looking-to-sign-robbie-keane/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 21:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/27/should-newcastle-united-really-be-looking-to-sign-robbie-keane/</guid>
      <description>Keane - Can you see him playing his football at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park this season? Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I&amp;rsquo;m all for it and think Robbie Keane would be a very addition to the Newcastle United squad. However, what I want to know - is whether you, the Geordie fans think that the Irishman would be a good signing by Chris Hughton and his team? I mean, Keane is 30 years of age and arguably past his peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor placed on transfer list by Newcastle United hierarchy</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/25/steven-taylor-placed-on-transfer-list-by-newcastle-united-hierarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/25/steven-taylor-placed-on-transfer-list-by-newcastle-united-hierarchy/</guid>
      <description>Taylor - Newcastle United have reportedly transfer listed the defender Sky Sports News have broken quite a stunning story about Steven Taylor today, indeed claiming that Newcastle United have placed him on the transfer list. Taylor, who has had trouble with contract talks for quite a while now has supposedly gone a step too far in negotiations and with his demands, and now finds himself on the &amp;lsquo;For Sale&amp;rsquo; list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United have £5m offer for Mevlut Erding rejected</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/10/newcastle-united-have-5m-offer-for-mevlut-erding-rejected/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 12:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/10/newcastle-united-have-5m-offer-for-mevlut-erding-rejected/</guid>
      <description>Erding - Newcastle have had a £5m bid for the Frenchman rejected today We&amp;rsquo;ve been linked with Erding before, and today it&amp;rsquo;s being reported in France Football that we&amp;rsquo;ve had a €6m offer for the striker rejected by PSG. It seems as if Chris Hughton is keen to sign Erding, because if all reports are accurate, this is the second bid that has been rejected for his services. I can&amp;rsquo;t say I know a lot about the forward, but Arsenal were interested not very long ago so he&amp;rsquo;s obviously decent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Arfa waves goodbye to Marseille and sets sights on Premier League</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/09/ben-arfa-waves-goodbye-to-marseille-and-sets-sights-on-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/09/ben-arfa-waves-goodbye-to-marseille-and-sets-sights-on-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>Reports in the Shields Gazette are suggesting that French winger Hatem Ben Arfa who has been strongly linked with a move to Newcastle United - has waved goodbye to his fans at Marseille and his sights are now set on trying the Premier League. Ben Arfa who a couple of days ago came off the bench for Marseille assisted their only goal of the game with a delightful chip beyond Caen&amp;rsquo;s centre-backs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United signing Hatem Ben Arfa would be huge</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/08/newcastle-united-signing-hatem-ben-arfa-would-be-huge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 16:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/08/newcastle-united-signing-hatem-ben-arfa-would-be-huge/</guid>
      <description>Ben Arfa - Could add so much to Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s midfield this season We all know, or should do that Hatem Ben Arfa hasn&amp;rsquo;t been outstanding at Marseille since he moved there and his attitude has been a major stumbling block for both the club and himself. In the last week or so, we&amp;rsquo;ve been strenuously linked with the Frenchman, and even with my sheer disgust of French footballers of the modern setup, I would sincerely love to see the Tunisian born Ben Arfa wear Black and White this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United have cash offer for Ben Arfa rejected but talks continue</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/03/newcastle-united-have-cash-offer-for-ben-arfa-rejected-but-talks-continue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2010 14:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/03/newcastle-united-have-cash-offer-for-ben-arfa-rejected-but-talks-continue/</guid>
      <description>Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s interest in Hatem Ben Arfa has been well reported in the media in the last week or so, and today it&amp;rsquo;s said that we&amp;rsquo;ve had an initial bid rejected for the Frenchman from Marseille. The left-winger has found himself on the wrong side of his manager and the club are looking to let the lad go, on loan or perhaps for a fee. The French paper &amp;lsquo;La Provence&amp;rsquo; has reported today that a bid from Newcastle United has indeed been rejected, but the French side have offered him again to Newcastle, for a bit more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Gosling on a free – Something Dennis Wise wouldn’t have managed</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/23/dan-gosling-on-a-free-something-dennis-wise-wouldnt-have-managed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 14:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/23/dan-gosling-on-a-free-something-dennis-wise-wouldnt-have-managed/</guid>
      <description>The dislike of Dennis Wise for many Newcastle United fans stems from Kevin Keegan&amp;rsquo;s departure, James Milner&amp;rsquo;s move to Aston Villa, the signing of the Uruguayan Gonzalez, Xisco&amp;rsquo;s arrival on Tyneside and many other incidents at the club. He did spot Bassong and a few other promising young players but will never be warmly welcomed back to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park if he arrives some time in the future. we passed down the chance to sign Bastian Schweinsteiger who reportedly was keen for a switch to Newcastle United, Wise again having something to do with this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle cruise by Carlisle as Best &amp; Vuckic grab first goals for club</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/17/newcastle-cruise-by-carlisle-as-best-vuckic-grab-first-goals-for-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 21:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/17/newcastle-cruise-by-carlisle-as-best-vuckic-grab-first-goals-for-club/</guid>
      <description>Vuckic - Delighted after scoring his first goal for Newcastle United Newcastle kicked off their first preparation for the upcoming Premier League campaign by defeating Carlisle by three goals, with Leon Best, Haris Vuckic and Nile Ranger all hitting the back of the net. I&amp;rsquo;ve yet to see the goals but they were meant to be nice finishes from all three. Whilst seeing off The Cumbrians, the Toon lads sported the new Newcastle United away strip, and it&amp;rsquo;s a very nice jersey to say the least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United submit £5m bid for Anthony Annan?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/15/newcastle-united-submit-5m-bid-for-anthony-annan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 21:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/15/newcastle-united-submit-5m-bid-for-anthony-annan/</guid>
      <description>Annan - Hughton has reportedly submitted a £5m bid for the Ghanaian After browsing through Sky Sports transfer clock-watch, I stumbled upon a new enough update claiming that Newcastle United had bid £5m for Anthony Annan. The Ghanaian, who had a very good World Cup with the Africans is very much sought after, and whether this report has any accuracy or not remains to be seen. However, only a couple of days ago, Annan admitted that he would love to play in the Premier League, but only after reported interest from Chelsea and Manchester United.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Gosling to sign for the Toon soon?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/13/dan-gosling-to-sign-for-the-toon-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 22:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/13/dan-gosling-to-sign-for-the-toon-soon/</guid>
      <description>Gosling - Newcastle await an Evertonian appeal about the players exit We feared the worst when we were told that very little, if no money would be spent on Tyneside this summer to boost the Coca Cola Championship winning squad. However, nearly a fortnight into the transfer window, we&amp;rsquo;ve one player already signed for a rumoured fee of £1.5 - 2m and another promising youngster by the name of Dan Gosling seemingly set to wear the Black and White jersey of Newcastle United this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carroll commits to Newcastle leaving Stoke stumped</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/04/carroll-commits-to-newcastle-leaving-stoke-stumped/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 21:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/04/carroll-commits-to-newcastle-leaving-stoke-stumped/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Committed to Newcastle United and our Premier League survival bid Well we know Stoke were interested and who could blame them. A strong, tall old fashioned centre-forward at only 20 years of age and with a newly promoted team. In fact, he would have been the perfect player for Stoke City, and the &amp;lsquo;football&amp;rsquo; they play. With James Beattie looking like he may well leave The Britannia, Carroll would&amp;rsquo;ve been the ideal replacement but the Geordie lad is committed to his home-town club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United looking to recruit Dan Gosling</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/03/newcastle-united-looking-to-recruit-dan-gosling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 16:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/03/newcastle-united-looking-to-recruit-dan-gosling/</guid>
      <description>News from Sky Sports claim that Newcastle United are becoming extremely interested in Everton&amp;rsquo;s Dan Gosling and may well swoop for the 20 year-old. Gosling, who has been in a tangle with new contract negotiations may well leave this club this summer and Chris Hughton seems keen to recruit the 2009 FA Cup 4th Round hero. I must say, I&amp;rsquo;d be really pleased with Gosling at Newcastle if we could manage it but we do have a of midfield players at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle tracking French starlet Mevlüt Erdinç?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/30/newcastle-tracking-french-starlet-mevlut-erdinc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 18:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/30/newcastle-tracking-french-starlet-mevlut-erdinc/</guid>
      <description>Erdinç - €6m bid reportedly rejected for the Frenchman in the last day or so There are two questions here that need answering for many Newcastle United fans and they are as follows. Is this guys real name Mevlüt Erdinç or Melvut Erding? Who is he? and finally, do Newcastle United &amp;amp; Chris Hughton actually have some money to spend this summer? I can personally say that I don&amp;rsquo;t know a lot about Erdinç and I can&amp;rsquo;t say I&amp;rsquo;m an amid follower of Ligue 1 in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giovani dos Santos would be an excellent acquisition for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/29/giovani-dos-santos-would-be-an-excellent-acquisition-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 22:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/29/giovani-dos-santos-would-be-an-excellent-acquisition-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>dos Santos - Would be a great signing for Chris Hughton &amp;amp; Newcastle United Watching the World Cup so far, I&amp;rsquo;ve mainly been impressed by two teams, and one of them was not England. Argentina and Mexico have both had a real go at the competition and it&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate that the Mexicans had to meet Maradona&amp;rsquo;s side in the first knock-out round of the competition. A very offside goal from Carlos Tevez knocked spirits in Javier Aguirre&amp;rsquo;s camp and they never recovered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget the World Cup and look forward to Newcastle United in the Premier League</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/28/forget-the-world-cup-and-look-forward-to-newcastle-united-in-the-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 18:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/28/forget-the-world-cup-and-look-forward-to-newcastle-united-in-the-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>The usual hype of England in the World Cup, the talk of them winning it. The talk of Wayne Rooney establishing himself as the best English striker in football for a long long time, the chat of Fabio Capello leading the Three Lions to World Cup glory. The media expected, the country anticipated but the competition against produced same-old England. What could have been if the linesman actually opened his eyes and saw the Lampard &amp;lsquo;goal&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle track Samuel as Toon policies go out the window?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/24/newcastle-track-samuel-as-toon-policies-go-out-the-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 22:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/24/newcastle-track-samuel-as-toon-policies-go-out-the-window/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s been lots of rumours floating around Tyneside in the last few days while the World Cup progresses nicely but one of them, regarding Bolton defender Jlloyd Samuel is some real news as Chris Hughton admitted an interest in the Trinidad &amp;amp; Tobago international. Samuel, now 29 may well be leaving the Reebok Stadium this year because he contract runs out very soon and Bolton Wanderers would be quite foolish not to cash in on him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United should act quick and sign Martin Petrov</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/09/newcastle-united-should-act-quick-and-sign-martin-petrov/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/09/newcastle-united-should-act-quick-and-sign-martin-petrov/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m the only person who thinks that Newcastle United should move as quick as they can and snap up Manchester City former Martin Petrov. The Bulgarian was released from the club after a good three years at the club. The winger is a talented player and alongside Sylvinho, Mancini waved goodbye to his services at the club, simply because they are not good enough for what is becoming a monstrous squad, and that&amp;rsquo;s not mentioning the wage bill!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Kris Boyd wants to play for Newcastle United – Sign Him Up</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/05/if-kris-boyd-wants-to-play-for-newcastle-united-sign-him-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 22:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/05/if-kris-boyd-wants-to-play-for-newcastle-united-sign-him-up/</guid>
      <description>Growing reports over the last few days or so claim that Kris Boyd is keen on leaving Rangers - for Newcastle United. The Scottish International has signalled that he is indeed leaving Rangers this season and on a free transfer. Various clubs are in for the hitman however if rumours are to be believed, Boyd is keen on playing for Newcastle United in the Premier League in August. I think we realise at this stage that we have no money to spend this summer on any new players so we won&amp;rsquo;t be expecting Jamie O&amp;rsquo;Hara, Hamit Altintop or Kevin Prince Boetang arriving on Tyneside any time soon, as if it was going to happen anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United need to move on and move up</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/02/newcastle-united-need-to-move-on-and-move-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 16:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/02/newcastle-united-need-to-move-on-and-move-up/</guid>
      <description>Bullard - Off to Celtic apparently in the next few days after Toon snub In my rare free time, I&amp;rsquo;ve been keeping an eye on the latest Newcastle United news and the players that we have been linked with in the last few weeks. From Hamit Altintop to Jimmy Bullard, Kris Boyd to Dedryck Boyata. The rumour mill is alive and healthy that&amp;rsquo;s for sure. The one that really sticks out though is the possible signing of Nedum Onuoha from Manchester City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle’s Five Year Plans could find Chris Hughton’s men in trouble</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/05/10/newcastles-five-year-plans-could-find-chris-hughtons-men-in-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 21:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/05/10/newcastles-five-year-plans-could-find-chris-hughtons-men-in-trouble/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Really does need a couple of signings this summer to get things right I suppose when you see the demise of Portsmouth Football Club and indeed the serous financial state of many well known clubs across the land, you know it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be long before Newcastle United would be hit with some sort of financial implication. Indeed here it is. A statement released by the club yesterday outlined the boards&amp;rsquo; plans for the coming few years, which 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xisco was never given time to prove his worth on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/24/xisco-was-never-given-time-to-prove-his-worth-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/24/xisco-was-never-given-time-to-prove-his-worth-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>First of all, a huge congratulations to Newcastle United for winning the Coca Cola Championship and indeed lifting it at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park today in front of a massive 52,000 fans. The attendance puts Sunderland&amp;rsquo;s and indeed many more Premier League club&amp;rsquo;s to shame and just shows what a footballing town Newcastle Upon-Tyne really is. Before the match, Chris Hughton announced that Xisco would not be in his plans for the upcoming Premier League campaign and he indeed expects the Spaniard to move on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United venture in for Norwegian as the dust settles throughout Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/22/newcastle-united-venture-in-for-norwegian-as-the-dust-settles-throughout-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 21:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/22/newcastle-united-venture-in-for-norwegian-as-the-dust-settles-throughout-europe/</guid>
      <description>Vital Football, who&amp;rsquo;s reliability is questionable for transfer stories have today revealed that Chris Hughton and co. made contact with Norwegian side FC Brann regards their little superstar with the name of Erik Huseklepp. This guy has been linked a fair few times to Newcastle and it&amp;rsquo;s believed that in the early hours of Monday morning Chris Hughton picked up the telephone and enquired about the tricky forward.
We&amp;rsquo;re making our transfer plans already which is good to see but if we do indeed making a formal offer for Huseklepp, I&amp;rsquo;m sure we&amp;rsquo;ll be surrounded by other clubs looking to take the Norwegian off FC Brann.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Chris Hughton not rate Ryan Taylor at all?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/20/does-chris-hughton-not-rate-ryan-taylor-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/20/does-chris-hughton-not-rate-ryan-taylor-at-all/</guid>
      <description>### Taylor - Hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen a whole lot of playing time on Tyneside this season
A great win yesterday and a very successful season to say the least. Thank you Chris Hughton, thank you supporters and indeed our thanks to the players. That aside, there&amp;rsquo;s been something in the back of my mind all the time and I have to bring it up. Ryan Taylor arrived from Wigan Athletic over a season ago, in the January transfer window alongside Kevin Nolan and came here with high hopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United considering keeping Fitz Hall permanently</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</guid>
      <description>There are reports flying about the place in the last couple of days that Fitz Hall could be arriving on Tyneside on a permanent basis once the transfer window reopens. The defender, on-loan from Queens Park Rangers has seen a turbulent time at Loftus Road and indeed has seen the club dig their way through more than 3 managers this season. Their current manager in Neil Warnock could well have very different plans for the back four he wants next season and indeed Hall may not be included in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United need to buy this Summer if we want to stay up</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</guid>
      <description>Owen - We don&amp;rsquo;t want too many signings similar to this guy anytime soon The day we splashed a record-breaking £15m to bring Alan Shearer to Newcastle from Premier League winning Blackburn Rovers, the footballing world came to a standstill and admired the Tyneside team for their courage in doing so, or at least we like to think they did! What a signing Alan Shearer turned about to be though, a true predator in front of goal and one of the best English strikers ever, if not the.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Newcastle avoid relegation it will be a very successful season in the Premier League</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/08/if-newcastle-avoid-relegation-it-will-be-a-very-successful-season-in-the-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 18:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/08/if-newcastle-avoid-relegation-it-will-be-a-very-successful-season-in-the-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>In the last few days, since Newcastle United were officially announced as a Premier League team, the question is being thrown about already, as to where the Magpies will finish come May 2011. A few pundits I&amp;rsquo;ve seen already are confident they&amp;rsquo;ll see Newcastle lie in and around the 12-15th spot, but I can&amp;rsquo;t help but think that&amp;rsquo;s very far fetched. Saying that, who thought Alex McLeish&amp;rsquo;s Birmingham City would be where they are at the start of the season?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley more involved in Newcastle United’s Coca Cola Championship season</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/19/mike-ashley-more-involved-in-newcastle-uniteds-coca-cola-championship-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/19/mike-ashley-more-involved-in-newcastle-uniteds-coca-cola-championship-season/</guid>
      <description>In a season that has saw our owner Mike Ashley try to sell but failing miserably yet again, however finally deciding to establish a tad of stability at the club. By that, it meant selling players, keeping some and after a long debacle as to who would be the full-time manager of Newcastle United, appointing Chris Hughton the former assistant of Kevin Keegan and Alan Shearer (alongside Iain Dowie). Hughton has since guided us to a pretty decent season so far which sees us top of the Coca Cola Championship, as we enter the final stages of what&amp;rsquo;s been a long season, and it&amp;rsquo;s still not over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton has changed the face of Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/06/chris-hughton-has-changed-the-face-of-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 21:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/06/chris-hughton-has-changed-the-face-of-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Doing a very professional job at Newcastle United this season As expected for some, we&amp;rsquo;re top of the Coca Cola Championship and so far so good for Newcastle United. In less that 12 months after we plummeted into the Coca Cola Championship without a whimper, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen a fair few &amp;lsquo;big&amp;rsquo; players leave the clubs and leave behind them, their big wages. Michael Owen, Obafemi Martins, Mark Viduka, Habib Beye, Damien Duff and many more left, as Newcastle United prepared for their first season in the lower tier of English football, in 16 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January transfer analysis – What Newcastle did differently this year</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/01/january-transfer-analysis-what-newcastle-did-differently-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 22:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/01/january-transfer-analysis-what-newcastle-did-differently-this-year/</guid>
      <description>Wayne Routledge was a good signing for Newcastle United  Routledge - Arrived on Tyneside for £1m in a successful transfer period  6 signings, no last minute stuff, and the majority for less than £1m. Mike Williamson, Danny Simpson, Wayne Routledge, Fitz Hall, Patrick van Aanholt and Leon Best all arrived at Newcastle in this January transfer window. 4 permanent signings, two loan deals. With Jose Enrique injured, Patrick van Aanholt has shown very promising signs in the Black and White shirt, and it seems as if he&amp;rsquo;s a very similar player to Jose, which is always a good find.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will we see Chris Hughton sign any more players before the deadline?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/31/will-we-see-chris-hughton-sign-anymore-players-before-the-deadline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 19:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/31/will-we-see-chris-hughton-sign-anymore-players-before-the-deadline/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Disappointed over missing out on Moses and rightly so News is rife that Wigan Athletic has completed the signing of promising English talent Victor Moses from Crystal Palace for a fee of £2.5m. The Nigerian born was heavily linked with a move for Moses, however the Magpies were unwilling to match the administrators asking price of £2.5m which could turn out to be a great bargain in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hall joins as Moses holds-out for Madrid call</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/29/hall-joins-as-moses-holds-out-for-madrid-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/29/hall-joins-as-moses-holds-out-for-madrid-call/</guid>
      <description>Hall - Good to some depth on the defensive side of things with Fitz It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I can say I&amp;rsquo;m quite happy with the transfer window. This time last year we signed Kevin Nolan and Ryan Taylor. Today we signed another two players in Fitz Hall &amp;amp; Patrick van Aanholt, to add to our 3 signings already. Although they&amp;rsquo;re only two loan signings, they&amp;rsquo;re our players for a while and that&amp;rsquo;s the most important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crystal Palace administrators will accept the highest bid for Moses</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/28/crystal-palace-administrators-will-accept-the-highest-bid-for-moses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 21:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/28/crystal-palace-administrators-will-accept-the-highest-bid-for-moses/</guid>
      <description>Moses - Would be a great signing from Chris if we could manage to pull it off You have to credit Chris Hughton since taking over this summer. Not only are we top of the table, playing generally well, but for the first time in a while, we&amp;rsquo;ve secured 3 transfer signings in a couple of weeks. This is very good news and encouraging stuff to say the least. With Danny Simpson, Wayne Routledge and Mike Williamson already confirmed Newcastle United players , theres strong reports that Brimingham&amp;rsquo;s Martin Taylor could be next on Tyneside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nile nets winner as the new-boys make their debuts on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Ranger - Netted again tonight as we saw Routledge &amp;amp; Williamson in action Tonights affair was a game we needed all three points from and the lads duly delivered the goods. In what was a Crystal Palace team without one of their main men in Victor Moses saw them concede within twenty minutes, a Shaun Derry O.G. In fairness, it seems as if Palace gave it a real go and could well have got something out of the game on another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayne Routledge is a very good signing for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/26/wayne-routledge-is-a-very-good-signing-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 16:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/26/wayne-routledge-is-a-very-good-signing-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Routledge - a Very good signing for the Toon Army is you ask me It&amp;rsquo;s surprise news to say the least to hear that Newcastle have signed Wayne Routledge from QPR today and very good news if you ask me. The winger has signed a reported 3 and a half deal on Tyneside and for a fee of £1m, which if true, is very good value. Routledge as you might remember was a Tottenham and Villa former and an exciting winger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edward Ofere being looked at with the news of Marlon Harewood’s broken foot</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/25/edward-ofere-being-looked-at-with-the-news-of-marlon-harewoods-broken-foot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 21:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/25/edward-ofere-being-looked-at-with-the-news-of-marlon-harewoods-broken-foot/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s being reported tonight that Mike Williamson has signed finally, for Newcastle United. The Portsmouth CB has supposedly signed on a 3-year deal for a fee of £1.2m. As well as this, according to Sky Sports, we could well make a move for Malmo&amp;rsquo;s Edward Ofere. As we reported in October of last year, Chris Hughton could well have the tall striker on his shortlist, and a list that&amp;rsquo;s getting shorter every day too I&amp;rsquo;m sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Shittu, Danny Simpson, Matthew Kilgallon &amp; Jemaine Beckford all Toon bound?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/14/danny-shittu-danny-simpson-matthew-kilgallon-jemaine-beckford-all-toon-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 20:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/14/danny-shittu-danny-simpson-matthew-kilgallon-jemaine-beckford-all-toon-bound/</guid>
      <description>Sky Sports are reporting that Bolton&amp;rsquo;s Danny Shittu could well arrive on Tyneside on a loan deal until the end of the season. The Nigerian hasn&amp;rsquo;t really had much of a look in at the Reebok and with the arrival of Owen Coyle, Newcastle are hopeful they can borrow the 6&amp;rsquo;2 centre half. Just in case you don&amp;rsquo;t know too much about him, he&amp;rsquo;s 29 years of age, a Nigerian international and has played for a fair few clubs in his time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Beckford bid fails for the last time, Hughton will look elsewhere</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/12/if-beckford-bid-fails-for-the-last-time-hughton-will-look-elsewhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/12/if-beckford-bid-fails-for-the-last-time-hughton-will-look-elsewhere/</guid>
      <description>Chris Hughton has today again reiterated his stance on Jermaine Beckford&amp;rsquo;s transfer scenario. Hughton has made it no secret that he&amp;rsquo;s after the 6&amp;rsquo;2 striker but insists that he&amp;rsquo;ll neither heighten his price, or be forced to do so. It&amp;rsquo;s believed that Newcastle have issued Leeds with an ultimatum, a bid of just about £2m, a take it or leave it offer for the Elland Road outfit. There&amp;rsquo;s no doubt that Beckford wants to join Newcastle and has even issued a transfer request to speed up his move away from Leeds if possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton should be looking abroad for new recruits</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/09/chris-hughton-should-be-looking-abroad-for-new-recruits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 21:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/09/chris-hughton-should-be-looking-abroad-for-new-recruits/</guid>
      <description>All the talk in the last few weeks has been about the likes of Matthew Kilgallon and Jermaine Beckford arriving on Tyneside. Today has been pretty quiet on the Toon front with the real focus on the snow, the other games in the Championship. We saw Cardiff City draw 1-1 at home to Ian Holloway&amp;rsquo;s Blackpool &amp;amp; Scunthorpe put four past a Derby County side which proved an equal match for us a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Players will be signed in January if needed – Llambias</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/23/players-will-be-signed-in-january-if-needed-llambias/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/23/players-will-be-signed-in-january-if-needed-llambias/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - Might actually invest in January in promotion bid
There&amp;rsquo;s some unbelievable news regarding Newcastle United today, Managing Director Derek Llambias has confirmed that Chris Hughton will be given cash to spend on new players if he needs. Ok, it mightn&amp;rsquo;t be that unbelievable but it might come as a surprise to some fans. Speaking today, Llambias said that Chris will be supported in the January transfer window by Mike Ashley and that it will be Chris&amp;rsquo;s own players that arrive at the club, if any players happen to arrive at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Beevers on Newcastle’s radar?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/22/mark-beevers-on-newcastles-radar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 15:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/22/mark-beevers-on-newcastles-radar/</guid>
      <description>### Beevers - Highly rated in English Football
It&amp;rsquo;s being reported, and not for the first time, that Newcastle United could well be taking a look at Sheffield Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s Mark Beevers. The defender who is a big 6&amp;rsquo;5 is meant to be attracting a lot of interest in not only the Championship, but also in the Premier League. Beevers received Player of the Season at Wednesday last year if memory serves me correct,and is only 20 years of age, and with a huge amount of potential if reports are accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can’t fault Chris Hughton so far</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/11/you-cant-fault-chris-hughton-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 16:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/11/you-cant-fault-chris-hughton-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Top of the table, seven points clear and a bunch of players that want success for this club, and no, I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about BSC Young Boys in the Super League in Switzerland. Newcastle are doing well and a man by the name of Chris Hughton is doing his job very well indeed. When Hughton&amp;rsquo;s name was mentioned with the permanent role as manager, a lot of people would&amp;rsquo;ve rather to have had Ruud Gullit back than Chris, but how that has changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton not looking to upset harmony in Toon squad</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/03/hughton-not-looking-to-upset-harmony-in-toon-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 22:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/03/hughton-not-looking-to-upset-harmony-in-toon-squad/</guid>
      <description>### Hughton - Not buying a truck load of players this Jan
Chris Hughton may be after a couple of players in January but he&amp;rsquo;s intent on not breaking the harmony within the Newcastle United squad at the minute. Or in simple English &amp;lsquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t fix it, if it&amp;rsquo;s not broken&amp;rsquo; and how right it is. We currently lie top of the Coca Cola Championship table as we enter a busy Christmas period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton in the hunt for new blood</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/07/hughton-in-the-hunt-for-new-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 14:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/07/hughton-in-the-hunt-for-new-blood/</guid>
      <description>Chris Hughton has said he&amp;rsquo;s very keen on strengthening his current crop of players will a couple of new arrivals. However, whether these arrivals will be permanent of not, is another matter. Reports are suggesting that although Ashley has agreed to back Chris in the transfer market, no new permanent arrivals could indeed land at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park during the Christmas period. There&amp;rsquo;s no doubt that numbers are needed for a vigorous upcoming Coca Cola Championship campaign, but we&amp;rsquo;re about a quarter of the way through and doing decently well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No more chops from Newcastle squad</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/06/no-more-chops-from-newcastle-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 17:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/06/no-more-chops-from-newcastle-squad/</guid>
      <description>### Hughton - Confident that only additions will be made
Chris Hughton has said he&amp;rsquo;s very confident that the squad will not shrink in numbers anymore, after nearly 10 players left in the summer. In return there&amp;rsquo;s been Danny Simpson, Marlon Harewood, and the long-named Zurab. All Premier League players to be fair but neither have showed any of that quality with perhaps Danny Simpson as an exception. However, Hughton believes that there will be no more out goings at the club but instead new faces will more than likely arrive at the forever St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Say – Will Newcastle United strengthen in January?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/29/your-say-will-newcastle-united-strengthen-in-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 19:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/29/your-say-will-newcastle-united-strengthen-in-january/</guid>
      <description>Now that Mike Ashley has decided to keep Newcastle United firmly within his grasp, reports are rife of players Chris Hughton is already lining up come January and when the transfer window opens again. Mike has promised to invest £20m of his own money by the end of the week, and a lot of that is believed to be going into the transfer pot for Chris, although I find that hard to believe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley promises Hughton a nice pot of gold – Sure</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/28/mike-ashley-promises-hughton-a-nice-pot-of-gold-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 16:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/28/mike-ashley-promises-hughton-a-nice-pot-of-gold-sure/</guid>
      <description>### Hughton - No grudge against him getting the job
The worst insult that a Newcastle United fan could get is not only destroying their beloved club, but trying to destroy their stadium name. Yesterday, on top of the devastating news that Mike Ashley had taken Newcastle United off the market, he also said that they were open to any offers for the naming rights of the stadium. This, is probably the cheekiest, and most arrogant move he has taken to date, and you really have to question yourself if he&amp;rsquo;s that stupid or being an outright (Insert your own word here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton offered £5000 a week at NUFC</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/25/chris-hughton-offered-5000-a-week-at-nufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 18:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/25/chris-hughton-offered-5000-a-week-at-nufc/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Expected to be announced soon It seems as if Chris Hughton will be the new Newcastle United manager, within the next few days. It comes as no surprise really but I&amp;rsquo;m sure there&amp;rsquo;s people out there who don&amp;rsquo;t like seeing Chris take full control. A huge amount of credit is due to Chris as he&amp;rsquo;s really brought Newcastle to it&amp;rsquo;s feet, on the field anyway and it seems as if he&amp;rsquo;s running a good system throughout the club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appointing Chris Hughton has it’s Pros and Cons</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/22/appointing-chris-hughton-has-its-pros-and-cons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 18:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/22/appointing-chris-hughton-has-its-pros-and-cons/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure we&amp;rsquo;re all well aware that Chris Hughton is very close to becoming Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s new manager within the next few days. Ashley, who looks to have failed with his attempts to sell the club again, is set to appoint Hughton as manager in hope of bringing us back to the Premier League. Two losses in a row, on the road have yet again highlighted our liabilities and none less than a shortage of players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United needs serious sorting out</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/21/newcastle-united-needs-serious-sorting-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 15:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/21/newcastle-united-needs-serious-sorting-out/</guid>
      <description>NUFC - Second loss in a row in the second tier of English football Yesterday Newcastle slumped to their second successive defeat on the road in the Coca Cola Championship. After going behind from some poor defending, we managed to equalise through Kevin Nolan, and it was a very good goal indeed, Premier League quality to be fair. However, we dropped out of the game again and conceded again with ten minutes remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another waste of time for NUFC</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/19/another-waste-of-time-for-nufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 15:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/19/another-waste-of-time-for-nufc/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - About to take NUFC off the market - again
I&amp;rsquo;m sorry if this article sounds a bit pessimistic but it&amp;rsquo;s hard not to be on a downer. News has broken today that Chris Hughton will be offered the full-time job and that later this week he&amp;rsquo;ll accept the final terms of what I&amp;rsquo;m sure will be quite a lucrative contract. However, that&amp;rsquo;s not the bad part, actually that probably the best news we could have expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton holds discussions with Mike &amp; Derek</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/17/hughton-holds-discussions-with-mike-derek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2009 10:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/17/hughton-holds-discussions-with-mike-derek/</guid>
      <description>I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that just after relegation, we wanted anybody but Chris Hughton as manager of Newcastle United. However, Shearer didn&amp;rsquo;t arrive, Kinnear&amp;rsquo;s comeback rumours were slashed at the but by NUFC themselves and David O&amp;rsquo;Leary&amp;rsquo;s move broke down. However now, Hughton has done a very good job and the majority of the players now want Chris as permanent manager. Lying top of the Coca Cola Chamoionship table and the players actually are playing for the shirt they wear, even the banana strip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gutierrez grateful for gaffers goodwill</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/10/gutierrez-grateful-for-gaffers-goodwill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 17:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/10/gutierrez-grateful-for-gaffers-goodwill/</guid>
      <description>### Jonas - Lining out for Argentina tonight
Newcastle United winger Jonas Gutierrez will tonight line out in what is a must win game for Argentina. If the Argies, led by former World Cup legend and the founder of the hand of god, Maradona, lose tonight, then their chances of making usually a familiar trip to the World Cup Finals, will be over. Maradona who claimed staggeringly, that his first three names on the Argentina team sheet were Lionel Messi, Javier Mascherano and Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s very own Jonas Gutierréz will as you&amp;rsquo;d expect start Jonas tonight and we certainly hope he comes back injury free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Michael to Marlon – Strikers void filled</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/27/from-michael-to-marlon-strikers-void-filled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 13:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/27/from-michael-to-marlon-strikers-void-filled/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago we had Michael Owen, one of the worlds most famous footballer, lining out in the Black and White of Newcastle United but after a rather dismal turn in events (relegation) Owen left, for the better we think. Yesterday the vacant #10 jersey was sported by Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s new signing, Marlon Harewood, on loan from Aston Villa. It quite an interesting turn around at Newcastle, as it seems Chris has filled the vacant positions, left behind by high paid &amp;lsquo;stars&amp;rsquo;, with determined players who want the very best for Newcastle United and their mighty fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Toon targets join other teams</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/20/two-toon-targets-join-other-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/20/two-toon-targets-join-other-teams/</guid>
      <description>Newcastle United have missed out on the chance of grabbing two strikers after the duo completed loan moves other Championship teams. James Vaughan, Everton&amp;rsquo;s striker join Derby County on loan whilst Irishman and Hull hitman, Caleb Folan completed his much awaited move to Middlesbrough. Both were targets of Newcastle, as confirmed by Chris himself and it&amp;rsquo;s quite disappointing to lose out, especially on James Vaughan who could&amp;rsquo;ve been excellent for us this season as we hope for a immediate return to the Premier League.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton wants another Hull hitman</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/13/hughton-wants-another-hull-hitman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 11:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/13/hughton-wants-another-hull-hitman/</guid>
      <description>### Cousin - Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a bad acquisition
After the news of Caleb Folan&amp;rsquo;s reported loan move to Newcastle United, there is more news today, that Newcastle are looking for Daniel Cousin as well. The forward who is very similar to Caleb Folan hasn&amp;rsquo;t been in and out of the Hull City side and it seems his relationship with manager Phil Brown isn&amp;rsquo;t a love affair by any means. Most of you will remember cousin scoring against us in the cup, which put us out last year but that was then and half the team that played that night no longer wear the Black and White of Newcastle United.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton may well deserve permanent deal</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/13/hughton-may-well-deserve-permanent-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 11:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/13/hughton-may-well-deserve-permanent-deal/</guid>
      <description>Chris Hughton enters today&amp;rsquo;s game in the Welsh capital with Manager of the Month accolade under his belt and with Shola Ameobi after claiming player of the month for the Coca Cola Championship as well. If Newcastle manage to beat Cardiff today, then they&amp;rsquo;ll return to the summit of the Coca Cola Championship and Hughton&amp;rsquo;s fine managerial experience will continue. I think most Toon fans have taken Chris for granted but there is now, the serious possibility that Mike Ashley will appoint Hughton manager on a full-time basis, should he fail to sell the club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton honoured with manager of the month</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/11/hughton-honoured-with-manager-of-the-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 19:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/11/hughton-honoured-with-manager-of-the-month/</guid>
      <description>A huge amount of credit is due to manager Chris Hughton as he has worked without one complaint, under sever conditions at Newcastle. The Irishman who was initially hired as an assistant for Kevin Keegan, in in his second term as temporary manager and he&amp;rsquo;s loving every minute of it, to say the least. And why wouldn&amp;rsquo;t he? Top of the table, playing good football and attracting on average, 40,000 Geordies to St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle interested in Potters defender?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/10/newcastle-interested-in-potters-defender/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 21:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/10/newcastle-interested-in-potters-defender/</guid>
      <description>### Cort - Good enough for Newcastle? Stokes&amp;rsquo; Leon Cort is being linked with a move to Newcastle tonight after the CB has fallen short of the first team at the Britannia. Bobby Robson engineered a move for Carl Cort, the infamous striker that cost Newcastle United £7m and failed to produce but we think things might be different with Leon. Of course he&amp;rsquo;d arrive on loan for a month and we&amp;rsquo;d take things from there but I suppose any back up or indeed players are only a plus at Newcastle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle target placed on transfer list</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/08/newcastle-target-placed-on-transfer-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 18:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/08/newcastle-target-placed-on-transfer-list/</guid>
      <description>Sturrock - Not our transfer target, but his manager Reported Newcastle United target Marcel Seip, from Plymouth Argyle, has been placed on the transfer window after a bust up with manager Paul Sturrock. It was reported that Newcastle were close to signing this player last weekend but Hughton dismissed these rumours. However, just like rumours are, they don&amp;rsquo;t go away too easily (especially at Newcastle) and news is rife that we&amp;rsquo;re about to complete a loan move for him within the next couple of days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harewood and Seip unlikely to arrive</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/07/harewood-and-seip-unlikely-to-arrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 14:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/07/harewood-and-seip-unlikely-to-arrive/</guid>
      <description>### Harewood - Out injured again
Chris Hughton today denied the rumours that he is set to capture Marcel Seip from Plymouth Argyle. The defender, who was reported to have had a bust up with manager Paul Sturrock was rumoured to have been on his way to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park within the next couple of days but today Chris refuted those reports. However one man that he took no time in confirming his interest in, was Marlon Harewood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton reveals his summer targets</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/03/hughton-reveals-his-summer-targets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 20:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/03/hughton-reveals-his-summer-targets/</guid>
      <description>### Hughton - Working under severe Ashley demands
Speaking today to local papers today, Chris Hughton, who is doing a really good job with the lads this season, revealed who he tried for during the transfer window period. Although the window has slammed shut, and slammed firmly shut for Chelsea, Championship squads can continue to loan and sign free agents. We&amp;rsquo;re currently top of the table, the last we said that was on the first day of the season with Sam Allardyce in charge, after a 3-1 victory at Bolton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harewood signing would add a new dimension</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/03/harewood-signing-would-add-a-new-dimension/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 17:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/03/harewood-signing-would-add-a-new-dimension/</guid>
      <description>### Harewood - Reportedly joining Newcastle next week
Well, I&amp;rsquo;m back from holidays in the Algarve, albeit a little sunburnt but the good news is, Newcastle United are top of the Coca Cola Championship with Chris Hughton doing a great job. A rather great goal from &amp;lsquo;Dan the man Guthrie&amp;rsquo; saw us through Leicester with Nile Ranger showing signs of a very good future striker. Steve Howard caused a few problems to our defence but Jose Enrique, Steven Taylor and co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still hope of more signings after Lovenkrands</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/02/still-hope-of-more-signings-after-lovenkrands/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 15:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/02/still-hope-of-more-signings-after-lovenkrands/</guid>
      <description>The Toon hopeful are still holding onto a glimmer of hope that we may well sign more than Peter Lovenkrands. Championship clubs still have the option to bring players in outside the transfer window. Craig Cathcart, Marlon Harewood, Darron Gibson and Franco di Santo have all be mentioned. Stay tuned to Sky Sports to get the latest developments on the scenario .
More to follow..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will it be a hectic day come Tuesday?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/31/will-it-be-a-hectic-day-come-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 16:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/31/will-it-be-a-hectic-day-come-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>### Hughton - Will he sign any players?
I haven&amp;rsquo;t been on in a day or so and I see not much has changed, besides the good news that Steven Taylor is committed to the club and also the fact that we can go top of the Championship if we beat Leicester tonight. Chris Hughton promised Toon fans a hectic day of transfer activity when the window slams shut on Tuesday but the signs aren&amp;rsquo;t really backing up that statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some transfer activity before Tuesday for Toon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/27/some-transfer-activity-before-tuesday-for-toon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/27/some-transfer-activity-before-tuesday-for-toon/</guid>
      <description>Chris Hughton has given us the clearest indication yet that more players will leave at Newcastle and as well as that, new faces are set to arrive. As the transfer window closes very very soon, Hughton is braced for new arrivals and as reported last night Gareth Bale is rumoured to be extremely close to sealing a move. However, the only problem is, his wage demands. At Spurs, Bale is meant to be earning 45k a week and let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, that&amp;rsquo;s far too much for a lad his age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle working on transfer targets?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/25/newcastle-working-on-transfer-targets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 11:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/25/newcastle-working-on-transfer-targets/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Doesn&amp;rsquo;t look best pleased! As the transfer window closes in about a week, the only player we&amp;rsquo;ve signed has been Danny Simpson from Manchester United, on loan. Although we haven&amp;rsquo;t added any new players to our squad besides Danny, we&amp;rsquo;ve let nearly 10 players leave St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. The likes of Michael Owen, Mark Viduka, David Edgar, Obafemi Martins, Damien Duff, Habib Beye , Sebastien Bassong and Peter Lovenkrands have all left the club for pastures anew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton more than likely staying as manager for West Brom game</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 13:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</guid>
      <description>It seems that the hierarchy have learned nowt over the last season and continue to play their own game, which is affecting all of us. Mike Ashley doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he&amp;rsquo;s doing sadly enough and his puppets aren&amp;rsquo;t much better. Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;m being a little too harsh on them, after all Ashley did invest a whole lot of money into Newcastle United with very little, no, return. You would have to feel a little sympathy for him in that sense but he made no steps whatsoever to make amends and sort the club and effectively brought the club to it&amp;rsquo;s knees, meaning here we are in the Coca Cola Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton confident current Newcastle United squad can brace the Championship</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/19/hughton-confident-current-newcastle-united-squad-can-brace-the-championship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2009 10:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/19/hughton-confident-current-newcastle-united-squad-can-brace-the-championship/</guid>
      <description>Taylor - Scored again yesterday with a header After a comprehensive hammering yesterday, Newcastle United are still waiting on new owners and indeed waiting we&amp;rsquo;ve been. It&amp;rsquo;s been well over 40 days since relegation and the only real changes have been players leaving on free contracts. Michael Owen being the most noticeable, scoring the winner on his début in Malaysia. Speaking after the match Chris Hughton indicated he expected an &amp;lsquo;announcement&amp;rsquo; soon and he gave the impression that he wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be head coach of Newcastle United for much longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hughton could turn permanent Newcastle United manager</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/06/29/hughton-could-turn-permanent-newcastle-united-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 18:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/06/29/hughton-could-turn-permanent-newcastle-united-manager/</guid>
      <description>Hughton - Could be made permanent should Ashley&amp;rsquo;s regime continue As the confusion continues and there&amp;rsquo;s still no worthwhile communication it seems that Chris Hughton as scary as this may sound, is favorite to come Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s permanent manager, yes permanent, not interim. The first real bit of action from Newcastle (or someone) was to re appoint Chris Hughton to first team duties and get them organised for their pre-season, staring in Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>