<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yohan Cabaye on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/yohan-cabaye/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yohan Cabaye on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 16:30:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/yohan-cabaye/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Midterm Report: Just how good has Yohan Cabaye been this season?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/24/midterm-report-just-good-yohan-cabaye-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 16:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/24/midterm-report-just-good-yohan-cabaye-season/</guid>
      <description>After half an hour of Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s tie against West Ham in the Premier League last Saturday, it was absolutely clear the quality of a midfielder that the club have in Yohan Cabaye. When The Frenchman was linked with a move away in the summer some Newcastle fans played down his real ability, and dubbed him as a &amp;lsquo;good player&amp;rsquo; but &amp;lsquo;not great&amp;rsquo;, and certainly not European quality. I argued that he was one of the finest midfielders in Europe when on form and in turn asked some of the doubters why the likes of PSG and Arsenal were looking into signing him if he was - as they said - just a &amp;lsquo;good&amp;rsquo; midfielder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PIC: Yohan Cabaye spotted boarding Paris flight</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/03/pic-yohan-cabaye-spotted-boarding-paris-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 17:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/03/pic-yohan-cabaye-spotted-boarding-paris-flight/</guid>
      <description>Now before any of us get ahead of ourselves - this picture could be dated. Secondly if it is indeed a picture from today as many are suggesting then Yohan Cabaye might only be heading for a short break across the sea since he has been ruled out of Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s cup clash with Cardiff City. Anyway, Tyne Time will show the news for what it is and it looks as if Cabaye is heading to France for one reason of another, his latest &amp;lsquo;injury&amp;rsquo; adding to claims that the talented midfielder may well be looking to secure a move away from St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona after Yohan Cabaye for £8m – Pigs can fly</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/11/barcelona-after-yohan-cabaye-for-8m-pigs-can-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 12:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/11/barcelona-after-yohan-cabaye-for-8m-pigs-can-fly/</guid>
      <description>#### Cabaye - Worth £20m at the very least and has no intentions of leaving NUFC
There has been some typically bad journalism from the Daily Mail in the last few years regarding Newcastle United, but they&amp;rsquo;ve certainly topped this years efforts with the latest rumour. Today, they linked Yohan Cabaye to Barcelona - for a fee of £8m. First off, why would Barcelona need more midfielders with the likes of Xavi, Iniesta, Busquets and countless others in their ranks, including all their young prospects that will gradually make a move up to the first team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is the last time Newcastle United have had so many..</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/when-is-the-last-time-newcastle-united-have-had-so-many/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 21:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/when-is-the-last-time-newcastle-united-have-had-so-many/</guid>
      <description>Benny - Making the French squad a testament to his work since the horrid broken leg NUFC players heading to a major tournament? World Cup 2010, Jonas Gutierrez featured for Argentina, was there anyone else in South Africa on Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s books? Euro 2008? Can&amp;rsquo;t say I remember anyone representing NUFC at the tournament. This year however, Hatem Ben Arfa, Yohan Cabaye and Tim Krul look likely to go. For a European championship, that is a pretty impressive showing, and a testament to Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s fantastic season; especially when two of the three are part of a potential Euro 2012 winning team, in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classy Cabaye sends The Potters packing – Goal Highlights</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/21/classy-cabaye-sends-the-potters-packing-goal-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 19:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/21/classy-cabaye-sends-the-potters-packing-goal-highlights/</guid>
      <description>Cabaye - Played his best 90 minutes in a Black and White shirt today scoring twice Yohan Cabaye today turned in his best performance in a Newcastle United jersey against Stoke City in a comfortable 3-0 win for the lads. Opening &amp;amp; closing the scoring, with a routine Papiss Cissé goal inbetween - Cabaye sent Newcastle United into 4th spot in the Premier League. It was all NUFC from the first whistle, and after 13 minutes a bit of brilliance from Ben Arfa out on the wing helped the ball into Cissé who hit the bar - only for Cabaye to follow-up and nod it in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United scouted Yohan Cabaye for 5 years before placing bid</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/23/newcastle-united-scouted-yohan-cabaye-for-5-years-before-placing-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 15:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/23/newcastle-united-scouted-yohan-cabaye-for-5-years-before-placing-bid/</guid>
      <description>Cabaye - Turning out to be a contender for Premier League signing of the season In aninteresting read by Mark Douglas over at the Sunday Sun, revealed that Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s scouting team were keeping tabs on Yohan Cabaye, before signing him this summer. To be honest, I find that slightly difficult to believe. If we date back five years from this very day, we&amp;rsquo;re in the year 2006. Those were the years of Glenn Roeder, and the likes of Damien Duff, Obafemi Martins, Anotine Sibierski and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yohan Cabaye the lynchpin of the new-look Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/21/yohan-cabaye-the-lynchpin-of-the-new-look-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 17:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/21/yohan-cabaye-the-lynchpin-of-the-new-look-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Cabaye - Class act and another shrewd piece of business by Newcastle United We may well look back at Saturday the 17th of September as the day Yohan Cabaye announced his arrival in the Premier League. The Frenchman played arguably his best ninety minutes in a Black and White shirt since his arrival and generally was sublime on the ball. It&amp;rsquo;s just a pity that he didn&amp;rsquo;t get his deserved goal on the day, the crossbar and a magnificent Shay Given save denying him two possible goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United set for most exciting summer transfer window in years</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/09/newcastle-united-set-for-most-exciting-summer-transfer-window-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/09/newcastle-united-set-for-most-exciting-summer-transfer-window-in-years/</guid>
      <description>Gervinho - Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too surprised if he doesn&amp;rsquo;t arrive on Tyneside I&amp;rsquo;m sure that most the Premier League are aware of the Gervinho scenario by now. Over a week ago he was meant to have signed for Newcastle United, alongside Yohan Cabaye. The funny this is: neither have signed officially yet however, Cabaye is expected to be revealed holding our new 2011&amp;frasl;12 jersey as early as tomorrow. I am also quite sure that most internet friendly NUFC fans will have wandered on to Twitter at some stage, whether it&amp;rsquo;s been to follow us or indeed keep tabs on the many rumour &amp;lsquo;merchants&amp;rsquo; flooding the Newcastle news scene lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lille’s Yohan Cabaye the inevitable replacement for the loyal Joey Barton</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/01/lilles-yohan-cabaye-the-inevitable-replacement-for-the-loyal-joey-barton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 18:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/01/lilles-yohan-cabaye-the-inevitable-replacement-for-the-loyal-joey-barton/</guid>
      <description>Cabaye - Likely to replace Joey Barton as the club looks to offload the POTS The board at this club continue to confuse me with their antics. Firstly they sack an absolute gent of a manager who after bringing Newcastle United back to the Premier League at first attempt, was looking like he would finish midtable after some stunning results throughout the season - including an away win at Arsenal, Chelsea, Everton &amp;amp; indeed absolute routs at home to Aston Villa and Sunderland.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>