<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fabricio Coloccini on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/fabricio-coloccini/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fabricio Coloccini on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 17:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/fabricio-coloccini/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabricio Coloccini wants to see out remainder of career at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2015/08/05/fabricio-coloccini-wants-to-see-out-career-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 17:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2015/08/05/fabricio-coloccini-wants-to-see-out-career-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - Reportedly plans on ending his playing career at Newcastle United There have been many questions raised about the future of current Newcastle United captain, Fabricio Coloccini as the new season approaches. The 33 year-old Argentine joined The Magpies in a £10m deal from Deportivo La Coruna and became one of Kevin Keegan&amp;rsquo;s first signings in his second stint in charge of the club. While many managers and players have come and gone since 2008, Coloccini has - surprisingly - stayed on Tyneside those seven years and became something of an adopted Geordie alongside the recently released, Jonas Gutierrez.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabricio Coloccini acts as Pardew’s mouth-piece ahead of crunch clash</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/19/fabricio-coloccini-acts-pardews-mouth-piece-ahead-crunch-clash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 19:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/19/fabricio-coloccini-acts-pardews-mouth-piece-ahead-crunch-clash/</guid>
      <description>With less than 20 hours till Newcastle United play host to what is expected to be the most toxic atmosphere in the club&amp;rsquo;s history, club &amp;lsquo;captain&amp;rsquo; Fabricio Coloccini has called on supporters to come out and give the team their full backing when they take to St. James&amp;rsquo; Park against Hull City. Coloccini, who arrived on Tyneside in 2008 under Kevin Keegan has gone on to become on of Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s finest defenders in recent years, however, over the past 12 months, the Argentine has lost the respect of a considerable number of supporters, including myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Coloccini’s commitment to Newcastle signal bear significance?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/05/06/coloccinis-commitment-newcastle-signal-bear-significance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 16:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/05/06/coloccinis-commitment-newcastle-signal-bear-significance/</guid>
      <description>In a timely boost for all associated with Newcastle United, captain Fabricio Coloccini today confirmed that he will be staying at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park for next season, at least. The Argentinian centre-back was widely expected to depart Tyneside for a return to his home nation, but all has been put to bed as the ball-playing defender announced to the Shields Gazette that he is already looking forward to the next campaign in a Newcastle jersey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midterm Report: Consistent Coloccini classy as ever</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/21/midterm-report-consistent-coloccini-classy-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 19:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/21/midterm-report-consistent-coloccini-classy-ever/</guid>
      <description>To this very day of writing, Fabricio Coloccini remains Mike Ashley&amp;rsquo;s most expensive signing. The club parted with £10.3m for the composed Argentine and just six months later it looked like he had the makings of another Jean Alain-Boumsong or Titus Bramble. Coloccini&amp;rsquo;s lack of pace saw him vulnerable in his debut season and as we all know, the club eventually succumbed to dreaded relegation in 2009. Despite that, down to a mixture of the club being unable to sell him and Fabricio&amp;rsquo;s sense of underachievement the bushy haired South American stayed with the club in the Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Fabricio Coloccini keep his promise to Newcastle United fans?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/23/will-fabricio-coloccini-keep-his-promise-to-newcastle-united-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 14:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/23/will-fabricio-coloccini-keep-his-promise-to-newcastle-united-fans/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - Made a promise to Newcastle United fans a couple years ago Just over two years ago in an interview with The Northern Echo; Fabricio Coloccini promised Newcastle United fans something quite special if Newcastle United were to play Champions League football some stage in the future. In the build up to our away game against Plymouth Argyle - where we clinched the Championship title - Coloccini made the pledge that he would shave his head if Newcastle United managed to secure a top 4 place in the EPL anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The most worrying thing as a Newcastle United fan right now</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/12/the-most-worrying-thing-as-a-newcastle-united-fan-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 21:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/12/the-most-worrying-thing-as-a-newcastle-united-fan-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - We need to make sure we sign this guy down for the rest of his career There is very little to be worried about as Newcastle United fan at the minute, especially as we lie sixth in the table, a solitary point off a Champions League spot. The fantastic season we&amp;rsquo;ve had so far has come down to a great team effort, and one of the performers of the campaign so far is without doubt Fabricio Coloccini.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabricio Coloccini has been an absolute steal for £10.5m from Deportivo La Coruna</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/18/fabricio-coloccini-has-been-an-absolute-steal-at-10-5m-from-deportivo-la-coruna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 15:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/18/fabricio-coloccini-has-been-an-absolute-steal-at-10-5m-from-deportivo-la-coruna/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - Has been outstanding in only his 2nd season in the Premier League I think we all remember Fabricio Coloccini&amp;rsquo;s first season in the Premier League. Lack of pace, and prone to many a blunder. Some of us asked ourselves if he was really worth the £10.5m Kevin Keegan paid over, if in fact he was Kevin&amp;rsquo;s choice at all.
Following relegation, Coloccini did not leave and it seemed as if no one was going to take a gamble on the Argentinian international after what was nothing short of a disastrous first season in English football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United considering keeping Fitz Hall permanently</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</guid>
      <description>There are reports flying about the place in the last couple of days that Fitz Hall could be arriving on Tyneside on a permanent basis once the transfer window reopens. The defender, on-loan from Queens Park Rangers has seen a turbulent time at Loftus Road and indeed has seen the club dig their way through more than 3 managers this season. Their current manager in Neil Warnock could well have very different plans for the back four he wants next season and indeed Hall may not be included in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloccini has helped Mike Williamson settle on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/04/coloccini-has-helped-mike-williamson-settle-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/04/coloccini-has-helped-mike-williamson-settle-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - Mike Williamson grateful of the Argentine&amp;rsquo;s help and experience It&amp;rsquo;s true to say Fabricio Coloccini has been a rock at the central of defence this season at Newcastle United and really, he&amp;rsquo;d want to be putting in a good shift after setting us back £10.3m in the &amp;lsquo;Keegan Summer&amp;rsquo;. Another centre-back who arrived on Tyneside this January by the name of Mike Williamson from troubled Portsmouth has also been sturdy at the heart of our defence, a position where we&amp;rsquo;ve lacked real quality throughout the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabricio Coloccini – Would you sell or keep?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/28/fabricio-coloccini-would-you-sell-or-keep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 21:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/28/fabricio-coloccini-would-you-sell-or-keep/</guid>
      <description>A division down and a better looking Coca Cola Championship table. A better looking defence and a far better looking goal difference. However, don&amp;rsquo;t be entirely convinced, our players haven&amp;rsquo;t just found magical form this season. One man who has caught the eye of many is Fabricio Coloccini and his improved performances this season have been a welcome relief. Let&amp;rsquo;s not forget though, this guy cost £10.3m and at one stage, played every single game in the La Liga with Deportivo la Coruna.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabricio Coloccini absence costing Newcastle top spot?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/10/fabricio-coloccini-absence-costing-newcastle-top-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 16:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/10/fabricio-coloccini-absence-costing-newcastle-top-spot/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - Being missed at the heart of the Newcastle United defence? The questions are really mounting about Newcastle United and whether we&amp;rsquo;ll throw our promotion hopes out the window. It&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous to say we&amp;rsquo;re slipping up as this is our first defeat in 15 games in the league, albeit a big defeat. The pairing at the back yesterday of Mike Williamson and Fitz Hall were brilliant against Cardiff one Friday last, but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t keep out Rob Hulse and co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A laughable Toon rumour to end the year 2009?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/27/a-laughable-toon-rumour-to-end-the-year-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/27/a-laughable-toon-rumour-to-end-the-year-2009/</guid>
      <description>The Sunday Sun are reporting that Real Madrid could well be lining up a move for Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s Fabricio Coloccini after Pepe&amp;rsquo;s injury has proven to be a serious one, and will keep the Portuguese international out of action for months to come. In fairness to Coloccini, he&amp;rsquo;s being doing well this season as you&amp;rsquo;d expect, especially from a £10.3m signing who played in the Champions League only a few years back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloccini turned down move away from Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/30/coloccini-turned-down-move-away-from-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/30/coloccini-turned-down-move-away-from-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Despite having a torrid first season in the Premier League and indeed becoming the laughing stock of Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s leaky defence, it seems that Fabricio Coloccini still had offers on the table for his services. Saying that, I&amp;rsquo;d expect that there was offers but ones of a laughable amount, and we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too keen on seeing him go for pennies considering we paid over £10m for him last summer. Declaring himself very unhappy at Newcastle on many an occasion you were almost certain that Colo would move away from the Toon, be it on loan or permanent, however, after collecting the MOTM award on Saturday, I doubt he&amp;rsquo;ll be going anywhere any time soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloccini being courted by European clubs</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/17/coloccini-being-courted-by-european-clubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/17/coloccini-being-courted-by-european-clubs/</guid>
      <description>Fabricio Coloccini is being touted for a return to Spain after a number of clubs have show interest in the Argentinian centre back. Arriving from Deportivo for a staggering £10.3m, Colo never settled and his game under Kevin Keegan (yes, Kevin Keegan) against Manchester United was arguably his best one. We saw glimpses of the old Coloccini against reading on Saturday but it all has to do with confidence. If we get an offer of half the mount we paid to Fabricio I think that it may well be accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habib Beye involved in half-time scuffle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/habib-beye-involved-in-half-time-scuffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 23:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/habib-beye-involved-in-half-time-scuffle/</guid>
      <description>Beye - Fighting for Newcastle in every sense In a one nil victory over Huddersfield Town, in which Kevin Nolan scored the winner, Habib Beye was involved in a HT bust-up with Huddersfield Town captain Peter Clarke. It&amp;rsquo;s not fully clear what happened in the tunnel but it&amp;rsquo;s understood Beye nor Clarke were too happy about each other. Indeed it must have been something quite big as Fabricio Coloccini was too involved in a confrontation after the final whistle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloccini willing to stay at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/19/coloccini-willing-to-stay-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2009 17:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/19/coloccini-willing-to-stay-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - Will stay if his wages remain the same - no thank you Fabricio Coloccini said today that he would consider staying at Newcastle United during our first Coca Cola Championship campaign, but only if he retains his £50,000k + a week. Speaking about a proposed transfer away from the club he said it was basically impossible to leave at the time being because of Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s constant uncertainty and the mess we&amp;rsquo;re in right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United receive Coloccini and Oba Martins bids</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/04/newcastle-united-receive-coloccini-and-oba-martins-bids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 12:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/04/newcastle-united-receive-coloccini-and-oba-martins-bids/</guid>
      <description>Martins - Being forced out of Newcastle even though he wants to stay There are reports that Keith Harris, the guy in charge of selling Newcastle, has told Mike Ashley to accept bids for Fabricio Coloccini and Obafemi Martins to ease the financial strain on himself as the sale of NUFC nears a close. Obafemi Martins who has already said he wants to stay and doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to be sold is being forced out and the Journal have confirmed that bids from foreign clubs have been made for both players.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>