<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andy Carroll on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/andy-carroll/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Andy Carroll on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 14:47:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/andy-carroll/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Liverpool’s £17m valuation of Andy Carroll simply too high</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/17/liverpools-17m-valuation-of-andy-carroll-simply-too-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 14:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/17/liverpools-17m-valuation-of-andy-carroll-simply-too-high/</guid>
      <description>#### Carroll - Wants to come home and his return is a a real possibility
Some things are just perfect. Selling a guy to Liverpool for £35m after only playing three-quarters of a Premier League season, and then finishing above them in the league with their new signing having very little impact, is probably as close as perfect can get when it comes to football. The cherry on top of it all sees Newcastle United coming back in for Carroll in a cut price deal and the player himself, refusing to talk to any other club other than his homeland team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How much would you pay to bring Andy Carroll back to St.James’ Park?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/01/03/how-much-would-you-pay-to-bring-andy-carroll-back-to-st-james-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 17:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/01/03/how-much-would-you-pay-to-bring-andy-carroll-back-to-st-james-park/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - What price would you pay to bring the Geordie back to Tyneside? First of all, it&amp;rsquo;s not happening. Andy Carroll will not return to Newcastle United this January or even in the summer. Lazy journalism seems to have spurred on continuous rumours of a return for the £35m man; either on loan or permanently. I&amp;rsquo;m sure Andy himself would indeed welcome a move back to Tyneside in order to refind the form that saw the 6ft 2 striker become one of the most sought after English forwards of his decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There comes a time in football when realism must prevail</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/01/there-comes-a-time-in-football-when-realism-must-prevail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 19:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/01/there-comes-a-time-in-football-when-realism-must-prevail/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Off to Anfield whether pushed or shoved out of St. James&amp;rsquo; Park irst things first; yesterdays deadline window was no doubt the most enthralling transfer window I have ever followed, but Sky Sports really did over-do the whole thing. Every 5 minutes they popped back to David Craig outside St.James&amp;rsquo; Park and he seemed to have a new story, or something a little different each time. If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t that, they were in Liverpool trying to get the latest on the Fernando Torres deal from their correspondent, amidst overly-excited LFC fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United should venture in for Jô with Edin Džeko set for January move</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/29/newcastle-united-should-venture-in-for-jo-with-edin-dzeko-set-for-january-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 18:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/29/newcastle-united-should-venture-in-for-jo-with-edin-dzeko-set-for-january-move/</guid>
      <description>#### Jô - Would be an extremely good addition to Newcastle United this January
It is very likely that Edin Džeko will join Manchester City this January in a €35m move come January as VfL Wolfsburg have lowered their asking initial asking price. Another ridiculous fee to pay for a striker who I can only guess would be delighted to join the club for its wages. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, Edin is a fine talent and will score a lot of goals given the chance, but he isn&amp;rsquo;t worth any more than £17m in all honesty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirited Newcastle United performance undone by misfortune and Tevez</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/26/spirited-newcastle-united-performance-undone-by-misfortune-and-tevez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2010 22:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/26/spirited-newcastle-united-performance-undone-by-misfortune-and-tevez/</guid>
      <description>#### Carroll - Scored yet again today and continues to be linked with Toon exit
Frustrating isn&amp;rsquo;t the word. When Fabricio Coloccini put the ball into his own net in the last ten minutes of the game, my heart sank and I nearly dropped my turkey sandwich. We had dominated the second half, every ball was ours, Carroll won every header, Cheik Tiote cleaned up every spill in centre midfield and Jose Enrique &amp;amp; Jonas Gutierrez swept up everything on the leftside of the pitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton responsible for Andy Carroll’s inclusion in England squad</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/15/chris-hughton-responsible-for-andy-carrolls-inclusion-in-england-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 21:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/15/chris-hughton-responsible-for-andy-carrolls-inclusion-in-england-squad/</guid>
      <description>7 goals so far this season, including the memorable one against Arsenal at the Emirates to secure a truly inspirational win. Called up by Fabio Capello at the age of 21 to represent his country, it really doesn&amp;rsquo;t get much better for the Geordie lad. It&amp;rsquo;s not the fact he&amp;rsquo;s one of our own that makes us so happy with him, it&amp;rsquo;s the type of striker he is. A nuisance for defenders, a great header of the ball, an old fashioned CF to put it to you straight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carroll &amp; Nolan binge after the Sunderland victory, where do the media get off?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/07/carroll-nolan-binge-after-the-sunderland-victory-where-do-the-media-get-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 13:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/07/carroll-nolan-binge-after-the-sunderland-victory-where-do-the-media-get-off/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Staying in Nolan&amp;rsquo;s house since his courting hearing a few weeks ago Well my latest article has been a long time coming and I apologise for that, however, I was intending on writing an article before the Tyne Wear derby about why on earth there was rumours of Chris Hughton being sacked, but when they won 5-1 it would&amp;rsquo;ve look a little suspect. Observing all the latest news about Newcastle in the latest few weeks has led me to inevitably write this article, quite frankly because I can&amp;rsquo; believe what I&amp;rsquo;m seeing day in day out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carroll commits to Newcastle leaving Stoke stumped</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/04/carroll-commits-to-newcastle-leaving-stoke-stumped/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 21:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/04/carroll-commits-to-newcastle-leaving-stoke-stumped/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Committed to Newcastle United and our Premier League survival bid Well we know Stoke were interested and who could blame them. A strong, tall old fashioned centre-forward at only 20 years of age and with a newly promoted team. In fact, he would have been the perfect player for Stoke City, and the &amp;lsquo;football&amp;rsquo; they play. With James Beattie looking like he may well leave The Britannia, Carroll would&amp;rsquo;ve been the ideal replacement but the Geordie lad is committed to his home-town club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy Carroll putting his career in doubt with the latest events on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/23/andy-carroll-doesnt-deserve-to-be-a-footballer-with-the-latest-events-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/23/andy-carroll-doesnt-deserve-to-be-a-footballer-with-the-latest-events-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Foolish, selfish, ridiculous, childish, stupid, outrageous and more than anything, arrogant. The Andy Carroll story. Reportedly he&amp;rsquo;s after breaking Steven Taylor&amp;rsquo;s jaw in a Sunday training session and I needn&amp;rsquo;t say anymore. Disgraceful from a Geordie born lad who was making great strides this season. Now however, his season is over as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned and he&amp;rsquo;ll be extremely lucky to remain a Newcastle United player too. This is just utterly disgraceful and nothing less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watford v Newcastle – Magpies need to maintain goal monsoon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/27/watford-v-newcastle-magpies-need-to-maintain-goal-monsoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 02:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/27/watford-v-newcastle-magpies-need-to-maintain-goal-monsoon/</guid>
      <description>Every game from now until May is of huge importance to Newcastle United and our promotion hopes. The laughing stock of English football last year, we&amp;rsquo;ve managed to get a modest manager, and eventually managed to get some much needed faces in January, something that played a big factor in sending us down last season. Now however, we&amp;rsquo;re no longer the main club that&amp;rsquo;s subject to a huge amount of jokes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toon’s sunken ship steals point at Swansea City</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/13/toons-sunken-ship-steals-point-at-swansea-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2010 23:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/13/toons-sunken-ship-steals-point-at-swansea-city/</guid>
      <description>Cotterill - Scored a beauty today in what was a lucky point for the Toon A precious point, one to bring us aloft the Coca Cola Championship again, and even Nottingham Forest lost, again aiding our promotion push. Sounds like the perfect day eh? Not for me. A lazy, disappointing and a beleaguered effort from a side who based on todays performance, do not deserve to win the title outright.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovenkrands &amp; Carroll score twice as Cardiff capitulate</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/05/lovenkrands-carroll-score-twice-as-cardiff-capitulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 22:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/05/lovenkrands-carroll-score-twice-as-cardiff-capitulate/</guid>
      <description>Lovenkrands - Came off the bench to score twice including a beauty on his left First of all, I was very wrong in my predictions about tonights game. Very wrong indeed. In what was a totally one sided affair from the very first whistle, Newcastle United fired 5 goals past Dave Jones side. An early opener from Andy Carroll followed by an unfortunate turn of events which saw Gyepes put the ball into his own net, with Andy Carroll again to thank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy Carroll being dealt with by Newcastle over ‘incident’</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/10/andy-carroll-being-dealt-with-by-newcastle-over-incident/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 21:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/10/andy-carroll-being-dealt-with-by-newcastle-over-incident/</guid>
      <description>Being a young footballer at any club is a dream come true. Playing for local team and the club you&amp;rsquo;ve supported all you&amp;rsquo;re life is a boyhood dream. Money, women and the many other commodities of modern footballers has saw many of them fail to make the cut in football with their respective clubs. Not because of a lack of talent but because of a lack of maturity and responsibility, some thing that comes with age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now’s not the time for Newcastle nightclub nightmares</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/07/nows-not-the-time-for-newcastle-nightclub-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/07/nows-not-the-time-for-newcastle-nightclub-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>### Carroll - Arrested by police in early hours or Monday morning
It&amp;rsquo;s being reported pretty much everywhere that Andy Carroll has been arrested by police in the early hours of Monday morning following an incident in a local Newcastle nightclub. Carroll who was lounging with friends in the VIP area was involved in a scuffle with an unknown individual but what is known is that the unknown man, came out the worst in the affair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could Andy Carroll make the England World Cup squad?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/13/could-andy-carroll-make-the-england-world-cup-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 21:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/13/could-andy-carroll-make-the-england-world-cup-squad/</guid>
      <description>Andy Carroll has been training in Watford ahead of the England U-21&amp;rsquo;s must win fixture against Portugal in the European Qualifying Championship Qualifiers. Carroll who has been in pretty decent form for his local club Newcastle is supposedly being monitored by Fabio Capello for the England 2010 World Cup squad. These reports might seem just a little dubious and I&amp;rsquo;d be very surprised if the Newcastle born striker was handed a shirt in the same squad as Wayne Rooney, Jermaine Defoe and even the likes of Darren Bent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>