<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matthew Kilgallon on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/matthew-kilgallon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Matthew Kilgallon on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 16:31:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/matthew-kilgallon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilgallon could still arrive at Newcastle as Beckford transfer scenario lingers on</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/08/kilgallon-could-still-arrive-at-newcastle-as-beckford-transfer-scenario-lingers-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/08/kilgallon-could-still-arrive-at-newcastle-as-beckford-transfer-scenario-lingers-on/</guid>
      <description>Kilgallon - Newcastle still reportedly in the hunt despite statement Although Matthew Kilgallon indicated that he will stay on at Sheffield United for the remainder of the season, there are still rumours out there that he could well still arrive at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park. As he&amp;rsquo;s in his last few months of his contract at Bramall Lane, Kilgallon will seek a move in the summer for free, and to a Premier League club if he can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilgallon staying with Sheffield – Who next for Hughton?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/06/kilgallon-staying-with-sheffield-who-next-for-hughton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 11:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/06/kilgallon-staying-with-sheffield-who-next-for-hughton/</guid>
      <description>### Kilgallon - Staying at Bramall Lane until end of the season
Chris Hughton will now have to readjust his January transfer target and his main man, Matthew Kilgallon has said today that he&amp;rsquo;s staying put at Sheffield United. Kilgallon, who was expected to make the move to us this January has opted to try and push for promotion with the Blades and reassess his options in the summer. In fairness, you&amp;rsquo;ve to credit the lad there, he wants to stay and hopefully achieve promotion with manager Kevin Blackwell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It seems as if Kilgallon &amp; Beckford are close to signing for Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/01/it-seems-as-if-kilgallon-beckford-are-close-to-signing-for-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 17:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/01/it-seems-as-if-kilgallon-beckford-are-close-to-signing-for-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>### Targets - Hughton is confident they&amp;rsquo;ll arrive
According to surfacing reports and the many of them, Jermaine Beckford and Matthew Kilgallon will be signing for Newcastle United in the January transfer window. Both &amp;lsquo;The Killer&amp;rsquo; and Beckford have been lined with possible moves to Newcastle, since the start of 2009 but no move materialized for either of them. Kilgallon, as well as Beckford are in the final months of their respective contracts and Chris Hughton is hoping to get a bargain on both of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>