<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jermaine Beckford on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/jermaine-beckford/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jermaine Beckford on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 18:21:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/jermaine-beckford/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jermaine Beckford NOT arriving is a good thing</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/17/jermaine-beckford-not-arriving-is-a-good-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 18:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/17/jermaine-beckford-not-arriving-is-a-good-thing/</guid>
      <description>Beckford - Staying at Leeds until the end of the season to help promotion bid There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of disappointed Newcastle United fans out there today at the news Leeds United&amp;rsquo;s Jermaine Beckford will remain at Leeds United and try aid their promotion charge. A two nil away loss to Exeter City yesterday I&amp;rsquo;m sure played a certain part in his decision and there&amp;rsquo;s no doubt Leeds do really need the the striker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Shittu, Danny Simpson, Matthew Kilgallon &amp; Jemaine Beckford all Toon bound?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/14/danny-shittu-danny-simpson-matthew-kilgallon-jemaine-beckford-all-toon-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 20:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/14/danny-shittu-danny-simpson-matthew-kilgallon-jemaine-beckford-all-toon-bound/</guid>
      <description>Sky Sports are reporting that Bolton&amp;rsquo;s Danny Shittu could well arrive on Tyneside on a loan deal until the end of the season. The Nigerian hasn&amp;rsquo;t really had much of a look in at the Reebok and with the arrival of Owen Coyle, Newcastle are hopeful they can borrow the 6&amp;rsquo;2 centre half. Just in case you don&amp;rsquo;t know too much about him, he&amp;rsquo;s 29 years of age, a Nigerian international and has played for a fair few clubs in his time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Beckford bid fails for the last time, Hughton will look elsewhere</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/12/if-beckford-bid-fails-for-the-last-time-hughton-will-look-elsewhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/12/if-beckford-bid-fails-for-the-last-time-hughton-will-look-elsewhere/</guid>
      <description>Chris Hughton has today again reiterated his stance on Jermaine Beckford&amp;rsquo;s transfer scenario. Hughton has made it no secret that he&amp;rsquo;s after the 6&amp;rsquo;2 striker but insists that he&amp;rsquo;ll neither heighten his price, or be forced to do so. It&amp;rsquo;s believed that Newcastle have issued Leeds with an ultimatum, a bid of just about £2m, a take it or leave it offer for the Elland Road outfit. There&amp;rsquo;s no doubt that Beckford wants to join Newcastle and has even issued a transfer request to speed up his move away from Leeds if possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leeds won’t accept anything less than £2m for Jermaine Beckford</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/11/leeds-wont-accept-anything-less-than-2m-for-jermaine-beckford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 15:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/11/leeds-wont-accept-anything-less-than-2m-for-jermaine-beckford/</guid>
      <description>The speculation goes on. Just as it seemed Jermaine Beckford was joining Newcastle United this January, the tale has taken another twist. It&amp;rsquo;s now reported that Sunderland and Wolves have both joined the race to sign the FA Cup hero as Leeds United stall over Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s latest bid. Sources suggested that Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s latest bid was indeed rejected but no one knows for sure. Apparently The Elland Road outfit are holding out for £2m for Beckford but most of the teams know that his contract expires in only a few months time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilgallon could still arrive at Newcastle as Beckford transfer scenario lingers on</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/08/kilgallon-could-still-arrive-at-newcastle-as-beckford-transfer-scenario-lingers-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/08/kilgallon-could-still-arrive-at-newcastle-as-beckford-transfer-scenario-lingers-on/</guid>
      <description>Kilgallon - Newcastle still reportedly in the hunt despite statement Although Matthew Kilgallon indicated that he will stay on at Sheffield United for the remainder of the season, there are still rumours out there that he could well still arrive at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park. As he&amp;rsquo;s in his last few months of his contract at Bramall Lane, Kilgallon will seek a move in the summer for free, and to a Premier League club if he can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beckford – Confirms he’s joining Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/07/beckford-confirms-hes-joining-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 19:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/07/beckford-confirms-hes-joining-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Beckford - Seems pretty happy about joining Newcastle eh? News has just broke that Jermaine Beckford is joining Newcastle United. In possibly the shortest interview I&amp;rsquo;ve even read, Beckford simply said he would be joining Newcastle United and nothing else. It was a Tyne Time viewer who spotted this a few minutes ago and I in return am writing about what should be our first signing of the January transfer window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beckford hands in transfer request as £2m Toon move edges closer</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/06/beckford-hands-in-transfer-request-as-2m-toon-move-edges-closer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 21:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/06/beckford-hands-in-transfer-request-as-2m-toon-move-edges-closer/</guid>
      <description>Beckford - Clearly wants a move this January transfer window I think the next day or two will bring down the curtains on what has been a 2 year old love affair between Newcastle United and Jermaine Beckford. The Keegan, Kinnear, Shearer and now Hughton target has today handed a transfer request to the Elland Road hierarchy underlining his ambitions to leave Leeds United. After scoring the winner at Old Trafford amongst 19 other goals this year, Chris Hughton is clearly in the hunt for the 6&amp;rsquo;2 striker and I&amp;rsquo;d expect a move to materialize within the next 48 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jermaine Beckford isn’t worth £3m this January</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/05/jermaine-beckford-isnt-worth-3m-this-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 11:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/05/jermaine-beckford-isnt-worth-3m-this-january/</guid>
      <description>Beckford - Not worth more than £2.5m this January transfer window Fair enough, he scored the winner against Manchester United in the FA Cup a few days ago, granted he&amp;rsquo;s got 20 goals for Leeds United already and we&amp;rsquo;re just leaving Christmas but Jermaine Beckford isn&amp;rsquo;t worth the £3m Leeds United are reportedly looking for. With Newcastle expected to sign Beckford soon after submitting another, written transfer bid, it would be a risky transfer if we ssplashed out near four million pounds on a League 1 striker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leeds United reportedly holding out for £3m for Beckford</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/04/leeds-united-reportedly-holding-out-for-3m-for-beckford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 16:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/04/leeds-united-reportedly-holding-out-for-3m-for-beckford/</guid>
      <description>### Beckford - Leeds want £3m for FA Cup hero
If reports are to be believed, Leeds United are holding out for £3m for their FA Cup hero, Jermaine Beckford. The striker who scored the winning goal in Old Trafford yesterday to knock Manchester United out of the FA Cup, is highly touted to join us this January. However, the goalposts have moved pricewise, as you would have expected. Our original bid of £1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beckford does the business at Old Trafford as Toon move looms</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/03/beckford-does-the-business-at-old-trafford-as-toon-move-looms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/03/beckford-does-the-business-at-old-trafford-as-toon-move-looms/</guid>
      <description>### Beckford - Scored his 20th of the season to knock United out of the FA Cup
I think most of us were delighted in some way to see Jermaine Beckford and Leeds United, knock Manchester United out of the FA Cup, at just the 3rd round. Beckford who you&amp;rsquo;ll have probably heard, unless you&amp;rsquo;ve been under a stone for the last month, is being strongly linked with a move to Newcastle and within the next few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It seems as if Kilgallon &amp; Beckford are close to signing for Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/01/it-seems-as-if-kilgallon-beckford-are-close-to-signing-for-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 17:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/01/it-seems-as-if-kilgallon-beckford-are-close-to-signing-for-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>### Targets - Hughton is confident they&amp;rsquo;ll arrive
According to surfacing reports and the many of them, Jermaine Beckford and Matthew Kilgallon will be signing for Newcastle United in the January transfer window. Both &amp;lsquo;The Killer&amp;rsquo; and Beckford have been lined with possible moves to Newcastle, since the start of 2009 but no move materialized for either of them. Kilgallon, as well as Beckford are in the final months of their respective contracts and Chris Hughton is hoping to get a bargain on both of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signing a League 1 striker with Premier League ambitions in mind – A good idea?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/29/signing-a-league-1-striker-with-premier-league-ambitions-in-mind-a-good-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 21:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/29/signing-a-league-1-striker-with-premier-league-ambitions-in-mind-a-good-idea/</guid>
      <description>### Beckford - Is he really worth the hassle of luring to Toon?
It&amp;rsquo;s no lie to say that Jermaine Beckford is probably the best striker in League 1 albeit closely followed by Grant Holt of Norwich City. Racking up 16 goals to date, Beckford of course is attracting interest from beyond League 1 and our very own Newcastle United have been linked many a time with the 6&amp;rsquo;2 London born striker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Jermaine Beckford really worth £5m?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/09/is-jermaine-beckford-really-worth-5m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 20:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/09/is-jermaine-beckford-really-worth-5m/</guid>
      <description>With 11 goals to his name for Leeds United already, Jermaine Beckford is taking League 1 by storm so far. As Leeds look set to make it back to the Championship, although in early stages, another team that is expected to pop back up a division is us, Newcastle United. Beckford has been linked to Newcastle now on many occasions and especially in the summer when his agent said he would indeed be interested in moving clubs, and playing on a bigger stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 players Newcastle United should buy</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/13/5-players-newcastle-united-should-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 15:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/13/5-players-newcastle-united-should-buy/</guid>
      <description>Shearer - Appoint him now regardless of ownership As the saga continues were all getting sick of the same old news, the sale will be completed here there and everywhere. I&amp;rsquo;m taking my mind off the sale today and put together a list of players Newcastle United should sign as they prepare for their first Coca Cola Championship campaign. The main thing I can&amp;rsquo;t understand and you probably can&amp;rsquo;t either, is why Shearer hasn&amp;rsquo;t been appointed manager as the takeover talks continue?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jermaine Beckford ‘waiting’ for Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/09/jermaine-beckford-waiting-for-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 12:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/09/jermaine-beckford-waiting-for-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a pleasant surprise to see players wanting to join out club at this time, even though we&amp;rsquo;re in the worst possible scenario, no owner, no manager and players that want to leave. On the other hand there&amp;rsquo;s on man that wants to come and that&amp;rsquo;s Jermaine Beckford from Leeds United. Jermaine is quite a decent striker and stands at over 6ft. Leeds have transfer listed him and he wants to leave.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>