<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alan Shearer on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/alan-shearer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alan Shearer on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 18:14:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/alan-shearer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This day 3 years ago – A historic Newcastle United moment</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/24/this-day-3-years-ago-a-historic-newcastle-united-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 18:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/24/this-day-3-years-ago-a-historic-newcastle-united-moment/</guid>
      <description>#### Taylor - One of few players that day to show a genuine despair at relegation
Every Newcastle United fan will remember where they were when the final whistle sounded round Villa Park on the 24th of May, 2009. An own goal from Damien Duff, was the only thing that separated Newcastle United from Premier League survival and relegation to the Championship. Gareth Barry took a shot that was heading well off target and it hit Duff on the way only to evade Steve Harper and pop into the bottom corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United need to buy this Summer if we want to stay up</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</guid>
      <description>Owen - We don&amp;rsquo;t want too many signings similar to this guy anytime soon The day we splashed a record-breaking £15m to bring Alan Shearer to Newcastle from Premier League winning Blackburn Rovers, the footballing world came to a standstill and admired the Tyneside team for their courage in doing so, or at least we like to think they did! What a signing Alan Shearer turned about to be though, a true predator in front of goal and one of the best English strikers ever, if not the.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United needs serious sorting out</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/21/newcastle-united-needs-serious-sorting-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 15:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/21/newcastle-united-needs-serious-sorting-out/</guid>
      <description>NUFC - Second loss in a row in the second tier of English football Yesterday Newcastle slumped to their second successive defeat on the road in the Coca Cola Championship. After going behind from some poor defending, we managed to equalise through Kevin Nolan, and it was a very good goal indeed, Premier League quality to be fair. However, we dropped out of the game again and conceded again with ten minutes remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor could well have played his last game for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad when it has come to this, a Newcastle United player, brought through the ranks, and having becoming a Newcastle United first team member, looking for the exit door at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. Sky Sports News (who else?) are reporting that the local lad, could be set for a move to David Moyes&amp;rsquo;s Everton side who are fighting a losing battle with their own English centre back, Joleon Lescott. If this news is true, which we hope it&amp;rsquo;s not, then it&amp;rsquo;ll really put gas to the fire and the frustration will be taken out on Mike Ashley more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Hughton more than likely staying as manager for West Brom game</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 13:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/chris-hughton-more-than-likely-staying-as-manager-for-west-brom-game/</guid>
      <description>It seems that the hierarchy have learned nowt over the last season and continue to play their own game, which is affecting all of us. Mike Ashley doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he&amp;rsquo;s doing sadly enough and his puppets aren&amp;rsquo;t much better. Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;m being a little too harsh on them, after all Ashley did invest a whole lot of money into Newcastle United with very little, no, return. You would have to feel a little sympathy for him in that sense but he made no steps whatsoever to make amends and sort the club and effectively brought the club to it&amp;rsquo;s knees, meaning here we are in the Coca Cola Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United fans still loyal as ever</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/newcastle-united-fans-still-loyal-as-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/22/newcastle-united-fans-still-loyal-as-ever/</guid>
      <description>Fans - Where else would you find such fans? We may have suffered the worst in relegation but it could be a mixed blessing for the Toon faithful. We no longer will be paying high earners for sitting on the benches and won&amp;rsquo;t going through managers as if they were skittles - right? We certainly hope things will change but so far the only thing good at the club, are the fans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>