<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mike Williamson on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/mike-williamson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mike Williamson on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 17:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/mike-williamson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Midterm Report: The rise of Mike Williamson</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/21/midterm-report-the-rise-of-mike-williamson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 17:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/21/midterm-report-the-rise-of-mike-williamson/</guid>
      <description>Revert your thoughts to this time last year. Newcastle United fans across the world grimaced when the ball went anywhere near Mike Williamson. The centre-back portrayed a lumbering figure, bereft of confidence and limited in ability. I personally remember worrying about Loic Rémy facing Williamson in our crucial fixture against Queens Park Rangers towards the end of last season which secured our Premier League safety. Rémy had already struck away a penalty earlier in the game and Newcastle had regressed into their defensive shape which almost cost the club its league status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coloccini has helped Mike Williamson settle on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/04/coloccini-has-helped-mike-williamson-settle-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/04/coloccini-has-helped-mike-williamson-settle-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Coloccini - Mike Williamson grateful of the Argentine&amp;rsquo;s help and experience It&amp;rsquo;s true to say Fabricio Coloccini has been a rock at the central of defence this season at Newcastle United and really, he&amp;rsquo;d want to be putting in a good shift after setting us back £10.3m in the &amp;lsquo;Keegan Summer&amp;rsquo;. Another centre-back who arrived on Tyneside this January by the name of Mike Williamson from troubled Portsmouth has also been sturdy at the heart of our defence, a position where we&amp;rsquo;ve lacked real quality throughout the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nile nets winner as the new-boys make their debuts on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Ranger - Netted again tonight as we saw Routledge &amp;amp; Williamson in action Tonights affair was a game we needed all three points from and the lads duly delivered the goods. In what was a Crystal Palace team without one of their main men in Victor Moses saw them concede within twenty minutes, a Shaun Derry O.G. In fairness, it seems as if Palace gave it a real go and could well have got something out of the game on another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portsmouth or Newcastle need to fork out an extra £1.2m or Williamson won’t arrive on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/22/portsmouth-or-newcastle-need-to-fork-out-an-extra-1-2m-or-williamson-wont-arrive-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 22:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/22/portsmouth-or-newcastle-need-to-fork-out-an-extra-1-2m-or-williamson-wont-arrive-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Pompey - A real mess at that club right now both financially and on the fields After successfully completing a medical on Tyneside, Mike Williamson was expected to secure a £1m transfer to Newcastle today. However, some late checks on the contract by Pompey have resulted in them finding a snag or a little clause that they had forgot about. Sky Sports (who else?) reported that the deal had indeed been stalled after the club found the clause and they want Newcastle United to pay it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>