<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marlon Harewood on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/marlon-harewood/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marlon Harewood on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 18:54:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/marlon-harewood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harewood &amp; Ameobi send Middlesbrough marching</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/20/harewood-ameobi-send-middlesbrough-marching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 18:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/20/harewood-ameobi-send-middlesbrough-marching/</guid>
      <description>Another three points and another win against Middlesbrough. Well done Chris Hughton and well done the lads. In rather chilly conditions in St.James&amp;rsquo; Park, Marlon Harewood &amp;amp; Shola Ameobi both netted to ensure that we will have a happy Christmas period with a ten point gap between ourselves and West Bromich Albion. Although the game started quite slowly and perhaps Boro having the better spell of possession, it was Marlon Harewood who latched on to a Shola Ameobi knock-down to slide the ball home and bring his tally to 5 this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Marlon a chance to be a Magpie</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/27/give-marlon-a-chance-to-be-a-magpie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/27/give-marlon-a-chance-to-be-a-magpie/</guid>
      <description>### Harewood - Needs to be give time to adjust
Marlon Harewood&amp;rsquo;s great start in a Newcastle United shirt by scoring the equaliser against QPR seems like a distant memory now as the physical forward is beginning to irritate the Toon faithful. In the game against Doncaster Marlon didn&amp;rsquo;t play a blinder by any means but labelling him as a &amp;lsquo;donkey&amp;rsquo; is really justified as of yet. Arriving from Aston Villa on loan, the forward was brought here to score goals but it looks as if they&amp;rsquo;ll be few and far between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harewood will do a good job at Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/01/harewood-will-do-a-good-job-at-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 15:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/01/harewood-will-do-a-good-job-at-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>If it&amp;rsquo;s not very common at Newcastle, that players score on their home debut but Marlon Harewood did just that against Queens Park Rangers last night. Although we rued the chance to go five points clear at the top, the main thing is, the lads got something out of the game. It was a game that you just thought it was going to one of those nights. However, to say we were lucky isn&amp;rsquo;t even a joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Michael to Marlon – Strikers void filled</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/27/from-michael-to-marlon-strikers-void-filled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 13:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/27/from-michael-to-marlon-strikers-void-filled/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago we had Michael Owen, one of the worlds most famous footballer, lining out in the Black and White of Newcastle United but after a rather dismal turn in events (relegation) Owen left, for the better we think. Yesterday the vacant #10 jersey was sported by Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s new signing, Marlon Harewood, on loan from Aston Villa. It quite an interesting turn around at Newcastle, as it seems Chris has filled the vacant positions, left behind by high paid &amp;lsquo;stars&amp;rsquo;, with determined players who want the very best for Newcastle United and their mighty fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marlon Harewood to make Magpies loan move</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/21/marlon-harewood-to-make-magpies-loan-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 16:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/21/marlon-harewood-to-make-magpies-loan-move/</guid>
      <description>Marlon Harewood&amp;rsquo;s agent today confirmed that the Villa striker was very close to a loan move to Newcastle. The Villa forward, who has been out of action for a considerable amount of time now was being tracked by Chris Hughton since August and after Harewood overcame his injury, Hughton was once again in for his services. As you all know, Harewood is quite a beast or physical player on the ball, he also has the ability to score quite a few goals and we&amp;rsquo;d expect a fair share of them, in his stunt on Tyneside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harewood and Seip unlikely to arrive</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/07/harewood-and-seip-unlikely-to-arrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 14:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/07/harewood-and-seip-unlikely-to-arrive/</guid>
      <description>### Harewood - Out injured again
Chris Hughton today denied the rumours that he is set to capture Marcel Seip from Plymouth Argyle. The defender, who was reported to have had a bust up with manager Paul Sturrock was rumoured to have been on his way to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park within the next couple of days but today Chris refuted those reports. However one man that he took no time in confirming his interest in, was Marlon Harewood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harewood signing would add a new dimension</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/03/harewood-signing-would-add-a-new-dimension/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 17:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/03/harewood-signing-would-add-a-new-dimension/</guid>
      <description>### Harewood - Reportedly joining Newcastle next week
Well, I&amp;rsquo;m back from holidays in the Algarve, albeit a little sunburnt but the good news is, Newcastle United are top of the Coca Cola Championship with Chris Hughton doing a great job. A rather great goal from &amp;lsquo;Dan the man Guthrie&amp;rsquo; saw us through Leicester with Nile Ranger showing signs of a very good future striker. Steve Howard caused a few problems to our defence but Jose Enrique, Steven Taylor and co.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>