<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nile Ranger on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/nile-ranger/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nile Ranger on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 18:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/nile-ranger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One striker likely to leave St.James’ Park this summer</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/22/one-striker-likely-to-leave-st-james-park-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/22/one-striker-likely-to-leave-st-james-park-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>#### Ranger - Lot of raw potential but a poor attitude to accompany it
If one was to look at Nile Ranger&amp;rsquo;s CV, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make for bad reading at all. Once of Southampton, he featured in Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s promotion to the Premier League, and this year contributed to Sheffield Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s return to the Championship. Unfortunately he has the attitude of a gangster and is still surrounded by people he could do without.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s hope Nile Ranger doesn’t ruin his future at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/08/lets-hope-nile-ranger-doesnt-ruin-his-future-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/08/lets-hope-nile-ranger-doesnt-ruin-his-future-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Any time he has come on the pitch he has upped the tempo. His strength, height, ability in the air and his quick feet have caused problems for Liverpool, Arsenal, Chelsea and many other teams this season. He is 19 years of age, 6 feet 2 inches in height and has the potential to a Premier League class striker if not more. Nile Ranger&amp;rsquo;s attitude however is something that has caused problems in the past and continues to do so on a smaller level in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle cruise by Carlisle as Best &amp; Vuckic grab first goals for club</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/17/newcastle-cruise-by-carlisle-as-best-vuckic-grab-first-goals-for-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 21:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/17/newcastle-cruise-by-carlisle-as-best-vuckic-grab-first-goals-for-club/</guid>
      <description>Vuckic - Delighted after scoring his first goal for Newcastle United Newcastle kicked off their first preparation for the upcoming Premier League campaign by defeating Carlisle by three goals, with Leon Best, Haris Vuckic and Nile Ranger all hitting the back of the net. I&amp;rsquo;ve yet to see the goals but they were meant to be nice finishes from all three. Whilst seeing off The Cumbrians, the Toon lads sported the new Newcastle United away strip, and it&amp;rsquo;s a very nice jersey to say the least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nile nets winner as the new-boys make their debuts on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Ranger - Netted again tonight as we saw Routledge &amp;amp; Williamson in action Tonights affair was a game we needed all three points from and the lads duly delivered the goods. In what was a Crystal Palace team without one of their main men in Victor Moses saw them concede within twenty minutes, a Shaun Derry O.G. In fairness, it seems as if Palace gave it a real go and could well have got something out of the game on another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danger Ranger bags first of many or so we hope</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/10/danger-ranger-bags-first-of-many-or-so-we-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 17:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/10/danger-ranger-bags-first-of-many-or-so-we-hope/</guid>
      <description>In a good display from Newcastle United last night, Nile Ranger at long last got his first senior goal for the Toon Army and the travelling fans. The icing on the cake came with only a few minutes remaining, Enrique crossing for his second assist of the evening before Ranger, between two defenders prodded it home. Hopefully this goal, which has been a long time coming, will spur on a huge goal fest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shola Ameobi will be sorely missed – first time we’ve heard that</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/04/shola-ameobi-will-be-sorely-missed-first-time-weve-heard-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 17:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/04/shola-ameobi-will-be-sorely-missed-first-time-weve-heard-that/</guid>
      <description>Who would&amp;rsquo;ve thought or indeed would&amp;rsquo;ve said, a year ago, that Shola Ameobi would be a huge loss to Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s strike force? Ameobi, who is Nigerian by birth is starting to show, this season at least, some of the quality the famous Nigerian strikers had. Bagging a hattrick against Reading, scoring the winner v Sheffield Wednesday and adding to his tally in the Carling Cup vs Huddersfield, Shola has established himself as a real threat to Championship defences this season.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>