<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dan Gosling on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/dan-gosling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dan Gosling on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 15:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/dan-gosling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Gosling asked to play to Alan Pardew’s tune</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/29/dan-gosling-asked-play-alan-pardews-tune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/29/dan-gosling-asked-play-alan-pardews-tune/</guid>
      <description>If you had told any Newcastle United fan in September that come the end of the month of April, 2014, Yohan Cabaye would be plying his football in France, and Dan Gosling would be his replacement in midfield, then I think there would be a few raised eyebrows. Unfortunately that is exactly how things have panned out at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park. Mr. Gosling has made a dramatic return to the first team and on Monday night he started yet again in a midfield that might have as well stayed back on Tyneside as Arsenal romped to an easy three nil victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Newcastle United midfielder faces an uncertain future</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/03/24/this-newcastle-united-midfielder-faces-an-uncertain-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 14:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/03/24/this-newcastle-united-midfielder-faces-an-uncertain-future/</guid>
      <description>I remember the day Dan Gosling arrived at Newcastle United. We had managed to secure him on a free transfer from Everton after the Merseyside outfit failed to negotiate a new contract. Gosling arrived with potential, a decent passing range and even the odd goal - who can forget his 120th minute winner against Liverpool in the cup only a few years ago?! However since his arrival, injuries have hampered every opportunity he managed to get.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does this midfielder have a future at Newcastle United?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/09/does-this-midfielder-have-a-future-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 19:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/09/does-this-midfielder-have-a-future-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Gosling - Can he challenge Cabaye or even Guthrie for a first team position? When Newcastle United announced the signing of Dan Gosling I must admit that I was quite excited, and thought we have pulled of a sort of coup. Not that my opinion has changed or anything, but it seems as if Gosling might have an extremely hard time trying to crack the midfield four that currently line out for Newcastle United.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Window Closed – Hughton gets the job done for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>St.James&amp;rsquo; - Will be graced by Hatem Ben Arfa &amp;amp; Cheick Tioté against Blackpool Five players signed, and a job well done by Chris Hughton and co. James Perch, Dan Gosling, Sol Campbell, Cheick Tioté &amp;amp; Hatem Ben Arfa all signed for Newcastle United,a nd four of those on a permanent basis. The pick of the bunch really is a coin toss between Dan Gosling and Hatem Ben Arfa, but the fact Ben Arfa is fit and ready to go unlike his counterpart, perhaps shades it for the Frenchman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Gosling on a free – Something Dennis Wise wouldn’t have managed</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/23/dan-gosling-on-a-free-something-dennis-wise-wouldnt-have-managed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 14:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/23/dan-gosling-on-a-free-something-dennis-wise-wouldnt-have-managed/</guid>
      <description>The dislike of Dennis Wise for many Newcastle United fans stems from Kevin Keegan&amp;rsquo;s departure, James Milner&amp;rsquo;s move to Aston Villa, the signing of the Uruguayan Gonzalez, Xisco&amp;rsquo;s arrival on Tyneside and many other incidents at the club. He did spot Bassong and a few other promising young players but will never be warmly welcomed back to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park if he arrives some time in the future. we passed down the chance to sign Bastian Schweinsteiger who reportedly was keen for a switch to Newcastle United, Wise again having something to do with this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Gosling to sign for the Toon soon?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/13/dan-gosling-to-sign-for-the-toon-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 22:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/07/13/dan-gosling-to-sign-for-the-toon-soon/</guid>
      <description>Gosling - Newcastle await an Evertonian appeal about the players exit We feared the worst when we were told that very little, if no money would be spent on Tyneside this summer to boost the Coca Cola Championship winning squad. However, nearly a fortnight into the transfer window, we&amp;rsquo;ve one player already signed for a rumoured fee of £1.5 - 2m and another promising youngster by the name of Dan Gosling seemingly set to wear the Black and White jersey of Newcastle United this season.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>