<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stephen Ireland on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/stephen-ireland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stephen Ireland on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 10:49:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/stephen-ireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you want Stephen Ireland back at Newcastle United permanently?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/26/would-you-take-stephen-ireland-back-to-st-james-park-for-next-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 10:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/26/would-you-take-stephen-ireland-back-to-st-james-park-for-next-season/</guid>
      <description>Ireland - Has raw talent but can he regain old form at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park? There are emerging reports that Alan Pardew may well be interested in bringing Stephen Ireland back to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park on a permanent basis this summer. The Irishman, who had an injury plagued loan spell with Newcastle never really got going and played a mere 2 times for the club: both as substitute appearances. I think we all remember what a player this guy was only a couple of years ago; indeed he was awarded the Player Of the Year award at Eastlands for his fantastic endeavours throughout the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew can help Stephen Ireland rediscover his top form at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/04/alan-pardew-can-help-stephen-ireland-rediscover-his-top-form-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 22:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/04/alan-pardew-can-help-stephen-ireland-rediscover-his-top-form-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>#### Ireland - Can be a quality player under Alan Pardew at Newcastle United
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t that long ago when the we all watched Stephen Ireland become Manchester City&amp;rsquo;s Player Of The Season - less than two years ago in fact. The Cork-born midfielder excelled under Mark Hughes whilst Manchester City manager but since then the big spending Italian Roberto Mancini took the reigns and made it clear very quickly that he didn&amp;rsquo;t see a future for Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>