<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cheick Tioté on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/cheick-tiot%C3%A9/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cheick Tioté on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 18:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/cheick-tiot%C3%A9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheick Tioté wants out as Pardew limps on</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/10/01/cheick-tiote-wants-out-as-pardew-limps-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 18:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/10/01/cheick-tiote-wants-out-as-pardew-limps-on/</guid>
      <description>When Peter Crouch easily rose above captain Fabricio Coloccini to nod home what turned out to be Stoke City&amp;rsquo;s winner, it was all too familiar for Newcastle United fans. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t despair, no head in hands, no tears. A sense of acceptance swept through a wet Brittania Stadium. Then, as per the last few games, chants and banners dominated the TV screens as the majority of Newcastle supporters voiced their anger, and demands to the away dugout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are we really that worried about losing Cheik Tioté this summer?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/25/are-we-really-that-worried-about-losing-cheik-tiote-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 15:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/25/are-we-really-that-worried-about-losing-cheik-tiote-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>Tioté - Still has a huge amount to learn about the Premier League Like any other year, it comes as no surprise to us that the media are trying to cause unrest at Newcastle United, particularly the southern crew. Constantly our players are linked with moves away from St.James&amp;rsquo; Park, and it has come to a stage where Alan Pardew even admits that there is nothing he can do if bigger clubs come calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United have a stronger midfield than their opponents tonight</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/04/19/newcastle-united-have-a-stronger-midfield-than-their-opponents-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/04/19/newcastle-united-have-a-stronger-midfield-than-their-opponents-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Tioté - Will be crucial tonight if he can keep his discipline for the 90 minutes Tonight&amp;rsquo;s game is a game people have relished for many many years. Newcastle United and Manchester United locking horns always seems like quite a big game, a game between two big sides when reality there is one far superior side lining out on most occasions and it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been us for quite a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheik Tioté reveals he rejected move to Chelsea in January window</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/27/cheik-tiote-reveals-he-rejected-move-to-chelsea-in-january-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 16:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/27/cheik-tiote-reveals-he-rejected-move-to-chelsea-in-january-window/</guid>
      <description>Tioté - Opted to stay at Newcastle United in January despite Chelsea interest In an interview with a Sunday tabloid Cheick Tioté revealed why he opted to stay at Newcastle United and sign a 6.5 year long deal.
Tioté who we know already is one of Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s best players this season signed from FC Twente for a small fee of £3.5m, compared to what he is worth at this moment in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Cheik Tiote’s new 6½ year deal fails to excite</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/26/why-cheik-tiotes-new-6-year-deal-fails-to-excite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 14:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/26/why-cheik-tiotes-new-6-year-deal-fails-to-excite/</guid>
      <description>One man who won&amp;rsquo;t be short for money for years to come is our very own Cheik Tiote, after signing a new six and a half year deal with Newcastle United. Tioté, who had been linked with moves to Chelsea, Arsenal and even Manchester United put pen to paper on a rather outrageous deal in all honesty. It is one of the longest contracts I have ever heard of in football and if we&amp;rsquo;re to be realistic here, he will not see out those years at the Toon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United have the quality to beat Birmingham tonight</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/15/newcastle-united-have-the-quality-to-beat-birmingham-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 12:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/15/newcastle-united-have-the-quality-to-beat-birmingham-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Tioté - Very important again tonight but needs to watch his discipline All the talk ahead of tonight&amp;rsquo;s match between Birmingham City and Newcastle United is the about the upcoming battle between Nikola Žigic and our very own Mike Williamson. Žigic is 6&amp;rsquo;8 whilst Mike stands at a modest 6&amp;rsquo;4. There&amp;rsquo;s little doubt that Birmingham will try pick out their big man on every occasion tonight and it will be up to us to stop him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirited Newcastle United performance undone by misfortune and Tevez</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/26/spirited-newcastle-united-performance-undone-by-misfortune-and-tevez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2010 22:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/26/spirited-newcastle-united-performance-undone-by-misfortune-and-tevez/</guid>
      <description>#### Carroll - Scored yet again today and continues to be linked with Toon exit
Frustrating isn&amp;rsquo;t the word. When Fabricio Coloccini put the ball into his own net in the last ten minutes of the game, my heart sank and I nearly dropped my turkey sandwich. We had dominated the second half, every ball was ours, Carroll won every header, Cheik Tiote cleaned up every spill in centre midfield and Jose Enrique &amp;amp; Jonas Gutierrez swept up everything on the leftside of the pitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Window Closed – Hughton gets the job done for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/31/transfer-window-closed-hughton-gets-the-job-done-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>St.James&amp;rsquo; - Will be graced by Hatem Ben Arfa &amp;amp; Cheick Tioté against Blackpool Five players signed, and a job well done by Chris Hughton and co. James Perch, Dan Gosling, Sol Campbell, Cheick Tioté &amp;amp; Hatem Ben Arfa all signed for Newcastle United,a nd four of those on a permanent basis. The pick of the bunch really is a coin toss between Dan Gosling and Hatem Ben Arfa, but the fact Ben Arfa is fit and ready to go unlike his counterpart, perhaps shades it for the Frenchman.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>