<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peter Lovenkrands on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/peter-lovenkrands/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Peter Lovenkrands on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 00:34:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/peter-lovenkrands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovenkrands a big doubt for Bristol City clash</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/20/lovenkrands-a-big-doubt-for-bristol-city-clash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 00:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/20/lovenkrands-a-big-doubt-for-bristol-city-clash/</guid>
      <description>### Lovenkrands - Ankle injury could force the Dane out of Ashton Gate clash
The free-scoring Peter Lovenkrands is 50-50 to make Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s away trip to Bristol tomorrow after suffering a light ankle injury in Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s 3-0 win over Scunthorpe. The Dane who has been banging them in up-front alongside Andy Carroll has hit 11 goals in his last 12 appearances, a record any striker would be proud of. However, the Dane is also a doubt for tomorrows clash against Bristol City which will prove a very tough task too, especially at Ashton Gate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Lovenkrands has done a great job on Tyneside since his permanent move to Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/08/peter-lovenkrands-has-done-a-great-job-on-tyneside-since-his-permanent-move-to-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 22:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/08/peter-lovenkrands-has-done-a-great-job-on-tyneside-since-his-permanent-move-to-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>When Newcastle United in January 2009 confirmed that Peter Lovenkrands would indeed be staying until the end of the season under Joe Kinnear, there were a lot of unhappy Ton fans out there. In a dismal January transfer window which in a way sent us down from the Premier League, Lovenkrands was 1 of a mere 3 faces that arrived on a relegation threatened club at the time . He tried his best at Newcastle and score some important goals, like his goal away at West Brom and indeed sealing all 3 points in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovenkrands &amp; Carroll score twice as Cardiff capitulate</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/05/lovenkrands-carroll-score-twice-as-cardiff-capitulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 22:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/05/lovenkrands-carroll-score-twice-as-cardiff-capitulate/</guid>
      <description>Lovenkrands - Came off the bench to score twice including a beauty on his left First of all, I was very wrong in my predictions about tonights game. Very wrong indeed. In what was a totally one sided affair from the very first whistle, Newcastle United fired 5 goals past Dave Jones side. An early opener from Andy Carroll followed by an unfortunate turn of events which saw Gyepes put the ball into his own net, with Andy Carroll again to thank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Brom probably deserved all 3 points at Newcastle last night</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/19/west-brom-probably-deserved-all-3-points-at-newcastle-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 16:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/19/west-brom-probably-deserved-all-3-points-at-newcastle-last-night/</guid>
      <description>How suiting it was that Peter Lovenkrands had the last say in St.James&amp;rsquo; Park last night in what was a very exciting affair. Tyne Time predicted a 2-0 scoreline in Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s favour and we were wrong, however I did guarantee an even encounter, one which if you ask me, we didn&amp;rsquo;t deserve to win. The opening minutes saw West Brom throw the kitchen sink at Newcastle and they got their due reward when Olsson delicately flicked Dorran&amp;rsquo;s ball beyond the despairing Steve Harper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovenkrands returns to Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/01/lovenkrands-returns-to-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 16:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/01/lovenkrands-returns-to-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>### Lovenkrands - Welcomed back with open arms
On a deadline day which hasn&amp;rsquo;t produced anything special besides a lot of rumours, Newcastle United have completed the signing(re) of Peter Lovenkrands. The Dane who departed from Newcastle are receiving a letter from the hierarchy saying his services were no longer needed, has signed for Chris Hughton and it&amp;rsquo;s a very good signing for our threadbare Championship squad indeed.
More to follow on any breaking transfer news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter would løve to play for Newcastle United again</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/24/peter-would-love-to-play-for-newcastle-united-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 14:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/24/peter-would-love-to-play-for-newcastle-united-again/</guid>
      <description>Remember him? Peter Lovenkrands? Well, he used to play for us last season if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know and since then he has been relieved of his contract at Newcastle United, looking to ply his trade elsewhere. I think most people will remember him, he fought for the magpies in every game, and scored three goals in his stint here as well. Signed by Joe Kinnear on a free from Schalke, Lovenkrands most memorable Newcastle moment would have been scoring the third goal against Middlesbrough which indeed proved to be Newcastle]s&amp;rsquo;s last top flight goal that season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovenkrands open to rejoining Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/18/lovenkrands-open-to-rejoining-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 14:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/18/lovenkrands-open-to-rejoining-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Peter Lovenkrands may well come back to Newcastle United on a permanent basis it has been revealed. The Dane who signed for Newcastle on a free following his departure from Schalke saw Joe Kinnear snap him up on a contract until the end of the season however with the constant uncertainty and no manager, Lovekrands was released on a free after he received a letter from Newcastle saying that he wasn&amp;rsquo;t needed any more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>