<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Demba Ba on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/demba-ba/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Demba Ba on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 19:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/demba-ba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Demba Ba debacle blown out of proportion – he’s happy at NUFC</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/09/21/demba-ba-debacle-blown-out-of-proportion-hes-happy-at-nufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/09/21/demba-ba-debacle-blown-out-of-proportion-hes-happy-at-nufc/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s usually no better feeling in football than scoring in the dying seconds to achieve a result that looked virtually impossible. When Victor Anichebe powered home Everton&amp;rsquo;s second goal, it looked as if they were on course to take a deserved three points on an emotional night at Goodison. Unfortunately for Moyes&amp;rsquo; men, they hadn&amp;rsquo;t read the script. The other substitute of the night, Demba Ba, wasn&amp;rsquo;t finished just and thanks to a chest-on from Shola Ameobi - the Senegalese man prodded home a priceless equaliser to make it 2-2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is keeping Ba happy hindering Cissé’s performances?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/09/12/is-keeping-ba-happy-hindering-cisses-performances/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 16:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/09/12/is-keeping-ba-happy-hindering-cisses-performances/</guid>
      <description>Cissé - All eyes on Papiss after a phenomenal first half season in the EPL No one could quite believe their eyes from January onwards last season as Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s latest addition - Papiss Cissé - began scoring the most ridiculous of goals the Premier League is likely to see for some time. He notched up double figures in Black and White despite only arriving at the end of the season and almost all his goals oozed utter class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United unwilling to offer Demba Ba new deal – rightly so</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/24/newcastle-united-unwilling-to-offer-demba-ba-new-deal-rightly-so/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 17:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/24/newcastle-united-unwilling-to-offer-demba-ba-new-deal-rightly-so/</guid>
      <description>#### Ba - Could be eyeing up a move away from St.James&amp;rsquo; Park
Demba Ba arrived at Newcastle on a free transfer just less than a year ago, after impressing during a short stint at relegated West Ham. He scored goals as soon as he touched down in London, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t save Avram Grant&amp;rsquo;s Hammers from going down. A clause in his contract confirmed that he would be able to leave Upton Park on a free transfer should he endure relegation, and that&amp;rsquo;s when NUFC moved in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demba Ba will keep 50% of transfer fee received should he leave Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/19/demba-ba-will-keep-50-of-transfer-fee-received-should-he-leave-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 13:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/19/demba-ba-will-keep-50-of-transfer-fee-received-should-he-leave-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Ba - Has quite a peculiar contract and a slightly worrying one for NUFC There is some pretty interesting news coming from West Ham owner David Sullivan in the past day where he opens the lid on Demba Ba&amp;rsquo;s contract. The most staggering part of the interview with Iain Dale over at WestHamTillIDie is Sullivan&amp;rsquo;s claim that Demba Ba will receive half the transfer fee for himself should the Senegalese hitman move away from St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>