<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steven Taylor on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/steven-taylor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steven Taylor on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 14:35:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/steven-taylor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United eyeing up Yanga-Mbiwa as Alan Pardew steps up defender chase</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/05/newcastle-united-eyeing-up-yanga-mbiwa-as-alan-pardew-steps-up-defender-chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 14:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/05/newcastle-united-eyeing-up-yanga-mbiwa-as-alan-pardew-steps-up-defender-chase/</guid>
      <description>Mbiwa - £5m rated defender could arrive on Tyneside in January with Maiga With Steven Taylor very unlikely to feature again in the 2011&amp;frasl;12 Premier League campaign, Alan Pardew is set to up the ante in the January transfer window and sign a replacement. Frenchman Mapou Yanga-Mbiwa had been linked with Newcastle in recent weeks, however Pardew played down any supposed interest. As you would expect, since the injury to Tayls, we are being linked with him again and it&amp;rsquo;s reported that members of our scouting team have advised Alan on the defender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tamás Kádár has a huge chance to revive his Newcastle United career</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/04/tamas-kadar-has-a-huge-chance-to-revive-his-newcastle-united-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 15:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/04/tamas-kadar-has-a-huge-chance-to-revive-his-newcastle-united-career/</guid>
      <description>#### Duo - Chance for Perch and Kádár to stake their claims in the NUFC first team
Fourteen games into the Premier League campaign and we&amp;rsquo;ve managed the same back five for all of it. A proud achievement. However, towards the very end of our encounter with Chelsea yesterday afternoon Steven Taylor happened to damage his achilles and is to undergo surgery on Monday. The inevitability about it all is that Taylor, who has been one of our best players of the season so far , will miss the remainder of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor close to signing long-term Newcastle United deal</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/02/steven-taylor-close-to-signing-long-term-newcastle-united-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/02/steven-taylor-close-to-signing-long-term-newcastle-united-deal/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people seem to have lost faith and perhaps respect for Steven Taylor over the last few months, with the debacle over where his future lay very much up in the air. We read reports of Steven wanting close to £60,000 a week if he was to sign a new deal, and this outraged some Newcastle supporters, rightly so. However, his agent, and the controversial one at that, came out and dismissed any idea of Taylor wanting those outstanding wages, and said he just wanted to play for the club he loves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor placed on transfer list by Newcastle United hierarchy</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/25/steven-taylor-placed-on-transfer-list-by-newcastle-united-hierarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/25/steven-taylor-placed-on-transfer-list-by-newcastle-united-hierarchy/</guid>
      <description>Taylor - Newcastle United have reportedly transfer listed the defender Sky Sports News have broken quite a stunning story about Steven Taylor today, indeed claiming that Newcastle United have placed him on the transfer list. Taylor, who has had trouble with contract talks for quite a while now has supposedly gone a step too far in negotiations and with his demands, and now finds himself on the &amp;lsquo;For Sale&amp;rsquo; list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy Carroll putting his career in doubt with the latest events on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/23/andy-carroll-doesnt-deserve-to-be-a-footballer-with-the-latest-events-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/23/andy-carroll-doesnt-deserve-to-be-a-footballer-with-the-latest-events-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Foolish, selfish, ridiculous, childish, stupid, outrageous and more than anything, arrogant. The Andy Carroll story. Reportedly he&amp;rsquo;s after breaking Steven Taylor&amp;rsquo;s jaw in a Sunday training session and I needn&amp;rsquo;t say anymore. Disgraceful from a Geordie born lad who was making great strides this season. Now however, his season is over as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned and he&amp;rsquo;ll be extremely lucky to remain a Newcastle United player too. This is just utterly disgraceful and nothing less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ameobi limps off as Dorran’s penalties knock Toon out of FA Cup</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/23/ameobi-limps-off-as-dorrans-penalties-knock-toon-out-of-fa-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 19:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/23/ameobi-limps-off-as-dorrans-penalties-knock-toon-out-of-fa-cup/</guid>
      <description>Dorrans - Lethal from the penalty spot today as Brom progress to the next round I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t our best performance all season today at the Hawthorns, and when Jonas Olsson was again the first scorer you knew it wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be our day. I can&amp;rsquo;t say I saw the match but updates on nufc.co.uk got me through the feisty affair. Pre-match I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too concerned if were going to be knocked out or not but of course I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have minded a victory away to one our promotion rivals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would Taylor leave Newcastle United?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/25/would-taylor-leave-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 18:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/25/would-taylor-leave-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Reports are emerging of late that David Moyes is looking yet again, at Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s prominent centre back, Steven Taylor. Moyes, who was present at the Preston North End game on Monday has been after Taylor for many a season now if reports are to believed. Now it seems, with Moyes huge injury problems (sound familiar?) is looking to bolster his squad, and especially his defence. That&amp;rsquo;s all good and well, but the real question remains, will Stevie Taylor himself leave the club, or indeed be allowed to?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United continue their winning streak</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/23/newcastle-united-continue-their-winning-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 21:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/23/newcastle-united-continue-their-winning-streak/</guid>
      <description>Quite literally my headline suggests what I&amp;rsquo;m touching on, the absurd news of Derek Llambias running across the pitch in Selhurst park, totally naked. To think Newcastle couldn&amp;rsquo;t get any more, media attention but no , we&amp;rsquo;re brought to new depths. The best part is, we won two nil, and kept our third clean sheet, meaning we go top, even with our neighbours Middlesbrough. Things have gone really well for us so far, and all we need is the sale of the club to boost the morale even higher, however, with that behaviour from our hierarchy, I think (unfortunately), they may be tempted to keep the club, and take NUFC off the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor could well have played his last game for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad when it has come to this, a Newcastle United player, brought through the ranks, and having becoming a Newcastle United first team member, looking for the exit door at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. Sky Sports News (who else?) are reporting that the local lad, could be set for a move to David Moyes&amp;rsquo;s Everton side who are fighting a losing battle with their own English centre back, Joleon Lescott. If this news is true, which we hope it&amp;rsquo;s not, then it&amp;rsquo;ll really put gas to the fire and the frustration will be taken out on Mike Ashley more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>