<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xisco on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/xisco/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Xisco on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 14:45:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/xisco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The mysterious case of NUFC’s Francisco Jiménez Tejada</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/18/the-mysterious-case-of-nufcs-francisco-jimenez-tejada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 14:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/18/the-mysterious-case-of-nufcs-francisco-jimenez-tejada/</guid>
      <description>#### Xisco - Clearly not in Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s plans for the 2012&amp;frasl;13 Premier League season
There aren&amp;rsquo;t many cases stranger than Xisco&amp;rsquo;s career at Newcastle United.
The Spanish forward signed from Deportivo, on Dennis Wise&amp;rsquo;s recommendation, for a reported fee of £5.75m in the autumn of 2008. Shortly after he signed for NUFC, our manager at the time - Kevin Keegan - resigned after another player had been brought in, without him having much of a say in the matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where does Xisco stand in the middle of all these events at Newcastle United?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/08/where-does-xisco-stand-in-the-middle-of-all-these-events-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 16:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/08/where-does-xisco-stand-in-the-middle-of-all-these-events-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Xisco - Looking for a way out of the club but hasn&amp;rsquo;t succeed in finding a suitor He was the final straw in Kevin Keegan&amp;rsquo;s last tenure at Newcastle United. A Spaniard brought in from Deportivo behind King Kev&amp;rsquo;s back, and indeed another player recruited against his wishes. Xisco knew no better though, and is probably still wondering what is going on in what has been a very turbulent 3 years on Tyneside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xisco was never given time to prove his worth on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/24/xisco-was-never-given-time-to-prove-his-worth-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/24/xisco-was-never-given-time-to-prove-his-worth-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>First of all, a huge congratulations to Newcastle United for winning the Coca Cola Championship and indeed lifting it at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park today in front of a massive 52,000 fans. The attendance puts Sunderland&amp;rsquo;s and indeed many more Premier League club&amp;rsquo;s to shame and just shows what a footballing town Newcastle Upon-Tyne really is. Before the match, Chris Hughton announced that Xisco would not be in his plans for the upcoming Premier League campaign and he indeed expects the Spaniard to move on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>