<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alan Smith on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/alan-smith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alan Smith on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 20:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/alan-smith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The last of Newcastle United’s ‘disappointing generation’ nears the door</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/20/the-last-of-newcastle-uniteds-disappointing-generation-nears-the-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 20:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/20/the-last-of-newcastle-uniteds-disappointing-generation-nears-the-door/</guid>
      <description>#### Smith - An extremely disappointing signing for NUFC to say the very least
I remember the day we signed Alan Smith quite well, the start of August 2007 - another &amp;lsquo;coup&amp;rsquo; by Allardyce, or seemingly so. He arrived for £6m, a decent fee to pay for someone who was just returning from a serious injury. Pay for it we did. After signing a 5 and a half year deal at a modest £60,000 a week, Smith has never had a grip on the first team and at the end of June he will depart Newcastle United on a free transfer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United need to buy this Summer if we want to stay up</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/15/newcastle-united-need-to-buy-this-summer-if-we-want-to-stay-up/</guid>
      <description>Owen - We don&amp;rsquo;t want too many signings similar to this guy anytime soon The day we splashed a record-breaking £15m to bring Alan Shearer to Newcastle from Premier League winning Blackburn Rovers, the footballing world came to a standstill and admired the Tyneside team for their courage in doing so, or at least we like to think they did! What a signing Alan Shearer turned about to be though, a true predator in front of goal and one of the best English strikers ever, if not the.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allardyce wants to swap Keith Andrews for Alan Smith</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/24/allardyce-wants-to-swap-keith-andrews-for-alan-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 18:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/24/allardyce-wants-to-swap-keith-andrews-for-alan-smith/</guid>
      <description>Andrews - Reportedly wanted by Chris Hughton to bolster midfield The Sunday Papers are at it again per usual. Today they again threw up some tasty yet laughable rumours which you love to hate. The latest, is that Chris Hughton is looking to strengthen the midfield up, with Keith Andrews his preferred target. I must say, being an Irishman and seeing Andrews play internationally, he&amp;rsquo;s nothing special. Far from it actually, he&amp;rsquo;s a typical Sam Allardyce player, works hard and tackles hard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>