<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newcastle United Supporters Trust on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/newcastle-united-supporters-trust/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newcastle United Supporters Trust on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 15:07:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/newcastle-united-supporters-trust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Are NUST wasting their time with NUFC?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/02/are-nust-wasting-their-time-with-nufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 15:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/02/are-nust-wasting-their-time-with-nufc/</guid>
      <description>###NUST - Are they wasting their time with plan to buy Newcastle United FC?
NUST were big news last year when Mike Ashley was desperate to sell Newcastle United. They were on Sky Sports boasting plans of owning the club or indeed I should say, the fans owning the club in a similar style to Barcelona. However, they never made the offer if reports are to be correct and they never managed to get hold of the North-East club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llambias interested in hearing what NUST have to say</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/12/llambias-interested-in-hearing-what-nust-have-to-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 17:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/12/llambias-interested-in-hearing-what-nust-have-to-say/</guid>
      <description>Reports in the Chronicle today claim that Derek Llambias, the second man in charge at Newcastle United, is set to meet with the Supporters Trust, over a possible takeover. It&amp;rsquo;s understood that Llambias offered to meet them within an hour of releasing their statement of intent. However, the NUST have declined the invite and say they&amp;rsquo;re not yet ready to hold talks until their initial campaign has reached top gear. Why Llambias wants to hold talks so quickly, is perhaps because he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want the Supporters Trust uncovering some facts that won&amp;rsquo;t favour the current Toon hierarchy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>