<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Site on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Site on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 15:00:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyne Time Competition: Win yourself a limited edition Olympics camera!</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/28/tyne-time-competition-win-yourself-a-limited-edition-olympics-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/07/28/tyne-time-competition-win-yourself-a-limited-edition-olympics-camera/</guid>
      <description>#### Olympics - Team GB will be hoping to please the home crowds in the football
Despite all the issues with security that have been highlighted over the last couple of weeks - London and various parts of the UK are set for the 2012 Olympics. It&amp;rsquo;s sure to be a historic event, with some of the most able athletes from all corners of the world coming to Britain to compete in biggest combined sporting event in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Newcastle United fans across the globe: Happy Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/25/to-newcastle-united-fans-across-the-globe-happy-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 13:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/25/to-newcastle-united-fans-across-the-globe-happy-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas - Enjoy what&amp;rsquo;s been a good year for Alan Pardew and Newcastle Utd The season so far has been quite a surprisingly successful one. Newcastle United lay comfortably in the top half of the Premier League and on course for this campaigns expectations. We&amp;rsquo;ve had some memorable results including the win away at Sunderland, our thrashing of Stoke City away from home, and indeed we even went unbeaten in the Premier League for a record amount of games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make yourself some money while Newcastle United take a deserved rest</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/02/make-yourself-some-money-while-newcastle-united-take-a-deserved-rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/09/02/make-yourself-some-money-while-newcastle-united-take-a-deserved-rest/</guid>
      <description>#### Carroll - Misses out on the Portuguese encounter tomorrow due to injury
We&amp;rsquo;re all feeling the pinch - I know it myself. However, it&amp;rsquo;s a proven study that a lot of people are indeed adding Gambling to their list of growing hobbies and it is often providing some much needed extra cash. The stereotypical view of a bookmaker is someone who takes all your money and can be arrogant in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyne Time Competition : Win a World Cup 2010 Jersey</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/04/tyne-time-competition-win-a-world-cup-2010-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 18:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/04/tyne-time-competition-win-a-world-cup-2010-jersey/</guid>
      <description>World Cup - Answer a simple question and enter our competition! After a long vote between either a World Cup jersey or a Vuvuzela , it&amp;rsquo;s been decided that a jersey will indeed be the prize on offer here at Tyne Time. Over a year on the web now, Tyne Time has gained a lot of support from the thousands of Newcastle United fans online and will hopefully continue to do so, for years to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Feature – Tyne Time puts wits up against worlds leading sports psychic</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/05/new-feature-tyne-time-puts-wits-up-against-worlds-leading-sports-psychic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 23:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/05/new-feature-tyne-time-puts-wits-up-against-worlds-leading-sports-psychic/</guid>
      <description>As Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s exciting season continues on the field, Tyne Time have teamed up with Dean &amp;lsquo;Midas&amp;rsquo; Maynard, one the worlds most renowned psychics who has many successes to date. Dean and myself have agreed to have a little challenge to see who&amp;rsquo;s predictions are most accurate for the remaining 13 Coca Cola Championship games. Obviously a lot of people will be skeptic of Dean&amp;rsquo;s abilities and I must say I&amp;rsquo;m not really a man into this kind of stuff but nevertheless, it interests me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year to all Newcastle United Fans</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/31/happy-new-year-to-all-newcastle-united-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 19:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/31/happy-new-year-to-all-newcastle-united-fans/</guid>
      <description>### Team - Top the league and a nice way to end the year
As Christmas is over and we enter a new year, it again brings back the memories of 2009 and all those incidents. Sportingwise, I cannot forget Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s relegation from the Premier League or indeed the way in Ireland missed out on a World Cup place yet again. However, in a few hours we will have entered a new era, 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From all at Tyne Time – Have a Happy Christmas</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/24/from-all-at-tyne-time-have-a-happy-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 17:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/24/from-all-at-tyne-time-have-a-happy-christmas/</guid>
      <description>### Seasons Greetings to all you readers
As you know it&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Eve and tomorrow is Christmas day. Tyne Time would like to wish all it&amp;rsquo;s readers and every Geordie in the world, from Brazil to Australia, a very very Happy Christmas. I&amp;rsquo;m sure a lot of things have happened since the last time Christmas was celebrated, some good, some bad. However, for Newcastle United, things have marginally picked up. 10 points clear at the top of the Coca Cola Championship and stability at once is seems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it really fair for Shola to make World Cup and Shay to stay at home?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/19/is-it-really-fair-for-shola-to-make-world-cup-and-shay-to-stay-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/19/is-it-really-fair-for-shola-to-make-world-cup-and-shay-to-stay-at-home/</guid>
      <description>To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not in the best of moods today, mainly because France have cheated their way to the World Cup Finals in in South Africa at the expense of my nation, Ireland. Thierry Henry above all people blatantly handled the ball, not once but twice before laying it on William Gallas&amp;rsquo; head to head home an undeserved winner. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to sound biased but obviously I will as it&amp;rsquo;s my country who have been denied a spot in South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyne Time Special – Charity Weekend Bet #2</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/13/tyne-time-special-charity-weekend-bet-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 23:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/13/tyne-time-special-charity-weekend-bet-2/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of the week again when Tyne Time gathers all it&amp;rsquo;s prestige and invaluable information to form a bet which will see a charity of it&amp;rsquo;s choice, hopefully, be in luck and win 50% of the bet winnings. Last Saturday didn&amp;rsquo;t go too well but this week we here Tyne Time feel that this weeks one might stand more of a chance. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you might have saw the article a little further down the page about donating to keep this weekly bet going, and I must say that hopefully if any donations do come through we can keep this feature going for weeks to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling a tad generous?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/13/feeling-a-tad-generous/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/13/feeling-a-tad-generous/</guid>
      <description>Before I start, I&amp;rsquo;m not looking for donations of 20,000 so I can put a pot together to stage a takeover of Newcastle United or become a leading member of the Newcastle United Supporters Trust. Far from it, although if you feel like donating twenty thousand fee free to do so 😀 Anyway, what I am writing this article about, is the matter of &amp;lsquo;Tyne Time&amp;rsquo;s Weekend Charity Bet&amp;rsquo; which will tomorrow commence for it&amp;rsquo;s second week running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle’s finest hangs up his boots</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/10/newcastles-finest-hangs-up-his-boots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 16:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/10/newcastles-finest-hangs-up-his-boots/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to dedicate this article to someone I&amp;rsquo;m sure a lot of people will know, especially Newcastle United fans. Today Ed Harrison from NUFCBLOG has announced that he closing the site after 2 years of constant writing. Ed never failed to produce articles on any given day and considering he indeed lives in a different time zone in America, it&amp;rsquo;s a credit to him, what he has achieved. His article archives are full to the brim and he has written in the region of 7,858 articles, a staggering amount for one man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyne Time Special : Weekend Charity Bet</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/06/tyne-time-special-weekend-charity-bet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 20:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/06/tyne-time-special-weekend-charity-bet/</guid>
      <description>I thought I&amp;rsquo;d do something different for these exciting weekends of football and I&amp;rsquo;ve decided on a Charity Weekend Bet. This weekend brings a huge amount of games happening in the UK, ranging from Premier League, Championship, League 1, League 2, Scottish Premier Division and FA Cup. Every once in a while, Tyne Time will place £1 on a number of fixtures that should they come through, will pay out handsome dividends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>