<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modibo Maiga on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/modibo-maiga/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modibo Maiga on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 18:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/modibo-maiga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Modibo Maiga fails Newcastle United medical due to knee injury?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/16/modibo-maiga-fails-newcastle-united-medical-due-to-knee-injury/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 18:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/16/modibo-maiga-fails-newcastle-united-medical-due-to-knee-injury/</guid>
      <description>Maiga - Newcastle United January transfer deal off after failed medical It&amp;rsquo;s being reported on Twitter that Modibo Maiga has failed his medical with Newcastle United in the last couple of days following worries about his knee. L&amp;rsquo;Equipe have apparently publicised that Maiga will not join Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s side in January now, and that our attentions will turn to Oliver Giroud - who has been linked with us consistently for the past few weeks .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No chance of Jermain Defoe or Roman Pavlyuchenko signing for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/12/no-chance-of-jermain-defoe-or-roman-pavlyuchenko-signing-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 17:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/12/no-chance-of-jermain-defoe-or-roman-pavlyuchenko-signing-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Linked - Defoe &amp;amp; Pavlyuchenko both linked to Newcastle United this week I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed of late that quite a few websites are linking Roman Pavlyuchenko and Jermain Defoe to Newcastle United in a &amp;lsquo;double swoop&amp;rsquo;. Both of these guys have been rumoured to be on Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s wish-list since his arrival and I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that Jermain Defoe has been linked with a move to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park any time he hasn&amp;rsquo;t been playing for Harry Redknapp&amp;rsquo;s side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United ‘agree £7m deal’ with Sochaux over Modibo Maiga</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/18/newcastle-united-agree-7m-deal-with-sochaux-over-modibo-maiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 11:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/18/newcastle-united-agree-7m-deal-with-sochaux-over-modibo-maiga/</guid>
      <description>Pardew - Has managed to coax Modibo Maiga to Tyneside despite summer failure The fruitless long protracted talks with Sochaux over their prized forward Modibo Maiga in the summer may not have went down well on Tyneside, but news today from various sources including The Guardian claim that a deal has now been agreed between both parties and the Malian striker will pen a 4 and a half year deal at St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>