<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Danny Simpson on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/danny-simpson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Danny Simpson on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 17:53:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/danny-simpson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NUFC ‘closing in’ on Clyne as Simpson seeks new club</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/nufc-closing-in-on-clyne-as-simpson-seeks-new-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 17:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/05/18/nufc-closing-in-on-clyne-as-simpson-seeks-new-club/</guid>
      <description>#### Clyne - In high demand with Manchester United looking to poach the youngster
It is all very much paper talk at the moment surrounding Newcastle United and their proposed transfer targets, however, it is understood that Alan Pardew has made tentative inquiries about the availability of Crystal Palace right-back Nathaniel Clyne. At just 21 years of age, English, and with a lot of potential - Clyne is as expected very much sought after, but by Newcastle above all else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Danny Simpson really good enough to start for Newcastle?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/27/is-danny-simpson-really-good-enough-to-start-for-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 16:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/27/is-danny-simpson-really-good-enough-to-start-for-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>Simpson - Starting to shows signs of becoming a quite average right-back You would have to credit Danny Simpson with the fantastic point Newcastle United managed at Old Trafford against Manchester United earlier in the season, after he clawed what seemed a net destined header, off the line. In fact, his position on the line has saved Newcastle United goals this season. However, it seems to me that with every game that passes - Simpson looks increasingly average and surely isn&amp;rsquo;t one of the first names on Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s matchday teamsheet?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perch &amp; O’Connor next up as Newcastle sign Simpson</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/20/perch-oconnor-next-up-as-newcastle-sign-simpson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 21:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/20/perch-oconnor-next-up-as-newcastle-sign-simpson/</guid>
      <description>Perch - A more than decent defender who Forest want to keep The breaking news is, as I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve heard is that we&amp;rsquo;ve finally managed to sign someone, and in the shape of Danny Simpson. The Manchester United former joins for a reported fee of £500k and on £10,000 a week wages, which if true, is very very good value. On top of that, if the wage figure that&amp;rsquo;s being thrown about the place is accurate then I wonder what all the confusion was about?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Simpson transfer could still be sorted</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/16/danny-simpson-transfer-could-still-be-sorted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 21:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/16/danny-simpson-transfer-could-still-be-sorted/</guid>
      <description>Simpson - The deal is not totally dead according to reports Newcastle fans are describing the transfer of Danny Simpson as one of the most important steps Chris Hughton will take this season. The Manchester United RB has been on-loan since last year and has impressed the Geordie fans with his performances and especially, his attitude. However, the move has stalled because of Danny&amp;rsquo;s wage demands. As I wrote yesterday, NUFC supposedly have a wage-cap for the Coca Cola Championship campaign in place, and Simpson&amp;rsquo;s desired wage packet stretches beyond the limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny’s Newcastle United link utter Shittu as another Danny seems set for United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/15/dannys-newcastle-united-link-utter-shittu-as-another-danny-seems-set-for-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 23:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/15/dannys-newcastle-united-link-utter-shittu-as-another-danny-seems-set-for-united/</guid>
      <description>Do excuse the title. It was rather irresistible although probably just a little terrible all the same. Anyway, if the rumours are accurate and the many of them, Danny Simpson will return to Manchester United in the next few days. This comes as his contract talks with Chris Hughton &amp;amp; co. have resulted in the full-back demanding too much per-week, as listed in the &amp;lsquo;Newcastle United Coca Championship rule book&amp;rsquo;. As well as this it seems as if Matthew Kilgallon will wait until the summer to leave Sheffield United and Everton is his most likely destination now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Shittu, Danny Simpson, Matthew Kilgallon &amp; Jemaine Beckford all Toon bound?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/14/danny-shittu-danny-simpson-matthew-kilgallon-jemaine-beckford-all-toon-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 20:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/14/danny-shittu-danny-simpson-matthew-kilgallon-jemaine-beckford-all-toon-bound/</guid>
      <description>Sky Sports are reporting that Bolton&amp;rsquo;s Danny Shittu could well arrive on Tyneside on a loan deal until the end of the season. The Nigerian hasn&amp;rsquo;t really had much of a look in at the Reebok and with the arrival of Owen Coyle, Newcastle are hopeful they can borrow the 6&amp;rsquo;2 centre half. Just in case you don&amp;rsquo;t know too much about him, he&amp;rsquo;s 29 years of age, a Nigerian international and has played for a fair few clubs in his time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having the Tyne of his life</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/17/having-the-tyne-of-his-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 17:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/17/having-the-tyne-of-his-life/</guid>
      <description>Having arrived from Manchester United, it&amp;rsquo;s been a very good spell for Danny Simpson on Tyneside. The defender endured a frustrating time at Blackburn and indeed needed a move away from Manchester before the nerves got the better of him. Simpson, who had figured in most of our Championship games so far is on loan but he insists that he&amp;rsquo;s not counting the days until he returns to United, far from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle unlikely to sign any players before window</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/newcastle-unlikely-to-sign-any-players-before-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 15:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/newcastle-unlikely-to-sign-any-players-before-window/</guid>
      <description>Danny Simpson&amp;rsquo;s arrival from Manchester United a while back has been Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s only &amp;lsquo;signing&amp;rsquo; of the summer, so far. Mind you, it&amp;rsquo;s only a loan deal and lasts to January, which is pretty poor if you ask me. I can&amp;rsquo;t see why Newcastle don&amp;rsquo;t look to loan Macheda, or Fabio or indeed his brother Rafael.
There are plenty of players, as I&amp;rsquo;ve said many times before, that would join Newcastle in a flash, now more than ever, after our good start to the Coca Cola Championship campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simpson loan signing may indicate Ashley is staying on</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/simpson-loan-signing-may-indicate-ashley-is-staying-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/14/simpson-loan-signing-may-indicate-ashley-is-staying-on/</guid>
      <description>When you see loan signings coming to Newcastle you might, first of all, surprised that we have even attempted to sign a player or secondly there has been some development in the sale of the club. However, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get too excited as I think it could mean something far worse, Ashley staying on at Newcastle and regaining control of our club for another season. Sky Sports have just announced that David O&amp;rsquo;Leary is out of the running (Good) and that the post is still under consideration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>