<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fitz Hall on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/fitz-hall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fitz Hall on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 18:39:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/fitz-hall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United considering keeping Fitz Hall permanently</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/17/newcastle-united-considering-keeping-fitz-hall-permanently/</guid>
      <description>There are reports flying about the place in the last couple of days that Fitz Hall could be arriving on Tyneside on a permanent basis once the transfer window reopens. The defender, on-loan from Queens Park Rangers has seen a turbulent time at Loftus Road and indeed has seen the club dig their way through more than 3 managers this season. Their current manager in Neil Warnock could well have very different plans for the back four he wants next season and indeed Hall may not be included in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Fitz Hall really in talks with Newcastle United?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/21/is-fitz-hall-really-in-talks-with-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 16:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/21/is-fitz-hall-really-in-talks-with-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Hall - Was linked last year but whether he&amp;rsquo;s on the radar now we don&amp;rsquo;t know The news today is that Fitz Hall is having talks with Newcastle United FC &amp;amp; if these reports are to be believed, the talks aren&amp;rsquo;t going too well. A little reading around brought me to this issue and I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure if there&amp;rsquo;s any truth in it. Fitz Hall was linked last year and came close to a move if sources are to be believed, however it was wage demands that scuppered any possible switch to St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>