<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joe Kinnear on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/joe-kinnear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joe Kinnear on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 19:21:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/joe-kinnear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to judge Joe Kinnear – a verdict on the Irishman</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/02/03/time-judge-joe-kinnear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 19:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/02/03/time-judge-joe-kinnear/</guid>
      <description>I think we all remember the day Joe Kinnear announced that he was to become Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s director of football. I heard the news and quickly assumed that his role was simply a &amp;lsquo;favour for a mate&amp;rsquo; to get the Irishman back into a paying job and help him live comfortably, granted by owner Mike Ashley. Kinnear managed Newcastle in an ill-fated season at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park in which the famous football club suffered relegation to the Coca Cola Championship (npower) and although it may be contrary to the vast opinion among Newcastle fans, I do believe that the ex-Tottenham Hotspur footballer would have kept the club in the Premier League should he have been able to stay on as manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kinnear conundrum – Have Newcastle United fans overreacted?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/07/01/the-kinnear-conundrum-have-newcastle-united-fans-overreacted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 18:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/07/01/the-kinnear-conundrum-have-newcastle-united-fans-overreacted/</guid>
      <description>Not too many will forget Joe Kinnear&amp;rsquo;s talkSPORT interview just a few weeks ago. His mispronunciation of a trio of Newcastle United players caused a stir in the media, and if believed - amongst Yohan, Hatem, and indeed Sammy too. He concluded his interview with a needless insult seemingly aimed at the fans, claiming he withholds a level of intelligence far superior than the majority of NUFC fans, although his inability to pronounce the names of some of the players would argue otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew should be making plans for Charles N’Zogbia &amp; Hugo Rodallega</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/17/alan-pardew-should-be-making-plans-for-charles-nzogbia-hugo-rodallega/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 12:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/17/alan-pardew-should-be-making-plans-for-charles-nzogbia-hugo-rodallega/</guid>
      <description>Rodallega - Someone who could do a very good job at Newcastle United It was great on Sunday to sit back and watch both Birmingham vs. Fulham &amp;amp; Wigan Athletic vs. West Ham carefree. We did not need to worry about Newcastle United because we had guaranteed our safety a week earlier. Also, looking at Birmingham, Wigan and West Ham - you might also remember that we beat them all away from home this season, and indeed managed to get 16 out of a possible 18 points from those three troubled teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kinnear NOT returning to beached NUFC</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/05/kinnear-not-returning-to-beached-nufc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 12:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/05/kinnear-not-returning-to-beached-nufc/</guid>
      <description>### Kinnear - Clearly hasn&amp;rsquo;t taken the news well
Phew! That was a close one. Most fans were about to cry when they heard Joe Kinnear could be returning as Newcastle United manager but David Craig and his &amp;lsquo;sources&amp;rsquo; at Newcastle have confirmed that Kinnear will not be returning as manager. However it&amp;rsquo;s understood that Mike Ashley as Derek Llambias visited Joe Kinnear checking up on his, asking whether he was ready to return to football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Kinnear offered 2 year contract?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/05/joe-kinnear-offered-2-year-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 11:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/05/joe-kinnear-offered-2-year-contract/</guid>
      <description>Kinnear - Claims he&amp;rsquo;s been offered job at Newcastle Just when we thought we&amp;rsquo;d hear no more from him, Joe Kinnear has come out and claimed he has been offered his managerial spot back at Newcastle United. BBC News broke this story and since it&amp;rsquo;s been on Sky Sports News with David Craig up North-east has claimed that Joe Kinnear will not be returning as manager. This news comes as Keith Harris says the club should be sold by the end of August and we&amp;rsquo;ve no manager, and players leaving around us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Mike Ashley the worst football club owner ever?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/is-mike-ashley-the-worst-football-club-owner-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 17:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/23/is-mike-ashley-the-worst-football-club-owner-ever/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not funny really, how messed up we are. I&amp;rsquo;m not one for shifting the blame and allow things to justify themselves but Mike Ashley&amp;rsquo;s tenure at Newcastle United is far from laughable. The hopes and expectations when he took over were pretty high, the couple of men who voiced their concerns over his takeover were looked on is if they had two heads. Eventually them two guys turned into a group but still, the moderate Toon supporter backed the billionaire owner who invested nearly £300m into their beloved NUFC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Kinnear not returning but no resolution in sight</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/15/kinnear-not-returning-but-no-resolution-in-sight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 11:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/15/kinnear-not-returning-but-no-resolution-in-sight/</guid>
      <description>Newcastle United have announced , yes announced! that Joe Kinnear won&amp;rsquo;t be returning as manager of the club. In a statement they said talks were ongoing with prospective consortia and that a sale was still in the pipeline. What I can&amp;rsquo;t understand is why, they haven&amp;rsquo;t included in that statement a statement of intent and of what exactly was going on a club. Where the sale was , regarding progress and any time-scale although their predicted times when the deal would be finalised was less than accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>