<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jose Enrique on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/jose-enrique/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jose Enrique on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:40:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/jose-enrique/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Liverpool will undoubtedly venture in for Jose Enrique in the summer</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/14/liverpool-will-undoubtedly-venture-in-for-jose-enrique-in-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/14/liverpool-will-undoubtedly-venture-in-for-jose-enrique-in-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>In his first real season in the Premier League Jose Enrique has shown his critics why Newcastle United splashed out £6.25m on him during Sam Allardyce&amp;rsquo;s short reign at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. Enrique has turned in world class performances for the majority of the season and unsurprisingly, has attracted interest from some of the top clubs in England and indeed throughout Europe. It is believed an initial enquiry from AC Milan for Jose was turned down rather abruptly during the January transfer window but with only 18 months let on his contract; clubs are circling like vultures, eyeing up the soon-to-be Spanish international.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jose Enrique’s Natural Position – Defending Spain</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/03/jose-enriques-natural-position-defending-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 18:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/03/jose-enriques-natural-position-defending-spain/</guid>
      <description>Enrique - Believes Spain the credentials to lift the greatest trophy in the world Jose Enrique, left back extraordinaire for a talented Newcastle squad, will most probably be one of Spain’s primary defensive juggernauts in the future. As the team vies for a World Cup Championship on the heels of a European Championship (2008), he made his comments regarding Spain’s chances of winning.
Never one to shy away from hullabaloo, the six-foot defender emphatically stated that Spain has a great shot at winning the World Cup, and is only one of eight teams in the world capable of the feat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enrique wouldn’t dare join Sunderland</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/11/enrique-wouldnt-dare-join-sunderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 15:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/11/enrique-wouldnt-dare-join-sunderland/</guid>
      <description>As my headline suggests Sunderland have been linked with a move for Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s Jose Enrique today but there&amp;rsquo;s no need to get worried, it&amp;rsquo;s only coming from the News Of The World who on Sundays, usually dedicate at least 2 articles to us. The reports claim that Bruce will make his move in January for the Spaniard and will hope to seal a deal very quickly. However, I doubt very much as if Enrique will want to leave and honestly, he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be allowed after he was on the relegated side earlier this year, that still owe us a huge amount.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>