<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joey Barton on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/joey-barton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joey Barton on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 16:12:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/joey-barton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The scenario that will more than likely face Newcastle United fans on August 31st</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/05/the-scenario-that-will-more-than-likely-face-newcastle-united-fans-on-august-31st/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 16:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/05/the-scenario-that-will-more-than-likely-face-newcastle-united-fans-on-august-31st/</guid>
      <description>Questions - Who will be at Newcastle United and who&amp;rsquo;ll be gone come Aug 31st? Seemingly the drama surrounding Joey Barton, Twitter and the board and indeed Jose Enrique&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;impending&amp;rsquo; move to Liverpool is somewhat putting our transfer exploits on the back-burner - for the media at least. Today we found out that there have been talks with Tranquillo Barnetta and NUFC and that those very talks were going quite well - only for the Swiss to suffer an injury that could postpone the move to January or indeed permanently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lille’s Yohan Cabaye the inevitable replacement for the loyal Joey Barton</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/01/lilles-yohan-cabaye-the-inevitable-replacement-for-the-loyal-joey-barton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 18:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/01/lilles-yohan-cabaye-the-inevitable-replacement-for-the-loyal-joey-barton/</guid>
      <description>Cabaye - Likely to replace Joey Barton as the club looks to offload the POTS The board at this club continue to confuse me with their antics. Firstly they sack an absolute gent of a manager who after bringing Newcastle United back to the Premier League at first attempt, was looking like he would finish midtable after some stunning results throughout the season - including an away win at Arsenal, Chelsea, Everton &amp;amp; indeed absolute routs at home to Aston Villa and Sunderland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joey Barton available for £1.5m – West Ham &amp; Aston Villa line up bids.</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/joey-barton-available-for-1-5m-west-ham-aston-villa-line-up-bids/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 15:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/joey-barton-available-for-1-5m-west-ham-aston-villa-line-up-bids/</guid>
      <description>Barton - Newcastle have set an asking fee of £1.5m for the midfielder Everything that you hear from Newcastle United nowadays must be taken in with quite the opposite. Since Mike Ashley took over the club, things are gone bezerk to say the very least. As I said in my last article, we cannot really trust the owners of the club until they have handed over the keys to new owners and are on their way home - indeed the likelihood of that happening is quite low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too much being made of Barton punch on Gamst Pedersen</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/11/too-much-being-made-of-barton-punch-on-gamst-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 19:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/11/too-much-being-made-of-barton-punch-on-gamst-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>Barton - Made his feelings known to Morten Gamst Pedersen foolishly last night Well some say it was a matter of time. Joey Barton has hit the headlines again, not for his great performances of late which includes 3 assists in the last 4 games, but for another reason. As the many various papers and online journals have pointed out, Joey Barton struck Morten Gamst Pedersen in the stomach with a right handed clout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joey Barton v Wolves – A sign of a changing player</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/29/joey-barton-v-wolves-a-sign-of-a-changing-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/08/29/joey-barton-v-wolves-a-sign-of-a-changing-player/</guid>
      <description>I would like to highlight the word &amp;lsquo;changing&amp;rsquo; in this article. We won&amp;rsquo;t forget the dark dark days that Joey Barton has put Newcastle United Football Club through since his £5.8m move from Manchester City and we won&amp;rsquo;t forget that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t half as much as he should have. Saying that, there&amp;rsquo;s strong evidence to suggest that he&amp;rsquo;s maturing as a footballer and as an individual. It&amp;rsquo;s also obvious that Wolverhampton Wanderers targeted Barton today, and hoped that he would retaliate - ending up in a sending off and inevitably, a Wolves victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joey Barton couldn’t be returning to the Newcastle team at a better time</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/18/joey-barton-couldnt-be-returning-to-the-newcastle-team-at-a-better-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 22:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/18/joey-barton-couldnt-be-returning-to-the-newcastle-team-at-a-better-time/</guid>
      <description>Ok, maybe it could be better. Perhaps lying in the top half of the Premier League table would be a better scenario but our current one isn&amp;rsquo;t far off. There&amp;rsquo;s major relief and indeed contentment around Tyneside as it seems we&amp;rsquo;re on our way back up to the Premier League following relegation from it last year. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, there&amp;rsquo;s still 10 games or so left, but surely we can&amp;rsquo;t throw away a 12 point lead from the automatic promotion spots away?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where will Joey Barton fit in once he comes back from injury?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/09/where-will-joey-barton-fit-in-once-he-comes-back-from-injury/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 22:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/09/where-will-joey-barton-fit-in-once-he-comes-back-from-injury/</guid>
      <description>The recent performances of Danny Guthrie have been nothing short of fantastic as the former Liverpool midfielder continues to prove that he&amp;rsquo;s more of an asset in centre midfield. Guthrie scored twice on Saturday and both were from distance. He&amp;rsquo;s also got important goals this seasons like our home tie against West Brom, in the 2-2 draw. The forlorn figure of Joey Barton will reappear from Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s dressing-room in the next week or so but I can&amp;rsquo;t see him breaking into the Toon starting 11 straight away anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Joey Barton beginning to mature just a little?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/30/is-joey-barton-beginning-to-mature-just-a-little/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 20:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/30/is-joey-barton-beginning-to-mature-just-a-little/</guid>
      <description>Swollen eyes, burst lips, broken teeth and a jail term all are familiar terms associated with Joey Barton. However, the man who served time in prison for beating the daylights out of a youngster in Liverpool a while back, has today spoke out against modern day footballers who are living the dream so to speak. Speaking, he said that most footballers are &amp;lsquo;knobs&amp;rsquo; and think that their extreme wealth will continue forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Barton will be back for Brom battle?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/26/will-barton-will-be-back-for-brom-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 21:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/26/will-barton-will-be-back-for-brom-battle/</guid>
      <description>Barton - Will he miss the crucial tie with West Brom? Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;m looking into things just a little too much but it&amp;rsquo;s occurred to me, as I&amp;rsquo;m sure it has to you, that West Bromich Albion are hot on the tails of Newcastle in the Coca Cola Championship. Today, we were a little lacklustre in midfield and missed Alan Smith. Nicky Butt played well in many periods of the game but in fairness to the man, he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be first choice in the middle of the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barton ready to put bust-ups behind him</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/08/barton-ready-to-put-bust-ups-behind-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 15:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/08/barton-ready-to-put-bust-ups-behind-him/</guid>
      <description>We all remember Joey Barton don&amp;rsquo;t we? The guy who has played a few games for us and picks up a cool 65k a week, even when he was in prison last year. I think the name rings a bell. Well he;s injured again and taking time out he spoke to Sky Sports at length, confessing to bust-up&amp;rsquo;s with Chris Hughton and Alan Shearer, Kinnear the only one he didn&amp;rsquo;t have a tattle with it seems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>