<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wayne Routledge on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/wayne-routledge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wayne Routledge on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 23:28:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/wayne-routledge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Confident Coventry City performance sees Toon top table by three</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/17/confident-coventry-city-performance-sees-toon-top-table-by-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 23:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/02/17/confident-coventry-city-performance-sees-toon-top-table-by-three/</guid>
      <description>Well it does feel good to stay top of the table and even better to score four goals against a pretty decent Coventry City team. In what was a must-win game ( which ones aren&amp;rsquo;t? ) the lads truly delivered. Although it didn&amp;rsquo;t start the best, and it took us a little while to get into the game, we eventually got a grasp on the game and didn&amp;rsquo;t loosen our grip on it once we scored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nile nets winner as the new-boys make their debuts on Tyneside</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/27/nile-nets-winner-as-the-new-boys-make-their-debuts-on-tyneside/</guid>
      <description>Ranger - Netted again tonight as we saw Routledge &amp;amp; Williamson in action Tonights affair was a game we needed all three points from and the lads duly delivered the goods. In what was a Crystal Palace team without one of their main men in Victor Moses saw them concede within twenty minutes, a Shaun Derry O.G. In fairness, it seems as if Palace gave it a real go and could well have got something out of the game on another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayne Routledge is a very good signing for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/26/wayne-routledge-is-a-very-good-signing-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 16:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/26/wayne-routledge-is-a-very-good-signing-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Routledge - a Very good signing for the Toon Army is you ask me It&amp;rsquo;s surprise news to say the least to hear that Newcastle have signed Wayne Routledge from QPR today and very good news if you ask me. The winger has signed a reported 3 and a half deal on Tyneside and for a fee of £1m, which if true, is very good value. Routledge as you might remember was a Tottenham and Villa former and an exciting winger.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>