<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Papiss Demba Cissé on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/papiss-demba-ciss%C3%A9/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Papiss Demba Cissé on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 18:42:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/papiss-demba-ciss%C3%A9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew has a big decision to make</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/08/13/alan-pardew-big-decision-make/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 18:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/08/13/alan-pardew-big-decision-make/</guid>
      <description>Few football fans will ever forget Papiss Cissé&amp;rsquo;s incredible effort against Chelsea at Stamford Bridge during the 2011&amp;frasl;12 Premier League season. The Senegalese international rifled an almost physics-defying &amp;lsquo;banana effort&amp;rsquo; over Petr Cech&amp;rsquo;s head and into the back of the net to complete one of the best Premier League braces I have seen in quite some time. After that season came to a close, the real Cissé seemed to disappear. Following Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s exit from the Europa League to Benfica at the Quarter-finals stage, Papiss failed to find any real form and the club&amp;rsquo;s season suffered from then on - narrowly avoiding relegation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is keeping Ba happy hindering Cissé’s performances?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/09/12/is-keeping-ba-happy-hindering-cisses-performances/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 16:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/09/12/is-keeping-ba-happy-hindering-cisses-performances/</guid>
      <description>Cissé - All eyes on Papiss after a phenomenal first half season in the EPL No one could quite believe their eyes from January onwards last season as Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s latest addition - Papiss Cissé - began scoring the most ridiculous of goals the Premier League is likely to see for some time. He notched up double figures in Black and White despite only arriving at the end of the season and almost all his goals oozed utter class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fans Special: Get your Papiss Cissé wallpaper for free!</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/08/fans-special-get-your-papiss-cisse-wallpaper-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/08/fans-special-get-your-papiss-cisse-wallpaper-for-free/</guid>
      <description>Cissé - Scored a brace for the third game in a row including a stunning second It is hard not to sit back and relish Papiss Cisse&amp;rsquo;s goal scoring form for Newcastle United at the minute - what ever club you support in the Premier League, bar the obvious. Arriving from Germany for £9m - a little more than a quarter of Andy Carroll&amp;rsquo;s fee - he has already notched nine goals in eight games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Branson brought Papiss Demba Cissé to Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/01/20/richard-branson-brought-papiss-demba-cisse-to-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 20:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/01/20/richard-branson-brought-papiss-demba-cisse-to-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Branson - Influx of shirt sponsorship money seemingly financed Cissé move With Newcastle United managing the biggest, and most expensive coup of the January transfer window so far, many were surprised by the £9m spent on Senegalese striker Papiss Demba Cisse - including me. Of course you would be surprised though, after all Alan Pardew did say that they had no plans to bring in a striker this window - despite giving Jason Prior a trial on Tyneside .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>