<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonas Gutierrez on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/jonas-gutierrez/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jonas Gutierrez on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 23:01:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/jonas-gutierrez/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonas Gutierrez astonishingly focused on the 2010 World Cup</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/11/jonas-gutierrez-astonishingly-focused-on-the-2010-world-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 23:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/11/jonas-gutierrez-astonishingly-focused-on-the-2010-world-cup/</guid>
      <description>Jonas - Eager to do well with Argentina in South Africa this month Indeed Jonas Gutierrez is so concentrated on this upcoming World Cup that he forgot to pack normal everyday clothes! Packing just football gear and a tracksuit, Jonas forgot to put some normal clothes in what seemingly was a very small suitcase. However, he claims that it&amp;rsquo;s his ultimate focus for Argentina at the World Cup this year that inevitably resulted in him arriving in South Africa with no normal clothes to wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonas Gutierrez can play a huge part in Argentina winning the 2010 World Cup</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/08/jonas-gutierrez-can-play-a-huge-part-in-argentina-winning-the-2010-world-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 21:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/06/08/jonas-gutierrez-can-play-a-huge-part-in-argentina-winning-the-2010-world-cup/</guid>
      <description>Argentina - Tyne Time fancies the Argies to come very close to the trophy We here at Tyne Time like an odd punt on football and we know that most of readers do too. One site, we seriously recommended for availing of the best betting offers are simply because they have what you need. A clean site that tells you where you need to go to get the best sign-up offers that you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toon batter Barnsley and Gutierrez produces spiderman skills</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/07/toon-batter-barnsley-and-gutierrez-produces-spiderman-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 01:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/03/07/toon-batter-barnsley-and-gutierrez-produces-spiderman-skills/</guid>
      <description>Gutierrez - A clearly delighted Toon supporter shows his delight at Jonas&amp;rsquo;s mask! We spoke about Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s free-scoring form at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park this season and it continued again today with Barnsley the victims. 6 goals scored and five of them in the second half, including a rare goal from former Real Zaragoza winger Jonas Gutierrez, and what a goal it was. Cutting in from the left wing, he ghosted past two Barnsley markers before floating it into the top corner off the backside of the crossbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonas likely to leave as Roma move looms</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/01/jonas-likely-to-leave-as-roma-move-looms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/01/jonas-likely-to-leave-as-roma-move-looms/</guid>
      <description>### Jonas - Reportedly on Roma&amp;rsquo;s radar
Just as it seems all is settled on Tyneside regards players, reports have emerged of Jonas Gutierrez possibly moving away from Newcastle in January. The news comes from no-one else but his agent, and how annoying them agents happen to become. As a Newcastle United fan down through the years, agents of players have often proved to be a thorn in our side as they like to force moves and indeed make themselves a little money in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonas could be a very big player for Newcastle this season</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/16/jonas-could-be-a-very-big-player-for-newcastle-this-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 18:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/16/jonas-could-be-a-very-big-player-for-newcastle-this-season/</guid>
      <description>### Jonas - Rejoins his high-flying club
Jonas Gutierrez in midweek secured his longest dream, of bringing Argentina to South Africa and indeed he himself, played a major hand in the deciding goal against Uruguay. Although he only won the free-kick which led to the goal, he looked quite sharp at times and the oppositions full-back found it quite difficult to keep taps on the &amp;lsquo;greyhound&amp;rsquo;. Tomorrow, Jonas is expected to line out in Nottingham where hopefully he&amp;rsquo;ll play his part in a win for Newcastle United.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gutierrez grateful for gaffers goodwill</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/10/gutierrez-grateful-for-gaffers-goodwill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 17:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/10/gutierrez-grateful-for-gaffers-goodwill/</guid>
      <description>### Jonas - Lining out for Argentina tonight
Newcastle United winger Jonas Gutierrez will tonight line out in what is a must win game for Argentina. If the Argies, led by former World Cup legend and the founder of the hand of god, Maradona, lose tonight, then their chances of making usually a familiar trip to the World Cup Finals, will be over. Maradona who claimed staggeringly, that his first three names on the Argentina team sheet were Lionel Messi, Javier Mascherano and Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s very own Jonas Gutierréz will as you&amp;rsquo;d expect start Jonas tonight and we certainly hope he comes back injury free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argentine returns as Taylor is out</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/29/argentine-returns-as-taylor-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 15:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/29/argentine-returns-as-taylor-is-out/</guid>
      <description>### Ryan - Has settled well on Tyneside
You could nearly say that he&amp;rsquo;s been one our players of the season so far. Chipping in with a couple of goals too, and no ordinary goals mind you. Ryan Taylor&amp;rsquo;s latest was against Ipswich when he caught the keeper in an awkward position and caressed it into the top corner, and not a fluke as some may have suggested. He also hit the target with a stunning strike, with his left this time, into the other top corner, in a two nil win against Crystal Palace earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonas ready to leave troubled Toon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/10/jonas-ready-to-leave-troubled-toon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 16:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/10/jonas-ready-to-leave-troubled-toon/</guid>
      <description>### Jonas - Ready for Greek move
Some may be delighted to see the guy go, he&amp;rsquo;s been labelled everything from a headless chicken to an astounding dribbler but either way he wants out of Newcastle, and sooner the better. I suppose I can&amp;rsquo;t blame Gutierrez too much for leaving and I believe that he&amp;rsquo;ll be a very good player in the years to come. I&amp;rsquo;ll never forget that performance in Old Trafford when he caused real havoc for United, indeed most Toon fans will never forget that, managing a point but not only that, Fabricio Coloccini having a great game too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>