<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alan Pardew on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/alan-pardew/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alan Pardew on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 18:30:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/alan-pardew/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew – What Crystal Palace fans can expect from the self-proclaimed king</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2015/01/03/alan-pardew-crystal-palace-fans-can-expect-self-proclaimed-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 18:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2015/01/03/alan-pardew-crystal-palace-fans-can-expect-self-proclaimed-king/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not going to lie, it brings me great pleasure to be able to write this article at the start of a new year. Alan Pardew has finally packed his bags and left Newcastle United after four years in charge. I think most NUFC fans were beginning the accept the sad fact that Pardew was not going to be sacked, especially when the club enter a truly horrid period of form at the start of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hull City collapse prolongs Pardew’s painful stay</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/20/hull-city-collapse-prolongs-pardews-painful-stay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 19:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/20/hull-city-collapse-prolongs-pardews-painful-stay/</guid>
      <description>The atmosphere promised to be toxic. That very word had been bandied around the offices of every media outlet covering Newcastle United ahead of their home encounter with Hull City. The SackPardew campaign had gone down seamlessly and was going nicely up until kick-off. As crowds filtered into St. James&amp;rsquo; Park, security guards confiscated hundreds of banners and posters, despite the protesters being given a written go-ahead from the club and the local police.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew knows he is nearing the end of his time at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/14/alan-pardew-knows-nearing-end-time-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2014 14:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/14/alan-pardew-knows-nearing-end-time-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>I have often felt some sort of empathy towards Newcastle United managers in the past who have been shown the door at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park. In fact, in years gone-by, &amp;lsquo;revolving door&amp;rsquo; became a common buzzword on Tyneside when talking about managers. Realistically, Sir Bobby Robson should never have been sacked in 2004 after the club drifted just outside the Champions League places. From then on, things just got worse. His replacement Graeme Souness couldn&amp;rsquo;t hack it in the North-East, although certain personalities in the dressing-room made it even more difficult for the Scot to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew: At a point of no return with Newcastle supporters?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/09/alan-pardew-at-a-point-of-no-return-with-newcastle-supporters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 18:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/09/09/alan-pardew-at-a-point-of-no-return-with-newcastle-supporters/</guid>
      <description>There are very few professions in the world that people often pray/beg/call for the sacking of an individual from his day job. Politics and football are an exception, and these are two things Mr. Alan Pardew is well used to both at Newcastle United since taking control in 2010. One could be forgiven for looking in from the outside and coming to the conclusion that Newcastle fans can never be pleased; after all Pardew was the same guy who led the Magpies to brink of Champions League football in 2011&amp;frasl;12 only to miss out in the final two games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have the players given up on manager Alan Pardew?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/03/30/players-given-manager-alan-pardew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 20:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/03/30/players-given-manager-alan-pardew/</guid>
      <description>There have been a few times this season when Newcastle United have looked a Championship team at best - no less than in our latest mauling at Southampton on Saturday. The players looked clueless, disinterested and generally lazy throughout the 90+ minutes at St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s, and it&amp;rsquo;s not the first time such a performance has materialised. At home to Tottenham Hotspur - truth be told - a pretty awful Tottenham Hotspur showed up to stick four past Tim Krul in the Newcastle United goal and leave a packed out St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Kinnear’s resignation signal a victory for Alan Pardew?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/02/04/kinnears-resignation-signal-victory-alan-pardew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 18:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/02/04/kinnears-resignation-signal-victory-alan-pardew/</guid>
      <description>Finally there is a little good news on Tyneside. Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s Director of Football Joe Kinnear announced his &amp;lsquo;resignation&amp;rsquo; from his position at the club with immediate effect — just hours after Tyne Time delivered a verdict on the &amp;lsquo;job&amp;rsquo; he had done so far. Of course it is likely that Kinnear resigned earlier that day, we&amp;rsquo;ll just all pretend that he read our article and decided it was time to go, OK?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deciphering Alan Pardew’s pre-season comments</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/07/26/deciphering-alan-pardews-pre-season-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 19:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/07/26/deciphering-alan-pardews-pre-season-comments/</guid>
      <description>Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s Portuguese pre-season tour seems to have went pretty well in terms of preparation for the upcoming season if a whole host of Northern journalists are to be believed. Fitness levels are extremely high - a result of four hour long training sessions led by Alan Pardew in relative heat, while there seems to be a stern and focused mentality. Such results offer immense encouragement to Newcastle United fans who have grown tired of countless transfer rumours, and little end product, as of yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew will stay on as Newcastle United manager</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/05/13/alan-pardew-will-stay-on-as-newcastle-united-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2013/05/13/alan-pardew-will-stay-on-as-newcastle-united-manager/</guid>
      <description>Back at the start of December 2012, a couple of days after Newcastle United had fielded a side with Nile Ranger up front away at Bordeaux in the Europa League, a survey was carried out. The question was simple, is Alan Pardew the man to bring Newcastle United forward as a club? 95% of voters claimed he was. Fast forward five months and NUFC have staved off the threat of relegation, just about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graham Carr in France scouting players as we speak</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/22/graham-carr-in-france-scouting-players-as-we-speak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 15:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/22/graham-carr-in-france-scouting-players-as-we-speak/</guid>
      <description>Debuchy - On a long list of players in France that NUFC are interested After already luring the likes of Ben Arfa, Cabaye, Marveaux and Mehdi Abeid from France, Graham Carr in already working on new transfer targets as the season draws to a close. In a recent interview, Alan Pardew confirmed that work was already under way for next season, as Newcastle United hope to build on what has been quite honestly, a phenomenal second season in the Premier League since our return from the Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Brom vs. Newcastle United – What we can expect from Hodgson’s side</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/22/west-brom-vs-newcastle-united-what-we-can-expect-from-hodgsons-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 11:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/22/west-brom-vs-newcastle-united-what-we-can-expect-from-hodgsons-side/</guid>
      <description>Brom - Happened to be Chris Hughton&amp;rsquo;s final game in charge of NUFC The last time Newcastle United met West Brom at the Hawthorns we were on the end of a 3-1 loss, courtesy of Peter Odemwingie &amp;amp; Simon Tchoyi. Peter Lovenkrands managed our only goal in that game, indeed what turned out to be Chris Hughton&amp;rsquo;s final game in charge of Newcastle United. Things really have changed since then and we are going to West Brom with a different team , a different manager and an improved league position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Alan Pardew look to secure Junior Hoilett in the summer?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/10/should-alan-pardew-look-to-secure-junior-hoilett-in-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2012 18:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/10/should-alan-pardew-look-to-secure-junior-hoilett-in-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>#### Hoilett - Out of contract in the summer and NUFC could do with a new winger
If you followed today&amp;rsquo;s Premier League games then you&amp;rsquo;ll definitely have noticed Blackburn&amp;rsquo;s win away at Wolves, and Junior Hoilett&amp;rsquo;s goal haul in that game. The winger scored twice to clinch three crucial points of Steve Kean&amp;rsquo;s side as they look to pull away from the dreaded relegation zone. The forward is out of contract in the summer according to reports and it will be hard for the Blackburn hierarchy to hold onto him with many clubs sniffing around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatem Ben Arfa has the potential to rip apart the Premier League</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/06/hatem-ben-arfa-has-the-potential-to-rip-apart-the-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 13:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/03/06/hatem-ben-arfa-has-the-potential-to-rip-apart-the-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>Ben Arfa - Has raw potential that needs harnessing by Alan Pardew &amp;amp; NUFC I think it is fair to say that when Hatem Ben Arfa came on for Newcastle United against Sunderland on Sunday; the Geordie faithful felt he had the potential to rescue what was an impending disaster. We weren&amp;rsquo;t wrong. The Frenchman gave Kieran Richardson one of the hardest times he&amp;rsquo;ll get all season from anyone on the wing - tearing him to pieces over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demba Ba will keep 50% of transfer fee received should he leave Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/19/demba-ba-will-keep-50-of-transfer-fee-received-should-he-leave-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 13:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/19/demba-ba-will-keep-50-of-transfer-fee-received-should-he-leave-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Ba - Has quite a peculiar contract and a slightly worrying one for NUFC There is some pretty interesting news coming from West Ham owner David Sullivan in the past day where he opens the lid on Demba Ba&amp;rsquo;s contract. The most staggering part of the interview with Iain Dale over at WestHamTillIDie is Sullivan&amp;rsquo;s claim that Demba Ba will receive half the transfer fee for himself should the Senegalese hitman move away from St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United will look to secure Brazilian defender in the summer</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/03/newcastle-united-will-look-to-secure-brazilian-defender-in-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/02/03/newcastle-united-will-look-to-secure-brazilian-defender-in-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>Douglas - Didn&amp;rsquo;t make the move to NUFC in January for various reasons When you compare the January transfer window of 2012 to a year previous, it makes for surprising reading. Newcastle United lost Andy Carroll to Liverpool for the guts of forty million pounds, while on that same day managed to bring Stephen Ireland in on loan. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the happiest of times for Toon fans but this year however, couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been more of a contrast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Newcastle United really pay £10m for Jan Vertonghen?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/23/will-newcastle-united-really-pay-10m-for-jan-vertonghen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 14:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/23/will-newcastle-united-really-pay-10m-for-jan-vertonghen/</guid>
      <description>Vertonghen - Carr and NUFC scouting team have been watching for some time The last time Newcastle United dished out double figures for a player that I can remember off the cuff was when we signed a certain Fabricio Coloccini, the current captain. Mike Ashley had just bought the club, and Coloccini was one of Kevin Keegan&amp;rsquo;s first signings at the club, arriving from Deportivo. When you consider the performances he has put in for NUFC in the last three seasons then you would have to say that his price tag has been more than justified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United eyeing up Yanga-Mbiwa as Alan Pardew steps up defender chase</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/05/newcastle-united-eyeing-up-yanga-mbiwa-as-alan-pardew-steps-up-defender-chase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 14:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/12/05/newcastle-united-eyeing-up-yanga-mbiwa-as-alan-pardew-steps-up-defender-chase/</guid>
      <description>Mbiwa - £5m rated defender could arrive on Tyneside in January with Maiga With Steven Taylor very unlikely to feature again in the 2011&amp;frasl;12 Premier League campaign, Alan Pardew is set to up the ante in the January transfer window and sign a replacement. Frenchman Mapou Yanga-Mbiwa had been linked with Newcastle in recent weeks, however Pardew played down any supposed interest. As you would expect, since the injury to Tayls, we are being linked with him again and it&amp;rsquo;s reported that members of our scouting team have advised Alan on the defender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No chance of Jermain Defoe or Roman Pavlyuchenko signing for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/12/no-chance-of-jermain-defoe-or-roman-pavlyuchenko-signing-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 17:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/11/12/no-chance-of-jermain-defoe-or-roman-pavlyuchenko-signing-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Linked - Defoe &amp;amp; Pavlyuchenko both linked to Newcastle United this week I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed of late that quite a few websites are linking Roman Pavlyuchenko and Jermain Defoe to Newcastle United in a &amp;lsquo;double swoop&amp;rsquo;. Both of these guys have been rumoured to be on Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s wish-list since his arrival and I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that Jermain Defoe has been linked with a move to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park any time he hasn&amp;rsquo;t been playing for Harry Redknapp&amp;rsquo;s side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United scouted Yohan Cabaye for 5 years before placing bid</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/23/newcastle-united-scouted-yohan-cabaye-for-5-years-before-placing-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 15:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/23/newcastle-united-scouted-yohan-cabaye-for-5-years-before-placing-bid/</guid>
      <description>Cabaye - Turning out to be a contender for Premier League signing of the season In aninteresting read by Mark Douglas over at the Sunday Sun, revealed that Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s scouting team were keeping tabs on Yohan Cabaye, before signing him this summer. To be honest, I find that slightly difficult to believe. If we date back five years from this very day, we&amp;rsquo;re in the year 2006. Those were the years of Glenn Roeder, and the likes of Damien Duff, Obafemi Martins, Anotine Sibierski and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United ‘agree £7m deal’ with Sochaux over Modibo Maiga</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/18/newcastle-united-agree-7m-deal-with-sochaux-over-modibo-maiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 11:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/18/newcastle-united-agree-7m-deal-with-sochaux-over-modibo-maiga/</guid>
      <description>Pardew - Has managed to coax Modibo Maiga to Tyneside despite summer failure The fruitless long protracted talks with Sochaux over their prized forward Modibo Maiga in the summer may not have went down well on Tyneside, but news today from various sources including The Guardian claim that a deal has now been agreed between both parties and the Malian striker will pen a 4 and a half year deal at St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United still desperate to land African forward in January</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/06/newcastle-united-still-desperate-to-land-african-forward-in-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 10:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/10/06/newcastle-united-still-desperate-to-land-african-forward-in-january/</guid>
      <description>Maiga - Newcastle United still pressing hard to get a January transfer deal done Despite landing their main target in the summer to partner Leon Best/ Demba Ba Newcastle United still remain very keen on Modibo Maiga of Sochaux. In fact; they&amp;rsquo;ve been out to watch him since the window has closed with a plan to lure him to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park in January. The very fact that Carr &amp;amp; Pardew are so keen to land the striker must tell you something - the lad must have a lot of potential in English football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yohan Cabaye the lynchpin of the new-look Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/21/yohan-cabaye-the-lynchpin-of-the-new-look-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 17:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/21/yohan-cabaye-the-lynchpin-of-the-new-look-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Cabaye - Class act and another shrewd piece of business by Newcastle United We may well look back at Saturday the 17th of September as the day Yohan Cabaye announced his arrival in the Premier League. The Frenchman played arguably his best ninety minutes in a Black and White shirt since his arrival and generally was sublime on the ball. It&amp;rsquo;s just a pity that he didn&amp;rsquo;t get his deserved goal on the day, the crossbar and a magnificent Shay Given save denying him two possible goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Same old excuses and same old lies from the hierarchy at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/03/same-old-excuses-and-same-old-lies-from-the-hierarchy-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 15:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/09/03/same-old-excuses-and-same-old-lies-from-the-hierarchy-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Llambias - Released statement explaining failed striker hunt after window shut When the window slammed shut at 11PM on Thursday night most Newcastle United fans were disappointed, tired, and angered that we hadn&amp;rsquo;t managed to recruit a new striker with £40m plus in our back-pockets and with over 8 months to do it. Of course we got Demba Ba in early on in the season - because he was a free transfer, looked for modest wages and wasn&amp;rsquo;t incredibly old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle trying to push through last minute move for Modibo Maiga &amp; also consider Nolan Roux</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/31/newcastle-trying-to-push-through-last-minute-move-for-modibo-maiga-also-consider-nolan-roux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/31/newcastle-trying-to-push-through-last-minute-move-for-modibo-maiga-also-consider-nolan-roux/</guid>
      <description>#### Maiga - Desperate to join Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s Newcastle United today
Modibo Maiga has been desperate for a move to Newcastle United since the day they expressed their first interest in him. He has had quarrels with the board, refused to play; dropped from squads and all the likes - but still he remains a Sochaux player as we approach the final seven hours of the summer transfer window. Despite the signing of a much needed full-back in Davide Santon, NUFC still haven&amp;rsquo;t added a striker to their ranks to add to our collection already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew has two days to bring in 2 players at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/29/alan-pardew-has-two-days-to-bring-in-2-players-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 17:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/29/alan-pardew-has-two-days-to-bring-in-2-players-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Pardew - Clock is ticking as NUFC desperately try to lure to players to St. James&amp;rsquo; It was always going to come down to the final couple of days wasn&amp;rsquo;t it? A whole summer was spent trying to find a new club for Joey Barton, get the best possible price for Jose Enrique and relocate Kevin Nolan. The whole summer is nearly gone; and we&amp;rsquo;re still crying out for a striker, and a left-back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United reportedly bid £10m for Inter Milan defender Davide Santon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/25/newcastle-united-reportedly-bid-10m-for-inter-milan-defender-davide-santon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/25/newcastle-united-reportedly-bid-10m-for-inter-milan-defender-davide-santon/</guid>
      <description>#### Santon - Would be a real statement of intent from NUFC if they pulled it off
There are emerging reports suggesting that Newcastle United are in advanced talks with Inter Milan&amp;rsquo;s Davide Santon over a move to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. I think most people will know Santon and also be aware of the talent he is. He was very much a wonderkid in the making a couple of years ago but for one reason or another - the Italian side may be willing to let the 20 year-old depart the San Siro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United eyeing up Bristol City’s Nicky Maynard?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/16/newcastle-united-eyeing-up-bristol-citys-nicky-maynard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 12:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/16/newcastle-united-eyeing-up-bristol-citys-nicky-maynard/</guid>
      <description>Maynard - May be a target for Alan Pardew if other forwards don&amp;rsquo;t arrive There&amp;rsquo;s some interesting news regarding our search for a striker; and that Alan Pardew may have turned his attention to Bristol City&amp;rsquo;s main man - Nicky Maynard. The striker is 24 years of age, fitting our age category for recruitments and is out of contract at the end of this forthcoming season - meaning he could be obtained for a half decent price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you take Carlton Cole to St.James’ Park at this stage of the transfer window?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/06/would-you-take-carlton-cole-to-st-james-at-this-stage-of-the-transfer-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/06/would-you-take-carlton-cole-to-st-james-at-this-stage-of-the-transfer-window/</guid>
      <description>Cole - Would you pair him up front with new summer signing Demba Ba? With a deal for Paris St.Germain striker Mevlut Erding dead or seemingly so - you really have to ask yourself what strikers Newcastle United are still pursuing. Peter Crouch, Jermain Defoe, Shane Long, and even Jermaine Beckford have all been linked with us this summer to name but a few but it is unlikely that any of the above will end up on Tyneside come the end of August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The scenario that will more than likely face Newcastle United fans on August 31st</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/05/the-scenario-that-will-more-than-likely-face-newcastle-united-fans-on-august-31st/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 16:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/05/the-scenario-that-will-more-than-likely-face-newcastle-united-fans-on-august-31st/</guid>
      <description>Questions - Who will be at Newcastle United and who&amp;rsquo;ll be gone come Aug 31st? Seemingly the drama surrounding Joey Barton, Twitter and the board and indeed Jose Enrique&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;impending&amp;rsquo; move to Liverpool is somewhat putting our transfer exploits on the back-burner - for the media at least. Today we found out that there have been talks with Tranquillo Barnetta and NUFC and that those very talks were going quite well - only for the Swiss to suffer an injury that could postpone the move to January or indeed permanently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew could be very close to cracking point as manager of Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/01/alan-pardew-could-be-very-close-to-cracking-point-as-manager-of-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 11:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/08/01/alan-pardew-could-be-very-close-to-cracking-point-as-manager-of-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>#### Pardew - Get the feeling all is not well under the covers at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park
It could well be just me, but I think there is something pretty serious going on at Newcastle United right now and it might not be very encouraging at all. Recent criticisms of the board and their regime have been well documented in the press the last week or so, with Jose Enrique openly venting his frustration at Mike Ashley and the lack of ambition show by the club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darron Gibson not a player Newcastle United should be looking at this summer</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/27/darron-gibson-not-a-player-newcastle-united-should-be-looking-at-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 21:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/27/darron-gibson-not-a-player-newcastle-united-should-be-looking-at-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>#### Gibson - Not good enough for our midfield and not worth five million
In the last couple of days, Irish midfielder Darron Gibson has been strongly linked with a move away from Manchester United and more noticeably to the Stadium of Light to join an already meagre midfield setup. However, as I mentioned in articles before this; Newcastle United and SAFC seem to share an awful lot of similar targets and are inevitably linked with the same players, over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you want Stephen Ireland back at Newcastle United permanently?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/26/would-you-take-stephen-ireland-back-to-st-james-park-for-next-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 10:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/26/would-you-take-stephen-ireland-back-to-st-james-park-for-next-season/</guid>
      <description>Ireland - Has raw talent but can he regain old form at St. James&amp;rsquo; Park? There are emerging reports that Alan Pardew may well be interested in bringing Stephen Ireland back to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park on a permanent basis this summer. The Irishman, who had an injury plagued loan spell with Newcastle never really got going and played a mere 2 times for the club: both as substitute appearances. I think we all remember what a player this guy was only a couple of years ago; indeed he was awarded the Player Of the Year award at Eastlands for his fantastic endeavours throughout the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint-Étienne’s Blaise Matuidi the preferred replacement for Kevin Nolan</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/20/saint-etiennes-blaise-matuidi-the-preferred-replacement-for-kevin-nolan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 15:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/20/saint-etiennes-blaise-matuidi-the-preferred-replacement-for-kevin-nolan/</guid>
      <description>#### Matuidi - Being targeted by Alan Pardew as a replacement for Kevin Nolan
I suppose there&amp;rsquo;s two sides to the story regarding Kevin Nolan&amp;rsquo;s departure to West Ham. A large chunk of the fans will blame the ownership for stalling on a new deal, and failing to reward their captain for the fantastic season his put in on our return to the Premier League, yielding twelve goals. The other side, will see Nolan&amp;rsquo;s move as a step forward for Newcastle United; one more high waged player off the bill and an aging, slow midfielder no longer our responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United set to sign Mevlut Erding in the next few days?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/14/newcastle-united-set-to-sign-mevlut-erding-in-the-next-few-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/14/newcastle-united-set-to-sign-mevlut-erding-in-the-next-few-days/</guid>
      <description>Erding - Expected to sign in the coming week or so for a fee in the region of £8m It seems as if our failure with Kevin Gameiro and likely end of interest in Lille&amp;rsquo;s Gervinho has brought Alan Pardew onto his next target: Paris Saint-Germain striker Mevlut Erding. Of course if you remember correctly we were after this guy back in August 2010 and had a £5m rejected with Chris Hughton in charge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United &amp; Sunderland set to battle it out for Craig Gardner</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/14/newcastle-united-sunderland-set-to-battle-it-out-for-craig-gardner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/14/newcastle-united-sunderland-set-to-battle-it-out-for-craig-gardner/</guid>
      <description>Gardner - In high demand after Birmingham&amp;rsquo;s drop from the Premier League Whatever players Sunderland are being linked to, it seems we&amp;rsquo;re also looking to sign them. Of course that is usually the case, but now more than ever. From the top of my head, since the end of the season, the following players have been strongly linked with both of us: Jay Bothroyd, Sebastian Larsson, Demba Ba, Peter Crouch, Charles N&amp;rsquo;Zogbia, Emile Heskey, Kieran Westwood and now Craig Gardner , to mention but a few.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United ‘agree terms’ with Senegalese international Demba Ba</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/11/newcastle-united-agree-terms-with-senegalese-international-demba-ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/11/newcastle-united-agree-terms-with-senegalese-international-demba-ba/</guid>
      <description>Ba - Reports are suggesting we have signed the African for a small amount There are reports swirling around both Twitter and a few radio stations that we have signed Demba Ba for a minimal amount. The Senegalese international is supposedly a free transfer now after a clause in his contract was triggered, seeing him become a free agent courtesy of West Ham&amp;rsquo;s relegation from the Premier League. I&amp;rsquo;m sure most of us will have noticed that he scored a nice few goals in his time at Upton Park and tried his best to keep them in the top flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United stand a very good chance of landing Charles N’Zogbia</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/10/newcastle-united-stand-a-very-good-chance-of-landing-charles-nzogbia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 22:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/10/newcastle-united-stand-a-very-good-chance-of-landing-charles-nzogbia/</guid>
      <description>N&amp;rsquo;Zogbia - Seems like he wants to return to St. James&amp;rsquo; Park again I must admit; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really that disappointed to see Charles N&amp;rsquo;Zogbia depart Newcastle United on January 3 years ago and in fact, was excited at the prospect of capturing Ryan Taylor. Taylor, who just couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop scoring against Newcastle each season had indeed nabbed a very important goal in that very season, a spectacular free-kick if I remember correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United set for most exciting summer transfer window in years</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/09/newcastle-united-set-for-most-exciting-summer-transfer-window-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/09/newcastle-united-set-for-most-exciting-summer-transfer-window-in-years/</guid>
      <description>Gervinho - Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too surprised if he doesn&amp;rsquo;t arrive on Tyneside I&amp;rsquo;m sure that most the Premier League are aware of the Gervinho scenario by now. Over a week ago he was meant to have signed for Newcastle United, alongside Yohan Cabaye. The funny this is: neither have signed officially yet however, Cabaye is expected to be revealed holding our new 2011&amp;frasl;12 jersey as early as tomorrow. I am also quite sure that most internet friendly NUFC fans will have wandered on to Twitter at some stage, whether it&amp;rsquo;s been to follow us or indeed keep tabs on the many rumour &amp;lsquo;merchants&amp;rsquo; flooding the Newcastle news scene lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Carew would be a worthwhile signing for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/27/john-carew-would-be-a-worthwhile-signing-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 14:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/27/john-carew-would-be-a-worthwhile-signing-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Carew - Released by Aston Villa today after completing loan spell at Stoke City I have always been a fan of John Carew and was quite disappointed to see him go to Villa first, especially as a swap deal for Milan Baros. His first season with Villa saw him produce 3 goals in 11 appearances, his first happened to come against us when we beat them 3-1. A strong, combative CF is what Carew brings to the plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clint Dempsey is a player Newcastle United should be looking at this summer</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/02/clint-dempsey-is-a-player-newcastle-united-should-be-looking-at-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/05/02/clint-dempsey-is-a-player-newcastle-united-should-be-looking-at-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>Dempsey - A brilliant player that has scored over 10 goals this season I have been watching Clint Dempsey for a few years now and he continues to impress me. His flair, vision and ability to score goals is something that a lot of people have not recognised, and he has not got half enough praise for his endeavours for both his country, and for Fulham over the years. He would be right up my list of players to sign this summer although I&amp;rsquo;m sure Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s wishlist would differ quite a bit from mine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you really want Gervinho at Newcastle United next season?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/04/26/do-you-really-want-gervinho-at-newcastle-united-next-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 14:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/04/26/do-you-really-want-gervinho-at-newcastle-united-next-season/</guid>
      <description>Gervinho - Strong links between him and Newcastle since Hughton&amp;rsquo;s time The rumours regards Gervinho&amp;rsquo;s future at Lille have been circling for the past 18 months. Lille signed the Ivorian from Le Mans for a fee of about €9m and he has been scoring goals quite frequently in Ligue 1, however he is already being linked with a move away from France and it is more than likely that he will make a move this summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United can confirm safety at Villa Park – The place where the Geordie passion grew stronger</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/04/07/newcastle-united-can-confirm-safety-at-villa-park-the-place-where-the-geordie-passion-grew-stronger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 10:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/04/07/newcastle-united-can-confirm-safety-at-villa-park-the-place-where-the-geordie-passion-grew-stronger/</guid>
      <description>#### Houllier - Faces a difficult challenge in motivating a lacklustre Villa side
Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m alone in my opinion of Gerard Houllier but I regard the Frenchman as one of those managers who always seem to get decent jobs, yet have very little understanding of the modern game. When Martin O&amp;rsquo;Neill left Villa Park things took a change for the worst. Milner had gone, Ashley Young was looking for a way out (still is) and John Carew; one of the most prominent strikers was loaned out to Stoke City for the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s hope Nile Ranger doesn’t ruin his future at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/08/lets-hope-nile-ranger-doesnt-ruin-his-future-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/08/lets-hope-nile-ranger-doesnt-ruin-his-future-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Any time he has come on the pitch he has upped the tempo. His strength, height, ability in the air and his quick feet have caused problems for Liverpool, Arsenal, Chelsea and many other teams this season. He is 19 years of age, 6 feet 2 inches in height and has the potential to a Premier League class striker if not more. Nile Ranger&amp;rsquo;s attitude however is something that has caused problems in the past and continues to do so on a smaller level in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Pardew can help Stephen Ireland rediscover his top form at Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/04/alan-pardew-can-help-stephen-ireland-rediscover-his-top-form-at-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 22:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/03/04/alan-pardew-can-help-stephen-ireland-rediscover-his-top-form-at-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>#### Ireland - Can be a quality player under Alan Pardew at Newcastle United
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t that long ago when the we all watched Stephen Ireland become Manchester City&amp;rsquo;s Player Of The Season - less than two years ago in fact. The Cork-born midfielder excelled under Mark Hughes whilst Manchester City manager but since then the big spending Italian Roberto Mancini took the reigns and made it clear very quickly that he didn&amp;rsquo;t see a future for Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There comes a time in football when realism must prevail</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/01/there-comes-a-time-in-football-when-realism-must-prevail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 19:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/02/01/there-comes-a-time-in-football-when-realism-must-prevail/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Off to Anfield whether pushed or shoved out of St. James&amp;rsquo; Park irst things first; yesterdays deadline window was no doubt the most enthralling transfer window I have ever followed, but Sky Sports really did over-do the whole thing. Every 5 minutes they popped back to David Craig outside St.James&amp;rsquo; Park and he seemed to have a new story, or something a little different each time. If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t that, they were in Liverpool trying to get the latest on the Fernando Torres deal from their correspondent, amidst overly-excited LFC fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two players Newcastle United should look at bringing in this January</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/19/two-players-newcastle-united-should-look-at-bringing-in-this-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 09:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/19/two-players-newcastle-united-should-look-at-bringing-in-this-january/</guid>
      <description>That sick feeling of Sunderland&amp;rsquo;s 93rd minute equaliser still lingers somewhat as I write this article, but it could have been worse; it could have been a 93rd winner for them, and our best striker could have handed in a transfer request the day after the game - Imagine that!
However, we proved yet again yesterday that we are better than Sunderland on the pitch, and were so unlucky not to have done the double over Steve Bruce&amp;rsquo;s side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunderland v Newcastle United : Step forward Shola Ameobi</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/15/sunderland-v-newcastle-united-step-forward-shola-ameobi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 20:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/15/sunderland-v-newcastle-united-step-forward-shola-ameobi/</guid>
      <description>Ameobi - Can he extend his extremely good record in Tyne-Wear derbies at SOL?
I think everyone will remember at least two of Shola Ameobi&amp;rsquo;s many goals against Sunderland throughout the years, and that&amp;rsquo;s without counting his brace when we thrashed them at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park at Halloween. He has a very good record of scoring against SAFC down through the years, and we will need him more than ever tomorrow at the Stadium Of Light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stevenage v Newcastle United – An FA Cup affair that the lads should handle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/08/stevenage-v-newcastle-united-an-fa-cup-affair-that-the-lads-should-handle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 16:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/08/stevenage-v-newcastle-united-an-fa-cup-affair-that-the-lads-should-handle/</guid>
      <description>Best - Should be available for the tie against Stevenage this evening It&amp;rsquo;s that time of the year again when the FA Cup dominates the scene. Newcastle United are away to Stevenage at 5.30 and it is live on TV, which is a bit of a novelty in FA Cup ties nowadays. However, it won&amp;rsquo;t be an easy feat against the League 2 outfit, if we give them too much respect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Alan Pardew, Please do not sign Robbie Keane</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/03/dear-alan-pardew-please-do-not-sign-robbie-keane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 18:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/03/dear-alan-pardew-please-do-not-sign-robbie-keane/</guid>
      <description>I have noticed in the last couple of weeks amongst many Newcastle United fans, how excited they are at the prospect of Robbie Keane arriving on Tyneside. I however, do not want the Tallaght man to join Newcastle United and a lot of Irish NUFC fans are in agreements with me. Of course, you will wonder why I do no want to sign a proven striker, that has scored at the highest level , from the World Cup to the Premier League, indeed a forward who has scored goals anywhere he went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United should venture in for Jô with Edin Džeko set for January move</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/29/newcastle-united-should-venture-in-for-jo-with-edin-dzeko-set-for-january-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 18:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/29/newcastle-united-should-venture-in-for-jo-with-edin-dzeko-set-for-january-move/</guid>
      <description>#### Jô - Would be an extremely good addition to Newcastle United this January
It is very likely that Edin Džeko will join Manchester City this January in a €35m move come January as VfL Wolfsburg have lowered their asking initial asking price. Another ridiculous fee to pay for a striker who I can only guess would be delighted to join the club for its wages. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, Edin is a fine talent and will score a lot of goals given the chance, but he isn&amp;rsquo;t worth any more than £17m in all honesty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirited Newcastle United performance undone by misfortune and Tevez</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/26/spirited-newcastle-united-performance-undone-by-misfortune-and-tevez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2010 22:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/26/spirited-newcastle-united-performance-undone-by-misfortune-and-tevez/</guid>
      <description>#### Carroll - Scored yet again today and continues to be linked with Toon exit
Frustrating isn&amp;rsquo;t the word. When Fabricio Coloccini put the ball into his own net in the last ten minutes of the game, my heart sank and I nearly dropped my turkey sandwich. We had dominated the second half, every ball was ours, Carroll won every header, Cheik Tiote cleaned up every spill in centre midfield and Jose Enrique &amp;amp; Jonas Gutierrez swept up everything on the leftside of the pitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To all Newcastle United fans – Happy Christmas from Tyne Time</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/24/to-all-newcastle-united-fans-happy-christmas-from-tyne-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 22:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/24/to-all-newcastle-united-fans-happy-christmas-from-tyne-time/</guid>
      <description>NUFC - Has been a hectic year for Newcastle United as club but enjoy Xmas! It really has been a frantic year as a Newcastle United supporter. From January till May, we were crowned Coca Cola Championship champions with a record number of points, and back in the Premier League after a little while away. We had made great improvements since the bad years upon Tyneside, with stability under Chris Hughton, and a great team spirit amongst the lads in the dressing -room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United close to signing Ben Arfa – An early Christmas present?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/23/newcastle-united-close-to-signing-ben-arfa-an-early-christmas-present/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 16:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/23/newcastle-united-close-to-signing-ben-arfa-an-early-christmas-present/</guid>
      <description>#### Ben Arfa - Wants to play for Newcastle United and is looking for permanent deal
We may well be in for an early Christmas present with the new that Hatem Ben Arfa, could be quite close to a permanent deal at Newcastle United. The French winger who joined this summer thanks to Chris Hughton, played less than five games, in which he scored a stunner against Everton at Goodison Park, in an excellent away win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joey Barton available for £1.5m – West Ham &amp; Aston Villa line up bids.</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/joey-barton-available-for-1-5m-west-ham-aston-villa-line-up-bids/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 15:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/joey-barton-available-for-1-5m-west-ham-aston-villa-line-up-bids/</guid>
      <description>Barton - Newcastle have set an asking fee of £1.5m for the midfielder Everything that you hear from Newcastle United nowadays must be taken in with quite the opposite. Since Mike Ashley took over the club, things are gone bezerk to say the very least. As I said in my last article, we cannot really trust the owners of the club until they have handed over the keys to new owners and are on their way home - indeed the likelihood of that happening is quite low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Newcastle United need to sign anyone this January transfer window?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/do-newcastle-united-need-to-sign-anyone-this-january-transfer-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 01:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/21/do-newcastle-united-need-to-sign-anyone-this-january-transfer-window/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people aren&amp;rsquo;t really sure of Alan Pardew yet, and one of the areas he can send out a message to Newcastle United fans is in the transfer market. In 10 or so days times, the January transfer window will open for business. Teams will enquire for players, other will try their utmost to hang on to their key men. Indeed that&amp;rsquo;s what I expect us to do this January, try keep Andy Carroll, Joey Barton and some of our youngsters at NUFC for the remainder of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United 3-1 Liverpool – A Tribute to Chris Hughton</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/11/newcastle-united-3-1-liverpool-a-tribute-to-chris-hughton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 23:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/12/11/newcastle-united-3-1-liverpool-a-tribute-to-chris-hughton/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Scored a peach of a goal today in a very good win dedicated to Chris First things first - what a brave man Mike Ashley is showing up to Newcastle United v Liverpool today. I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to see his unsightly figure in the luxurious stands of St.James&amp;rsquo; Park during Alan Pardew&amp;rsquo;s first game in charge. However, I expect it was exactly that that lured the owner to the game, to oversee his new signing, and to decide whether he needed the sack just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>