<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kevin Nolan on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/kevin-nolan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kevin Nolan on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 15:16:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/kevin-nolan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint-Étienne’s Blaise Matuidi the preferred replacement for Kevin Nolan</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/20/saint-etiennes-blaise-matuidi-the-preferred-replacement-for-kevin-nolan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 15:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/06/20/saint-etiennes-blaise-matuidi-the-preferred-replacement-for-kevin-nolan/</guid>
      <description>#### Matuidi - Being targeted by Alan Pardew as a replacement for Kevin Nolan
I suppose there&amp;rsquo;s two sides to the story regarding Kevin Nolan&amp;rsquo;s departure to West Ham. A large chunk of the fans will blame the ownership for stalling on a new deal, and failing to reward their captain for the fantastic season his put in on our return to the Premier League, yielding twelve goals. The other side, will see Nolan&amp;rsquo;s move as a step forward for Newcastle United; one more high waged player off the bill and an aging, slow midfielder no longer our responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carroll &amp; Nolan binge after the Sunderland victory, where do the media get off?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/07/carroll-nolan-binge-after-the-sunderland-victory-where-do-the-media-get-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 13:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/11/07/carroll-nolan-binge-after-the-sunderland-victory-where-do-the-media-get-off/</guid>
      <description>Carroll - Staying in Nolan&amp;rsquo;s house since his courting hearing a few weeks ago Well my latest article has been a long time coming and I apologise for that, however, I was intending on writing an article before the Tyne Wear derby about why on earth there was rumours of Chris Hughton being sacked, but when they won 5-1 it would&amp;rsquo;ve look a little suspect. Observing all the latest news about Newcastle in the latest few weeks has led me to inevitably write this article, quite frankly because I can&amp;rsquo; believe what I&amp;rsquo;m seeing day in day out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Nolan knows what it means to Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/24/kevin-nolan-knows-what-it-means-to-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 15:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/11/24/kevin-nolan-knows-what-it-means-to-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Newcastle again fought their way to a victory in rather undesirable conditions, in Deepdale. Kevin Nolan turned in his 9th goal of the season and again leads the scoring charts. From the first whistle, it was a game that could go either way but the further the game progressed, you just felt that a goal was coming for the Toon. Indeed it did come, and it quite a tasty goal to say the least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nolan nabs Newcastle winner as Toon go top</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/24/nolan-nabs-newcastle-winner-as-toon-go-top/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 19:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/24/nolan-nabs-newcastle-winner-as-toon-go-top/</guid>
      <description>### Nolan - Great strike to win it
A win is a win, sure enough, but there was nothing spectacular about Newcastle triumphing today, far from it. A 90th minute strike today sealed our first victory in some time and it came none sweeter than a right footed pelter into the bottom corner. The most important thing today is that we did indeed claim all three points, and we need to do the same for the majority of our home games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toon manage to tame tempered Terriers</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/toon-manage-to-tame-tempered-terriers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 22:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/toon-manage-to-tame-tempered-terriers/</guid>
      <description>Well in what was quiet an exciting game to say the least, Newcastle United managed to overcome Huddersfield Town. Goals from Shola Ameobi, Danny Guthrie, Geremi (I know 😮 ) and Kevin Nolan sealed a great comeback for the hard-working lads. Indeed that&amp;rsquo;s what they did, they worked. Although we had to introduce our first teamers, it was quiet a good performance all round by the little Newcastle squad. The much talked about, Nile Ranger played the game and did quiet well in what seemed to be a 4-5-1 formation from stand in boss, Chris Hughton.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>