<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Barry Moat on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/barry-moat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Barry Moat on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 15:15:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/barry-moat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moat’s Toon takeover hopes hit for 5</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/07/moats-toon-takeover-hopes-hit-for-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 15:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/07/moats-toon-takeover-hopes-hit-for-5/</guid>
      <description>As the great Ed Harrison reported on nufcblog.com, the settlement of the Keegan case would leave to some more takeover stories and indeed ones that are far from relevant. Just as Barry Moat was set to seal a deal and we think he is still in the driving seat, new consortia come along, on top of the other two already witting against the local Tyneside businessman. Today brings the news that South Africans have entered the race too, just like last year, expect they had no money to back their interest, story of NUFC all summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Moat about to keep Newcastle afloat</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/06/barry-moat-about-to-keep-newcastle-afloat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 15:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/06/barry-moat-about-to-keep-newcastle-afloat/</guid>
      <description>As it finally seems Mike Ashley will pack his bags and leave Newcastle United, a little premature excitement is creeping in. Not just the fact he&amp;rsquo;s leaving (or so we are led to believe) but also the reality that we are set to get a local owner, and not many clubs can say that. Today reports say that Mr.Barry Moat has written a letter to Mike with a formal offer, expected to be in the region of £90-95m and we expect our current owner to accept it or God knows what will happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Ashley days are finally numbered</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/04/mike-ashley-days-are-finally-numbered/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2009 12:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/10/04/mike-ashley-days-are-finally-numbered/</guid>
      <description>### Moat - At long last will complete takeover
Finally the day has come when I can say that Mike Ashley will not be Newcastle United owner for another few months. The Keegan scenario has been dealt with and £2m is a shock relief for Mike Ashley and his compatriots. This is good news, as it means that the wreckage has been cleared from the track to complete the sale of Newcastle United, and the long awaited one at that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silence is deafening on takeover front</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/28/silence-is-deafening-on-takeover-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 15:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/28/silence-is-deafening-on-takeover-front/</guid>
      <description>The news hasn&amp;rsquo;t bee based on the takeover news this Sunday or indeed the last week, which is quite surprising. Barry Moat is still on course to complete the takeover of our beloved club but he;s waiting on the Kevin Keegan court case to be settled before he&amp;rsquo;s handed the keys of St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. You can imagine the scenes around Newcastle when Mike Ashley finally leaves the club, and a local owner with every ambition to appoint Alan Shearer as manager, control the club properly, or so we hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle sale in final stages – again</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/19/newcastle-sale-in-final-stages-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/19/newcastle-sale-in-final-stages-again/</guid>
      <description>### Ashley - Agreed fee with unnamed group
We haven&amp;rsquo;t heard much on the Newcastle United sale lately but today brings news that a fee has been agreed with a buyer. The club issued an official statement to the &amp;lsquo;Journal&amp;rsquo; saying that the £100m had been met but the overdraft was still a stumbling block as well as the Kevin Keegan scenario. Although Barry Moat is being strongly linked with the role, and it&amp;rsquo;s more than likely he is the man involved, there are reported to be two other bidders interested in the club, but yet to make an official bid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moat’s takeover plans still afloat?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/05/moats-takeover-plans-still-afloat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/05/moats-takeover-plans-still-afloat/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re led to believe that Tuesday is the day of reckoning for Barry Moat and Newcastle United. Indeed it would bring Mike Ashley&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;deadlines&amp;rsquo; well into double figures without any end result in either of them. We&amp;rsquo;re sick of the constant rumours of who is taking us over and who isn&amp;rsquo;t, we just want new owners, and now, it seems that Barry Moat is well and truly the last contender for the club after the supposed American group failed to produce proof of funds, sound familiar?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Moat is Newcastle’s last chance saloon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/24/barry-moat-is-newcastles-last-chance-saloon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 14:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/24/barry-moat-is-newcastles-last-chance-saloon/</guid>
      <description>Ashley - Still in control Mike Ashley is still in control of Newcastle United, 13 weeks after we suffered the dreaded drop to the Coca Cola Championship. The news today, is that the deadline has been extended for Barry Moat to complete the takeover of the club but that news, carries both good and bad consequences. First of all it means we probably will not sign anyone this transfer window at all but the upside is, that Mike Ashley is very much willing to sell to Barry Moat and is trying his utmost to hand over the club to the local businessman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Taylor could well have played his last game for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/steven-taylor-could-well-have-played-his-last-game-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad when it has come to this, a Newcastle United player, brought through the ranks, and having becoming a Newcastle United first team member, looking for the exit door at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. Sky Sports News (who else?) are reporting that the local lad, could be set for a move to David Moyes&amp;rsquo;s Everton side who are fighting a losing battle with their own English centre back, Joleon Lescott. If this news is true, which we hope it&amp;rsquo;s not, then it&amp;rsquo;ll really put gas to the fire and the frustration will be taken out on Mike Ashley more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llambias – Barry Moat close to completing takeover</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/llambias-barry-moat-close-to-completing-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/20/llambias-barry-moat-close-to-completing-takeover/</guid>
      <description>We can&amp;rsquo;t fault the lads performances over the season so far, two wins and a draw, that draw being a dreaded away trip to the Hawthorns for any other Championship side. However Newcastle United are not any Championship side, only at Newcastle could we attract nearly 44,000 to a home game, mind you, it only being the third game of the season and the traveling Geordies weren&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. Another Ameobi goal and another three points, leaving Newcastle 3rd in the Coca Cola Championship league standings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moat may not complete Newcastle sale</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/moat-may-not-complete-newcastle-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 11:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/19/moat-may-not-complete-newcastle-sale/</guid>
      <description>The future of Newcastle United lies with a bank called Barclays, the sponsors of the Premier League. Today (Wednesday), Barry Moat was expected to hear back on whether he&amp;rsquo;s request was successful. If he is not which there is a good chance in happening, then Newcastle will remain in the hands of Mike Ashley until January at the very least, however, we&amp;rsquo;re hopeful that Moat does indeed get his loan from Barry Moat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Moat has competition for Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/18/barry-moat-has-competition-for-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/18/barry-moat-has-competition-for-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>Derek Llambias today confirmed to Sky Sports News that Barry Moat has indeed begun talks with the clubs hierarchy over the sale of the beleaguered club. Moat was present at our 3-0 win over Reading in which was one of the finest games the lads have played in St.James&amp;rsquo; Park in a long time. At the final whistle, Moat was seen shaking hands with Mike Ashley, perhaps just a business style fashion but it could be interpreted as agreeing on the sale of the club in principle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shola strolls in St.James’ success</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/15/shola-strolls-in-st-james-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/15/shola-strolls-in-st-james-success/</guid>
      <description>### Ameobi - Sublime three goals today
In a game which saw potential Newcastle United owner Barry Moat sit inbetween the current hierarchy at Newcastle of Mike Ashley and Derek Llambias, Newcastle produced a performance to remember and one needed to boost all sides morale. Newcastle started the game brightly creating chances and were comfortably controlling the game. Jonas was presented with a great opportunity after a Kevin Nolan through ball but the Argentine per usual, stumbled and didn&amp;rsquo;t show an end product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley and Moat both stubborn businessmen</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/12/ashley-and-moat-both-stubborn-businessmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 13:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/12/ashley-and-moat-both-stubborn-businessmen/</guid>
      <description>### Moat - Stubborn as Ashley
OK, you might be saying to yourself, Ashley is far from a businessman and has no brain at all. Each day it keeps tilting towards that instinct but considering he was a billionaire, he must have done some things right. He&amp;rsquo;s the owner of most Sports Direct retail stores, and even though their sales went sky high this year, their operating profit has decreased steadily from the last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ball is in Barry Moat’s court now</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/11/the-ball-is-in-barry-moats-court-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 13:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/11/the-ball-is-in-barry-moats-court-now/</guid>
      <description>Moat - Needs to deposit funds by Friday It seems that the decision is with Barry Moat whether to buy the club at this stage. It&amp;rsquo;s understood that Mike Ashley is willing to accept the offer from Moat but he wants a deposit by Friday in an unspecified bank account. If Moat can do this then he will complete the takeover and we will be finally be Ashley free. Whether Moat can agree to this is another thing, Ashley will then take Newcastle United off the market and appoint either David O&amp;rsquo;Leary or Joe Kinnear to the managerial role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Barry Moat float our boat?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/06/will-barry-moat-float-our-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 14:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/06/will-barry-moat-float-our-boat/</guid>
      <description>Moat - Has reportedly bid £100m The latest news coming for St.James&amp;rsquo; Park is that a local business tycoon has bid £100m for Newcastle United. This news comes as yesterdays article from The Times and The Chronicle claimed that local business tycoon was ready to invest into the club. Moat is a luxury box-office holder at Newcastle and has been for some time now. The payment from which he renewed his season ticket, the money was used in the youth setup and invested in that area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>