<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shola Ameobi on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/shola-ameobi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shola Ameobi on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 14:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/shola-ameobi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shola Ameobi laments lack of ambition at NUFC in radio interview</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/23/shola-ameobi-laments-lack-ambition-nufc-radio-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 14:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/04/23/shola-ameobi-laments-lack-ambition-nufc-radio-interview/</guid>
      <description>If it was ever in doubt, Shola Ameobi all but confirmed that he is to leave Newcastle United when his contract runs out at the end of the season in a radio interview with BBC Newcastle. The Nigerian international scored the opener in Saturday&amp;rsquo;s defeat to Swansea City in what may prove to be his final ever goal in a Black and White jersey. Ameobi has been on the books at NUFC for a staggering 14 years, and I say staggering because in that time he failed to convince many that he actually is a striker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The forgotten man who has a huge part to play in Newcastle United’s Top 4 push</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/20/the-forgotten-man-who-has-a-huge-part-to-play-in-newcastle-uniteds-top-4-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 16:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/04/20/the-forgotten-man-who-has-a-huge-part-to-play-in-newcastle-uniteds-top-4-push/</guid>
      <description>Ameobi - Joint longest serving Newcastle United player in the current squad While Demba Ba and Papiss Cissé receive nationwide praise for their goal scoring efforts this campaign and rightly so - there is one man who perhaps doesn&amp;rsquo;t get enough credit for his endeavours this season. That man is our joint longest serving player in the squad: Shola Ameobi. There hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a season that&amp;rsquo;s passed when Shola hasn&amp;rsquo;t managed an important goal or two, particularly against Sunderland, but that&amp;rsquo;s a story for another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunderland v Newcastle United : Step forward Shola Ameobi</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/15/sunderland-v-newcastle-united-step-forward-shola-ameobi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 20:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2011/01/15/sunderland-v-newcastle-united-step-forward-shola-ameobi/</guid>
      <description>Ameobi - Can he extend his extremely good record in Tyne-Wear derbies at SOL?
I think everyone will remember at least two of Shola Ameobi&amp;rsquo;s many goals against Sunderland throughout the years, and that&amp;rsquo;s without counting his brace when we thrashed them at St.James&amp;rsquo; Park at Halloween. He has a very good record of scoring against SAFC down through the years, and we will need him more than ever tomorrow at the Stadium Of Light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could Shola Ameobi be in line for the coveted #9 shirt?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/09/could-shola-ameobi-be-in-line-for-the-coveted-9-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 16:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/04/09/could-shola-ameobi-be-in-line-for-the-coveted-9-shirt/</guid>
      <description>Born in Nigeria but an English international at a young age, Shola Ameobi has been at Newcastle United for quite some time now. He was there for Shearer&amp;rsquo;s later glory days at the start of the new millennium and now he himself, has been playing pretty well in a Newcastle shirt of late. A lot of people regard Ameobi as a clumsy, lanky striker and some people have attributed the nick name &amp;lsquo;Stumbling Bambi&amp;rsquo; to the Toon striker as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ameobi limps off as Dorran’s penalties knock Toon out of FA Cup</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/23/ameobi-limps-off-as-dorrans-penalties-knock-toon-out-of-fa-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 19:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2010/01/23/ameobi-limps-off-as-dorrans-penalties-knock-toon-out-of-fa-cup/</guid>
      <description>Dorrans - Lethal from the penalty spot today as Brom progress to the next round I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t our best performance all season today at the Hawthorns, and when Jonas Olsson was again the first scorer you knew it wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be our day. I can&amp;rsquo;t say I saw the match but updates on nufc.co.uk got me through the feisty affair. Pre-match I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too concerned if were going to be knocked out or not but of course I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have minded a victory away to one our promotion rivals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harewood &amp; Ameobi send Middlesbrough marching</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/20/harewood-ameobi-send-middlesbrough-marching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 18:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/12/20/harewood-ameobi-send-middlesbrough-marching/</guid>
      <description>Another three points and another win against Middlesbrough. Well done Chris Hughton and well done the lads. In rather chilly conditions in St.James&amp;rsquo; Park, Marlon Harewood &amp;amp; Shola Ameobi both netted to ensure that we will have a happy Christmas period with a ten point gap between ourselves and West Bromich Albion. Although the game started quite slowly and perhaps Boro having the better spell of possession, it was Marlon Harewood who latched on to a Shola Ameobi knock-down to slide the ball home and bring his tally to 5 this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shola Ameobi will be sorely missed – first time we’ve heard that</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/04/shola-ameobi-will-be-sorely-missed-first-time-weve-heard-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 17:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/09/04/shola-ameobi-will-be-sorely-missed-first-time-weve-heard-that/</guid>
      <description>Who would&amp;rsquo;ve thought or indeed would&amp;rsquo;ve said, a year ago, that Shola Ameobi would be a huge loss to Newcastle United&amp;rsquo;s strike force? Ameobi, who is Nigerian by birth is starting to show, this season at least, some of the quality the famous Nigerian strikers had. Bagging a hattrick against Reading, scoring the winner v Sheffield Wednesday and adding to his tally in the Carling Cup vs Huddersfield, Shola has established himself as a real threat to Championship defences this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toon manage to tame tempered Terriers</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/toon-manage-to-tame-tempered-terriers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 22:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/toon-manage-to-tame-tempered-terriers/</guid>
      <description>Well in what was quiet an exciting game to say the least, Newcastle United managed to overcome Huddersfield Town. Goals from Shola Ameobi, Danny Guthrie, Geremi (I know 😮 ) and Kevin Nolan sealed a great comeback for the hard-working lads. Indeed that&amp;rsquo;s what they did, they worked. Although we had to introduce our first teamers, it was quiet a good performance all round by the little Newcastle squad. The much talked about, Nile Ranger played the game and did quiet well in what seemed to be a 4-5-1 formation from stand in boss, Chris Hughton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shola strolls in St.James’ success</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/15/shola-strolls-in-st-james-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/15/shola-strolls-in-st-james-success/</guid>
      <description>### Ameobi - Sublime three goals today
In a game which saw potential Newcastle United owner Barry Moat sit inbetween the current hierarchy at Newcastle of Mike Ashley and Derek Llambias, Newcastle produced a performance to remember and one needed to boost all sides morale. Newcastle started the game brightly creating chances and were comfortably controlling the game. Jonas was presented with a great opportunity after a Kevin Nolan through ball but the Argentine per usual, stumbled and didn&amp;rsquo;t show an end product.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>