<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mathieu Debuchy on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/mathieu-debuchy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mathieu Debuchy on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 16:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/mathieu-debuchy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Arsenal fans need to know about Mathieu Debuchy</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/07/08/arsenal-fans-need-know-mathieu-debuchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 16:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/07/08/arsenal-fans-need-know-mathieu-debuchy/</guid>
      <description>Back in January 2013 when Newcastle United completed the signing of Mathieu Debuchy from Lille in a £5m deal - I wondered how the club had pulled it off. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the fact that he had been linked with a switch to Newcastle for months previous but such a deal never materialised, nor was it the fact that player was eager to join. Even with all that going in the favour of NUFC, it still surprised me when he signed the dotted line at St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midterm Report: How much has Mathieu Debuchy improved?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/20/midterm-report-much-mathieu-debuchy-improved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 20:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2014/01/20/midterm-report-much-mathieu-debuchy-improved/</guid>
      <description>Mathieu Debuchy was a player that Newcastle had tried to bring to St. James&amp;rsquo; Park before the 2012 European Championship. Just a few minutes into the illustrious footballing tournament is was easy to see why. In the right-back position for France Mathieu was quick, well versed tactically and loved to get forward from right-back to aid his teammates — an ideal candidate for the Premier League. Against England Debuchy performed admirably and his good form continued throughout the rest of the tournament until the French were eliminated in the last 16 by eventual champions, Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How much are we willing to pay for Mathieu Debuchy?</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/08/01/how-much-are-we-willing-to-pay-for-mathieu-debuchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 17:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/08/01/how-much-are-we-willing-to-pay-for-mathieu-debuchy/</guid>
      <description>Debuchy - Reports him of arriving on Tyneside this week for medical You get the feeling that if Newcastle United wanted Mathieu Debuchy that much, then we&amp;rsquo;d have signed him already. NUFC&amp;rsquo;s first ever bid for the French international was somewhere in the region of £4m, and was indeed deemed insufficient. Since then - more than a month later - we haven&amp;rsquo;t made any apparent progress with a deal. Despite the countless media reports that Mathieu is desperate to complete a move to St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United offering cash deal to FC Twente for de Jong</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/06/29/newcastle-united-offering-cash-deal-to-fc-twente-for-de-jong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 14:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/06/29/newcastle-united-offering-cash-deal-to-fc-twente-for-de-jong/</guid>
      <description>Llambias - Has flown over with Lee Charnley to agree a fee for FC Twente&amp;rsquo;s #9 When Derek Llambias boards a plane to Holland for Newcastle United related business, you know something big is happening. The latest update in the Luuk de Jong situation is that we have a delegation over in the Netherlands to hopefully agree a fee for the forward and begin contract negotiations - before the striker makes a Europa League performance and inevitably, deem him ineligible for European action in a NUFC shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bayern Munich to rival Newcastle United for defender</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/06/24/bayern-munich-to-rival-newcastle-united-for-defender/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 15:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2012/06/24/bayern-munich-to-rival-newcastle-united-for-defender/</guid>
      <description>#### Debuchy - A man in high demand after excellent Euro 2012 showing
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t come as a surprise to see that Alan Pardew is having a bit of trouble trying to lure his number one target to St.James&amp;rsquo; Park under the radar. Indeed, before the start of the European Championships, Pardew made quite an effort to seal a deal for Mathieu Debuchy and wanted Poland &amp;amp; Ukraine to be a warmup for his pre-season campaign with the Magpies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>