<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gareth Bale on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/gareth-bale/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gareth Bale on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 12:32:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/gareth-bale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Some transfer activity before Tuesday for Toon</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/27/some-transfer-activity-before-tuesday-for-toon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/27/some-transfer-activity-before-tuesday-for-toon/</guid>
      <description>Chris Hughton has given us the clearest indication yet that more players will leave at Newcastle and as well as that, new faces are set to arrive. As the transfer window closes very very soon, Hughton is braced for new arrivals and as reported last night Gareth Bale is rumoured to be extremely close to sealing a move. However, the only problem is, his wage demands. At Spurs, Bale is meant to be earning 45k a week and let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, that&amp;rsquo;s far too much for a lad his age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spurs defender close to sealing loan move to Newcastle</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/spurs-defender-close-to-sealing-loan-move-to-newcastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 22:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/26/spurs-defender-close-to-sealing-loan-move-to-newcastle/</guid>
      <description>Bale - Would be a good addition It appears, well according to the BBC, that Gareth Bale is very close to joining Newcastle United on loan from Tottenham Hotspur. The news breaks after Newcastle&amp;rsquo;s emphatic win against Huddersfield Town, well maybe not emphatic, but it was a memorable sight. When is the last time we&amp;rsquo;ve came from 1-3 down and still win?
Anyway, there&amp;rsquo;s sure to be more details following this outburst of news, but it would be rather warming to get Bale in, as I personally, rate him very highly, even though he hasn&amp;rsquo;t overly impressed at Tottenham.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>