<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ananda Krishnan on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/ananda-krishnan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ananda Krishnan on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 16:26:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/ananda-krishnan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ananda Krishnan not interested in Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/08/ananda-krishnan-not-interested-in-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/08/ananda-krishnan-not-interested-in-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>Krishnan - Why only deny interest now? Oh lordy, the nonsense continues . One minute Ananda Krishnan is all set to takeover and now he&amp;rsquo;s confirmed he&amp;rsquo;s not interested in buying the club at all. This leaves us questioning everything. Perhaps there is another Malaysian in there? Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s an Asian buyer or maybe , just maybe it&amp;rsquo;s that Singaporean group that said they were interested in buying last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysians expected to gain control of Newcastle United today or tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/08/malaysians-expected-to-gain-control-of-newcastle-united-today-or-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 12:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/08/malaysians-expected-to-gain-control-of-newcastle-united-today-or-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>The debacle seems to continue on for ever but Mike Ashley is leaving, it&amp;rsquo;s official, although we already knew that, it&amp;rsquo;s going to happen in the next couple of days with Ananda Krishnan completing the buyout. indeed £100m isn&amp;rsquo;t too much to the billionaire that is worth just under $8bn and I&amp;rsquo;m sure a £20m transfer budget wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be stretching the bank either 😀 We&amp;rsquo;re expecting a press conference soon about the announcement as the Malaysians are putting the finishing touches to the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports – Ananda Krishnan in £80m bid for Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/03/reports-ananda-krishnan-in-80m-bid-for-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 12:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/03/reports-ananda-krishnan-in-80m-bid-for-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>There is more news about the mystery Malaysian bidder today, and his name is believed to be Ananda Krishnan a rich foreigner that is worth $7.5bn, a little less than Robert Kuok but certainly a very wealthy man. Reports are surfacing, especially in
The Chronicle that an £80m bid has been submitted and that Seymour Pierce has recommended a buyer to to Mike Ashley already, indeed it&amp;rsquo;s believed to be this man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysians supposedly interested in purchasing Newcastle United</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/02/malaysians-supposedly-interested-in-purchasing-newcastle-united/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/02/malaysians-supposedly-interested-in-purchasing-newcastle-united/</guid>
      <description>According to BBC Radio, Derek Llambias was showing a Malaysian bidder around St.James&amp;rsquo; Park. This news has only broken so it&amp;rsquo;s in, its infancy details-wise. Apparently the bidder could be a representative of Robert Kuok, who is worth $10bn as of last year. That is some fortune to have, indeed his nickname is &amp;lsquo;Sugar King of Asia&amp;rsquo; because he is responsible for about 10% of the worlds sugar! To make it even better , he&amp;rsquo;s a modest and quiet man that keeps to himself, perfect for Newcastle United if you ask me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>