<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Obafemi Martins on </title>
    <link>https://www.tynetime.com/categories/obafemi-martins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Obafemi Martins on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 15:51:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tynetime.com/categories/obafemi-martins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The the first of many to leave St.James’ Park</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/01/the-the-first-of-many-to-leave-st-james-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 15:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/08/01/the-the-first-of-many-to-leave-st-james-park/</guid>
      <description>### Martins - Should succeed in Germany
The first of many departures at Newcastle has begun with Obafemi Martins&amp;rsquo;s transfer to Wolfsburg. The Bundesliga champions paid Newcastle €10.5m for the Nigerian and that&amp;rsquo;s not a bad fee to receive. The only thing is, we wonder where the money will go. Into Mike Ashley pocket or back into the club in order to buy new players. We still don&amp;rsquo;t know if there are new owners on the horizon but we certainly hope so as this day week, we play West Brom in the opening game of the Coca Cola Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye to a flipping legend</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/goodbye-to-a-flipping-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 21:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/29/goodbye-to-a-flipping-legend/</guid>
      <description>Martins - The goal that nearly kept us up It&amp;rsquo;s well and truly the end of an era when you see Obafemi Martins departing from St.James&amp;rsquo;. Although he had mixed receptions from supporters it was pretty clear he was loved upon Tyneside and will be sorely missed in our front line. Martins scored an abundance of goals in his first season after arriving for £10m and earned Alan Shearer&amp;rsquo;s much coveted #9 shirt for Newcastle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle United receive Coloccini and Oba Martins bids</title>
      <link>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/04/newcastle-united-receive-coloccini-and-oba-martins-bids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 12:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tynetime.com/2009/07/04/newcastle-united-receive-coloccini-and-oba-martins-bids/</guid>
      <description>Martins - Being forced out of Newcastle even though he wants to stay There are reports that Keith Harris, the guy in charge of selling Newcastle, has told Mike Ashley to accept bids for Fabricio Coloccini and Obafemi Martins to ease the financial strain on himself as the sale of NUFC nears a close. Obafemi Martins who has already said he wants to stay and doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to be sold is being forced out and the Journal have confirmed that bids from foreign clubs have been made for both players.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>